The whole country of the system is that
I am not in this movie
only my name is in this movie
"Bachchan"
Whatever they are saying
they are lying
I can swear on Geeta
That's the first dialogue of play
and where is Geeta?
And where is the Gandhi Ji's picture
behind the chair
How long I should wait?
You are busy to make over this court
Tomorrow we have real hearing
in court
Where is your brother Abbas?
You also know how I am collecting
money for this case
I have sold my own taxi for this case
who is running from 3 years
And whom he sold his taxi
Now he is driving taxi for
those people
After dad's death our uncle
occupied our property
Now in which house we are living he
also wanted to occupy that house
If we will win this case
then we will keep our house
and we will be attached with
our dad's memories as well
Tomorrow's judgenment must be
in our favour
Don't worry!
We will must win
But you are telling this thing
since 3 years
I can give you guarantee
Now I have prepared the case
that your opponent won'tjust
give you the house but
they will give us compensation for
mental harrasement
Really?
Yes!
Judge is gonna be impressed with
my arguments
that he will say before judgement
All the Arguments of Abbas Ali's lawyer
and his given papers clearly tells
that this property doesn't
belongs to Abbas Ali
Now if he wants...
So he can file a case of Mental
Harrasement against Abbas Ali.
Where are you running?
Come here!
I am a lawyer
You are the last nail of grave
We will go to Supreme Court
Now you will go up
You have crossed the limits...
You have beaten your own lawyer
at government office
Thanks to Sania that he called me
and I have got bail for you
Otherwise! You didn't think about your
sister before doing it all
I have thought about Sania
that's why I have just beaten up
that bastard
Otherwise I would have kill him with
that Judge's hammer
I agreed that it all went wrong
with us
But it doesn't mean that you will
start kill everyone
What else I should do?
We have left this house
Junaid Bhai is refusing me to
give his taxi
he is saying that I am a criminal
In that case I won't lose my temper
then what else. Enough!
Sania!
Get some tea for him
Now I understand that...
Why Taj Mahal is a wonder
What?
Without getting loan from the bank
Shah Jehan has build up Taj Mahal
Wonder!
A middle class man have so many
basic wishes
6 figure salary
5 working days
4 wheeler car
2 bedroom flat
two kids and...
a life partner
But the reality is that...
In this world man's heavy burden
is his empty pockets...
Appreciation of good days comes
after bad days...
Thanks to confirm this thing that...
I am running on my bad days
It's good to understand your situation
But it's a bad thing to curse
on your situations...
You and Sania come with me
to my village
Me and your dad wasn't friends
for the namesake
we were like brothers...
Now you will do like I will say
If you'll stay here then you'll cursse
your luck to see those faces
And I will try
where I works you will get a
nice job there
Rananpur is such a wonderfull place
No politics is there
Nor crowd like city
Peace is all over the village
I have been working for Raghuwanshi
family from 30 years
Earlier with his father
and now I am working with his
son PrithviRaj...
PrithviRaj is such an amazing man
He have only two habits
First!
His second is speaking better english
than British people
More than English
He loves his sister Radhika
Right now Radhika is studying
in Dehli
whenever the matter comes for
Rananpur's village progress
PrithviRaj stands first of all...
This year in village
He is also starting the power plant
project in village
But his cousin Vikrant comes to
interfere in power plant project
To provoke the family enimty
He is against Prithviraj and
this Power Project
PrithviRaj looks such a honest
and decent man
You have decided to put Abbas
job on right place
He hates only one thing
What?
Lie!
How do you feeling?
I am feeling lot of pain
Have some water
Help!
He brought you here
Tell me which monster
turned you in this condition
I did it...
I have beaten him up
You have beaten him up and
you brought him here
He had lot of stains on his body
It was necessary to wash him
And to bringing him up here
was necessary for humanity
But what he has done?
He has done fraud!
He has done a fraud of 99 rupees
in accounts
Only for rupees 99...
It's not a matter of 99
It's a matter of lie
Prithiviraj salutes the truth
but he killed the lier
Next time if you will lie then
don't worry about the results
I will give you the prize
Find another man of his replacement
This Ravi is late again
he is not my son but my problem
He is the proof of my every disease
There must be some reason for late
Only one reason
His third class Aflatton Drama Company
My friend Abbas you have come
I have come to dehli many times
but you are welcome first time
in our village
Actually we came here to meet you
without changing our costumes
But you guys are late
I am standing here since long
because of you
Are you the coin of Sholay that you
have to stand since long
You could sit on the bench
Shame on you!
Show some manners of the act
of this Lord Raam
You are calling your dad from
his name
It depends on the father
Shastri!
Pick up the bags
Your drama company is really Aflatoon
I was saying now you have come here
So why don't you make over our
drama company's stage
Where else we will find a better
Art Director like you
At lease some intelligent came
to Joker Party
Tell me the theme of your new play
I will have to decide the things
for your play
People makes movies to inspire
from the play
but first time
I have made this play to inspire
with movies
What's the name of your play?
What else we can expect people
like you
You are good for nothing
We can't rehearse our play
because of him
One minute!
You are Shastri and he is Ravi
If not here then where do you
rehearse for your play
My dad used to say that human should
respect his moustache and his principles
Who doesn't have moustache he
doesn't have heart
By the way where is your dad?
He died four years ago
Good!
What an acting?
Your play is super hit
Abbas! I want you to pray the God
like my first act has come
Alibaba and 15 thieves
same as that this act should
be successful
15 thieves?
Alibaba had 40 thieves
It's a play for village
We have problem for budget
that's why Alibaba and 15 thieves
I have made the list of all things
You take Sania to Pichku's shop
and take credit
Actually we have a budget problem
Get down!
You will fall down
What are you doing up there?
Get down!
You will fall down!
Why temple is closed?
Abbas! This temple is at the boudary
of Ranantpur and Kherwara
See the result of two villages fight
Temple door is locked from many years
What are you doing?
Are you gone mad?
If you will enter the temple then
there will be a chaos
What you have done?
You have broken the temple's lock
Kid would sink down...
But!
Let's go from here
Who are you?
You are out of my mind
Where smoke doesn't appear...
Your dish get hot over there...
You don't interefere!
We already had many arguments
on this issue
You are shooting in the day
We have already warned you
You could be arrested for your act
But this guy has broken temple's lock
This guy has broken the temple's lock
to save this kid
I think that's the God wish
Now it will be against the religion
to lock down this temple
So what do you mean?
If temple is open so it will
remain open
I will take the permission
from Collector
If anybody will go against
this decision
then he would be arrested
I don't accept this decision...
S. P!
This temple will remain open
From today it's my responsibility
and if whoever will interfere
I will make him remember his
mom's milk
I have never seen you before...
He is my friend's son
He came from Dehli!
Name?
Abhishek Bachchan
His name is Abhishek Bachchan
What else I would say
Abbas Ali!
If villagers would know that Abbas
Ali has broken the temple's lock
then we all will be disappeared
But Abhishek Bachchan!
If Prithviraj will know this...
Come with me
He is the guy whom you wanted
to give job
Yes!
But you didn't tell me some
other name...
Who kept your name?
His dad...
But why Abhishek Bachchan?
Why not Sachin Tendulkar
Because when he born he was
taller than Tendulkar
I am joking
Why are you shying Abhishek?
Tell him how did you
get this name
My dad and mom was the huge
fan of Amitabh Bachchan...
So!
So mom and dad met in cinema
they both were gone to watch Deewar
They saw each other in interval
and they felt in love
Then?
Why are you shying?
Speak!
Next time...
they went to watch movie together
Chupke Chupke!
Then they took swear of marriage
that day Qasme Waade was released
when they got married then
Suhaag was released
and when mom gave good news
to my dad
then Parwarish was released
and when I was released
I mean when I was born
then Muqaddar Ka Siqandar was released
that's why my dad kept my name
Abhishek Bachchan
Thank God your family was not
the fan of Amjad Khan
Otherwise your name would be
Gabbar Singh
What is your Qualification?
Jamia Islamia University
Pandit Nehru College opposite
to that University
I have passed B. A from there
A. B has passed B.A.
He read 2 words and both wrong,
B.A.
Makhan!
Yes!
Give him the job of Superman
He is saying Supervisor
Salary 30,000
30,000!
35,000!
Not more!
Without any experience you gave
me a job
Our thirty years special appearance
You came here for his proposal
Truth is that...
He wants to say that I will
never let you down
Because my dad used to say...
I can't count your body parts
Don't look relationship's benefits but
their meanings
And remember one thing
If you will do it again
then I will kill you
Now do you understand why I
didn't let you go anywhere
They are our kins but they are
thirsty for our blood
If he have so many problems here
then why don't we shift
from Ranantpur
Ranantpur's every villager is more
than my relatives
They have some hopes with me
and I have learned only one thing
Rather break your relationship
but never break anyone's trust
Next time if you want to
go somewhere
then inform me first
Seve the food!
We are leaving!
Listen!
Today you have prooved
that you are notjust honest
but you are brave too...
Come!
Have food with me
No!
Today I am fasting
From today I have decided that
I will fasting
Why fasting on wednesday?
Day doesn't matter for mom
I am fasting specially
for my mom
One minute!
You said that only your sister
lives with you
Now where did your mom
came from?
Only you can have mom I jumped
out from the egg
Actually! I had only sister at home
but mom also came yesterday
Where did your mom came from?
Kashi!
That's why...
that's why I have decided that mom
wouldn't be well
I will fasting everyday
I will also fasting for your mom
What are you saying?
You will do so much for mom...
It's not enough
Tomorrow I will come
to your house
No!
Yes! Why?
Why not?
But why?
I will open my fast with your mom
Mom and Sister will be very happy
I will be also happy
Actually! Boss has seen the mom
but he haven't seen mom's love,
Makhan!
I didn't said listen!
I think your ears are not well...
How he will meet your mom?
If mom will exist then
he will meet
Where is your mom?
How would you bring the mom?
I think dad will passed away
for mom
We have fake mom in our play
Abbas!
Fake mom!
But how we will get fake mom?
We made Vidhya Sagar to play
girl's role
He will looks like mom
But I will never looks like his son
I have mom!
You have started again!
Stop narrating dialogues,
I am telling the truth
I have mom!
Look over there!
Your upcoming mom!
She!
Yes!
I need mom!
If she will start dancing in
front of Prithvi then...
She is an artist
And artists are like water
We will write down her dialogues
from Vidhya Sagar
It's good to being orphan,
Let's go! No!
Think about it!
4 minutes mom
orjob of 35,000
Sister's responsibility or unemployment
Mom's scarf or Prithivi's punch!
Tell me what do you want?
I have come to make you mom
What?
You too?
Ravi was saying that you are
expert in this thing
Don't refuse us...
You are famous in this job
We have many expectations
from you
You have some mis-understanding
You have to act to being his mom
in front of his boss
She thinks that we are lusty men
Listen the problem!
Your story's emotion is right
but it's wrong to make me mom
Your Boss will catch me
in 2 minutes
No!
He is not so lusty
Not like this catching...
He will catch our lie
And he will know that I
am not a mom
Because I don't look like
mom's age
Make me your lover
Call me friend,
Younger sister is also fine but
Now my second act is starting
I am leaving
This old woman will die
in 2 days
She have my curse
But that monster will come
in 2 hours
What will we do?
Find a mom!
Not less than any challenge
Isn't it?
What are you thinking Abbas?
Prithvi came here to break his
fast with us
But how suddenly he is gone
She is a ghost!
Not ghost!
She is Abhishek's sister Sania
She was Ameksha
My Ameksha
It will take time...
Eid's prayer will be over
in 5 minutes
Take your time
We are not in hurry!
You have done well to meet
Amirgarh's Collector
When Power Plant will start
in Ranantpur
then that you must see the
Vikrant's face
His face power will down
He is shooting in Amirgarh!
Not that one!
Our Abhishek from Ranantpur
Look over there!
Eid's sweet dish is really different
Have some!
Prithvi is here!
I have already told you rather
break the relationship
but don't break anyone's trust
I saw you in Amirgarh
You were hugging with everyone and
celebrating Eid
What's your reality?
Answer me!
You saw me in Amirgarh,
Now you need an answer
You wil give the answer
How would you give the answer in fact
you can't answer in your examination
I have an answer
Who you have seen that was me
but I wasn't that person
You were,
You were not!
That was my twin brother Abbas
Where are you going?
He is tolerating twin brothers
torture from the beginning
Since childhood
You tell him!
You know everything,
She is his sister
He stole mango from the tree
and he got beaten up
Dog came and bite him
and he got injections
He is my carbon copy
there is only the difference
of moustache
You didn't notice
I have moustache,
But he doesn't have
You must have seen him
Except moustache they
both are same
Same as that Abbas Ali
and Abhishek Bachchan
You suspected on my loyality
You are my kid
One minute!
How Abbas could be the brother
of Abbas Ali
He know the reality now what
will we tell him
You are right
that what will we say and how
we will say
that Abbas is not your twin brother
but he also your illegal brother
And what are you looking at?
You are also involved in this truth
Tell him the story
Which story?
Tell him the story of illegal Abbas
His dad got a contract
to break the stones at side...
A girl named Jameela used to pick
up the bricks there...
Dad broke the stones
and Jameela picked up the bricks
And then his dad gone mad
And he is gone behind the stones
with her
Then what happened?
Then after nine month in one night
Day or Night?
Both!
At one place Abhishek born in day
and same night Abbas born at
another place
Where is Abbas mom?
She is dead!
That's why Abbas lived with us
Abhishek took his responsibility
along with me
What he does?
Nothing!
He is a dancer
He is a classical dancer
Then send him to me
He is not good for you
You are type of wrestler man
and he is that...
Then he is really good for me,
What?
You won't understand
Send him to me,
I will put him on job
Why you are doing so much for me
I will have to remove your burden
We don't have relationship of
Boss and Servant
your mom is my mom
Your brother is my brother
Your sister is...
Boss!
Why did you get Abbas on job?
You often meet these kind of
people in your life
What do you mean?
Out of the blue...
He is good for nothing
But he is good for me
I mean...
He will teach dance to Radhika
then my sister will be secured
You have done greatjob
If T-Series people would be there
then they would must make it's
remix album
then one day you would be famous in
Ranantpur like me
Your dad?
Who?
Shastri get me on job
at Prithvi's place
He is not a wrestler but call him
Wild Buffalo
Let it be...
Why should I let it be?
He carries 100 kg weight but he doesn't
have intelligence of 10 grams
He would have understood that I am
Abhishek and Abbas Ali
Why you are speaking alot?
What happened to you?
You guys acts really well
I have come to tell you that stop
your brother to teach me
but now I will go and stop
my brother
I will stop him to trust fraud people
like you
He is so naive
So everyone wants to take
advantage of him
I am going to tell him the truth
You can tell your brother everything
But before thatjust once...
Listen once that why did we lied
to him
A middle man's life doesn't accompalish
to live with it
His life accompalished to fullfill his
family needs
Abbas had few dreams for me
But our family house has been
snatched from us
Abbas lost his job
Shastri Uncle brought us Ranantpur
and Abbas has broken the temple's lock
to save the kid's life
and to handle the situation I told his
name Abhishek Bachchan
And after that...
when Prithvi gave him a nice job
then our mistake didn't felt
offense to us
Mistakes shouldn't be committed
but it happens
You are right
If you want to tell Prithvi everything
so tell him
You know my brother
If he will know the truth
then he will kill all of you
That's why we didn't think about to
tell him the truth
Do it as you like
Come from tomorrow to teach
me dance
Ghost is lie
She is Abhishek's sister Sania
Thank God you have come
Will you rehearse with me
for a while
I have no experience of play
Your eyes are enough
You have to speak these four lines
I don't know how to speak dialogues
I know how to say listen,
Excellent!
Now you have to look at me and speak
I have to tell you something
Are you expressing the love or
starting the war
Say it from the heart
What is this nonsense?
It means I am your son
you grown up first,
Who are you?
And who you want to meet?
You didn't recognize Prithvi Raj
May I know you?
You better know that...
But I have known you very well
You are widow there,
and here you are dancing
You must have met my twin
sister Madhumati
That wasn't me
I also have two twin nephews,
Abhishek and Abbas
We sisters had twin moms
Is this a family?
Or the factory of making twin kids
He looks like rascal from his face
But you too...
What?
Are also amazing
You can't find out the difference
between Madhumati and Zohra
Please forgive me, I had
mis-understanding to see the poster
Give my greetings to my sister
Tell her that Zohra missed her alot
One minute!
How Zohra could be the sister
of Madhumati
I don't feel good to hear the same
story of stone and brick from woman
Abbas must be like her.
Dancer!
Don't you think?
That Zohra's message must be forward
to Madhumati right now,
to his house
They must be sleeping
Sania must be awake
Prithvi's hand was reached here
You were just lucky
In fact I was also lucky
My leg hair were exposed I thought
we all will be exposed
Who is there?
He is back
Get your moustache
I have told you
You can lose your respect to visit
someone's house over and over again
We have come to meet your mom
We have to talk to her
She is taking bath in bathroom
Let's go!
Boss!
Mom's message!
And how much time she will
take to bath
Sania is also here
to give us coffee
Sania!
Can we come in?
Liers must get punishment in climax
Where is our Abhishek?
He is gone to temple
One day you all wil be caught
doing this drama
Boss has trusted you alot
and you all are doing fake acting
I know everything about their play
Aflatoon Drama Company is doing it's
play with hardworking
Sania too...
I have invested my money on right place
Nobody is cheating on me
It's too late.
We are leaving
Now the entire tank would be empty
We can have another cup of coffee
Sania!
Would you give us a cup of coffee?
Why are you crying?
Coffee is over in house
What we will offer you?
If coffee is over then give
us tea
He is asking tea
Give him tea and give me poison
What will we do now?
Sania!
Who is there?
Not tea!
But we have mom
One minute!
Right now Shastri took bath
from which bathroom
how could mom came out from
the same bathroom
When twin brothers could be at home
so we couldn't have twin bathrooms
my sister Zohra called me on phone
You looks rascal from your face
What?
And you too, What?
Are amazing man
You heard him
I am very sorry!
Not at all
I am leaving
How come you are here?
And your sister Zohra?
I will tell you everything
No problem!
It will be done
We will have to start the power plant
boundary 150 yards away from here
If I would get this land's papers and
print so it would be better
Give him everything he want
And that greenary in that area...
It's not greenary
It's a great view
Two bodies are burning in love
Look! Your Ranantpur is
getting progress
I had warned you
don't step out from Ranantpur
But you were escaping from Rananpur
and for who?
For that coward who left you alone
Why are you quite?
Am I wrong?
You are right
True man is that
who doesn't escape from the problems
but to face them
Am I right?
Yes!
Who shouldn't care for his life but
he put his life in danger for relatives
Am I right?
Yes!
You should have find a life partner
who should protect you everytime
like I did
Am I right?
Yes!
Abhishek!
You are absolutely right!
Do you like Radhika?
Do I like Radhika?
Amazing!
You like Radhika.
Do you like Abhishek?
Yes!
You have opened my eyes
True man is that
who doesn't escape from the problems
but to face them
who shouldn't care for his life but
he put his life in danger for relatives
I am ready to marry you,
I can't marry with her
Why?
I have a private problem
Nowadays there are so many
medicines in market
and clinics are opened everywhere,
Prithvi!
I can't get married because
until my sister can't get married how
could I get married
You also have a virgin sister
Until she don't get married how
could you get married
Actually today I have come for
the proposal
But...
Abhishek!
When elders are talking so you
shouldn't interfere
What do you think about marriage?
I never think about it
I can understand!
You didn't get time to grown up
your kids and prayers...
to think about my and
Sania's marriage
If I have your permission...
Permission?
Why permission from this Madhumati
Even I jump down to marry with
an honest man like you
for the marriage arrangements
Shut up!
You didn't hear that
You get marry with Sania as
soon as possible
Fix the marriage date as
Now not one...
Two brothers will be busy for
thier sister's wedding
What did you need to accept
this proposal?
Does anyone can refuse that
kind of proposal
When Prithvi will know
that he is not marrying with Sania
Bachchan but with Sania Ali
He will kill all of us...
First time you spoke the truth
Prithvi will kill all of us
Everyone is dead!
Do one thing!
Get moustache to Sania
and tell that Prithvi who you have
seen that's not Sania
but her sister Dhania
and you change your looks and tell
I am not Ravi but Govinda
I will also tell that I am not Shastri
but I am a British Jailor
How much you will eat?
Save something for the coutry
If you will go to your village then
they will say someone else is coming
I can't marry with you
I have a personal reason to
shouldn't marry with you
I also had a personal reason
to marry you
She...
I was also shocked when
I saw you first time
She is Abhiksha
I loved her alot
Four years ago God snatched her from
me in an accident
Now she is not here
but I have her picture
Radhika doesn't know about her
After Abhiksha's death
I didn't have wish in my life
I was busy for Ranantpur's progress
Then I saw you...
so I felt...
that my Abhiskha is back
I was forgotten
that you are not Abhiksha!
But you are Sania Bachchan
Forgive me!
I brought the proposal without
your wish
But I am happy
because my sister is getting
married in your house
Come tomorrow morning
Why are you standing here?
We made a big mistake
We are cheating that person
who helped us on every step
He is such an honest
and naive person
When he will know that...
Abbas and Abhishek are not two
but he is the same person then
You have said
if I will keep doing it
then nor Allah will mind it nor
Bhagwan
but what we are doing with
that person
After that every God of every religion
will mind
Are you mad?
Yes!
With happiness
Just once speak the famous question
of Gabbar Singh
How many were they?
Not two but one
What do you mean?
I mean they are not two
but he is one...
Save my boss
It's all happening because of you
Now you save my boss
Me?
Yes!
Have you seen it's deepness
As much I will step as long
I have chances to die
Whatever is happening with
Prithvi it's just
happening because of your lie
From our lie to my lie
I don't know anything
If you won't save him so I will
never see your face again
I am the sister of Prithvi Raj
So?
If you won't save him so I will
never see your face again
I will also support my elders
I won't also see your face again
I will never see your face again
and me too
What do you think?
That you will say and I will go
What do you think about me
I am that man who don't feel pain
Save me!
How did you came here?
I have put my life on risk and
come to save you
I forgive you,
What?
You said it to me
that I forgive you
You have ruined that
cricketer's name
Sania you are my sister and
Radhika I am your love
but still you both are on his side
Today you listen to me
If you would break the mosque's lock
then you would tell your name
Prithvi Raj
You know what would you say
My name is Pervez Musharraf,
that's what you would said
I want to fast for your mom,
So go on
Why did you need to come home?
Even kids took 9 month to born
I born 3 moms in single day
You kept me on job
but no!
You also kept my brother on job
I loved your sister
but you also loved my sister
May I tell you one thing
from the bottom of my heart
I never did fraud with my work
I thought if I will keep working
with honesty
then nor Allah will mind
nor Bhagwan
but if you still thinks that
I am wrong
I...
I will jump down from here
Don't try to stop me
Don't hold my hand
Don't leave my hand
I forgive you
I will tell you my feelings today
I will never lie but you also promise
that you will never speak
english again
now pull me up!