This is lndia...
the land that glistens, shines...
the land bedecked
with the glitter of dreams...
beckoning you...
if you nurse a hunger,
she says, here...
you'll find
what satisfies it. Come...
rub your shoulders
till they're blue...
with fame, wealth, power, glory...
and your life becomes...
a sunlit dream
you never want to wake out of
Yes, this is lndia...a dream...
that Bunty and Babli dreamt
every night of their lives
And this is the lndia they live in...
an lndia that says...
your dreams should end
where your arms do...
and you should feel only
as much hunger as you can satisfy...
step forward....
but only when
you're in step with the others...
float to the top but not
at the cost of anyone else
love, compassion,
honesty, respect...
are what matter most...
this too is lndia...
the lndia Bunty and Babli grew up in
but didn't feel like they belonged to
This world we live in
has two kinds of people
One, the kind that does
just one thing all their lives and...
the kind that does...
just about everything in one life
l didn't say that, they did and they
didn't just say it, they lived it
And how ! No one ever lived life...
like they lived theirs and perhaps...
no one ever will
So much excitement...
so much adventure, so many joys...
all in one single lifetime...
no one could have imagined it possible,
not even them. Or then again...
maybe they could have
Text: By RahelSurshi
Small town cocoons
These dull afternoons...
l want to pack them up
and go away... away...
The rains come slow
The river lies low...
The sea will carry me away
Going away, l'm going away
Oh Ram Chand re...
Dhadak'dhadak Dhadak'dhadak
Watch the smoke billow
Hear the whistle blow
Dhadak'dhadak Dhadak'dhadak
Call me, oh, watch me go...
Stand aside, make way for me
Those clouds are mine to hold
Burnt in black on a white sheet sky
l'll write my name, big and bold
On the street
that curves around the moon...
At the bend is where l'll stay
On the street that curves around
the moon l'll stay far, far away
Going away, l'm going away
Oh Ram Chand re...
Dhin'tinak'dhin Dhin'dhin'ta
Small town cocoons
These dull afternoons
l want to pack them up
and go away... away...
Small town cocoons
These dull afternoons...
l want to pack them up
and go away... away...
The rains come slow
The river lies low...
The sea will carry me away
Going away, l'm going away
Oh Ram Chand re...
Dhadak'dhadak Dhadak'dhadak
Hear the whistle blow
Watch the smoke billow
Dhadak'dhadak Dhadak'dhadak
Call me, oh, watch me go...
When l ride l carry in my hair...
The cool whispers of the wind
Ride across the earth, the sky
Leave the world behind, unhinged
My forehead adorned, my jewel, the moon
l can't walk unnoticed amidst the stars
My forehead shorn of all but the moon
l can't live unnoticed up here with stars
Going away, l'm going away
Oh Ram Chand re...
Call me, oh, watch me go...
watch me go...
lt's not going to come.
- lt will
lt won't.- lt will
Boy, go down to the tap
and have your bath
Or you'll be standing at
the end of a very long line
No dearth of people
wanting to get into a line
What do you mean?
- What l mean Ma is...
this world has two kinds of people,
one, those who line up before taps...
and two, those who make themselves taps
so they won't need to stand in any line
l happen to belong to the latter.
- You don't belong anywhere
You've already spent
forty rupees on this gibberish
How much more will you blow up?
- Ma, how many times do l tell you...
l'm not spending anything.
This is an investment
For fifty bucks, this shower is
up and running... then l'll fix it...
to the community tap and everyone's
willing to part with fifty paise...
to bathe in a shower.lf five people
use it everyday, that's 2.50
ln twenty days, fifty bucks are back
That's 2.50 in profits
everyday from each shower
Stop. You're making my head spin
The problem with this Fursatganj,
talking sense sends heads spinning
Anyway, do you remember
my chit fund idea ?
A finance company in Lucknow...
- l don't want to know anything !
lf you don't stop now
you'll surely go to jail some day
There... l told you it'll come
Of course it will. Why won't it ?
How else will he drown his future ?
Why... oh today was your interview
for the railway job ! You didn't go ?
l went ! Pandey'ji
called to say that...
before l recommend my son
for another interview...
l should at least make sure that he
drags himself there on his own two legs
l've lain my thirty five years
in the service on the line...
and made him agree for
another chance tomorrow
Thank God he agreed
How does that matter?
l need to agree too
Rakesh, we're trying to be serious here
l told him l don't want to be
a ticket collector
So what do you want to be ?
The maker of failed schemes, for life ?
All of Fursatganj thinks
you're a deluded Don Quixote
You want them to coin new
euphemisms for you ? Everyone...
Fursatganj is packed with asses.
And all asses can do is...
chew the cud and bear the burden.
l wasn't born to do either
Oh you'll become a Birla-Tata-Ambani?
- Why can't l be ?
They didn't fall out of the sky.
They too were born here on this earth
At least they were born here. You belong
to a different planet altogether!
Dad, don't get me started again.
l've made up my mind
l'm not going to waste my entire life
trapped in a job
Look here
l've spent thirty five years in this job
You think my life's been a total waste ?
After a lifetime of service,
does the government even bother...
about your opinion?
After thirty five years of...
shuttling up and down that same
train route, does even one passenger...
from all those thousand trips remember
what you look like in your shabby coat ?
When you die, will anybody except
Ma and l, shed a single tear ?
Will the railways take a day off ?
Dad your life means nothing. There's
no respect, no fun, no meaning
When l walk wearing this shabby coat,
that seems to embarrass you so much...
people stop in their tracks
to pay me their respects
Shopkeepers are up on their feet
to attend to Mr Ticket Collector
Why?
Because my poor black cotton coat...
is untainted by ill-gotten gain...
it is the mark of my esteem
Rakesh...
the interview is at
9 o'clock tomorrow morning
Get there in time.
Or get lost
Find a meaning for your life
wherever you want, however you want to
Because we can't live up
to your high expectations...
we're sorry
There's something about you baby
You too
You're not half bad either
Go easy on the lipstick...
it shouldn't look too tacky.
And one thing you ought to know
A ragged skirt doesn't make you sexy
lt's what's in your eyes... like in mine
Dear God...
my daughter has gone insane!
- lf worshipping my beauty...
is tantamount to being insane,
then l plead insanity
lf craving for fame is insane
lf the desire to renounce this
pigeon-hole Pankinagar...
for the great wide marvellous
world outside is insane...
then l plead complete insanity
And you are driving me nuts.
Take off that shirt
l'm sorry, l don't believe
beauty needs cheap exposure
One tight slap
and all your beliefs will change
You've ruined all his best shirts
Ruined ? These shirts will fetch
millions. There'll be grand auctions
Supermodel Vimmi's shirts ! The ones
she wore when she dreamt of success
Ladies and gents, do l hear
a hundred thousand... One...Two... Three !
Jassi, where's my shirt ?
Right here...
What's she up to now?
- She's just fooling around...
Fooling around...?
Go on, enjoy yourself...
till the time you can
What are you trying to do?
- Trying to be coy about my marriage
But doesn't seem to be
coming too naturally
Your father isn't joking.
You won't find a man like Surinder...
even if you turn Kanpur and Lucknow
inside out. Count your blessings...
a head clerk has fallen into your lap
that too in a place like Pankinagar
Papa'ji, l think...
l'll run away from home
Listen to her ! l kept telling you
we shouldn't allow cable tv in her room
All day-and-nights she's whispering
to those naked witches on her walls
And now she even wants to run away.
- No harm in that, no ?
You go ahead, run away
But see, it's 1 1 o'clock.
Eat lunch before running
What are you saying?
- l don't want a weight on my mind...
my daughter running away
on an empty stomach ?
l'm warning you, l'll really run away
if you even think of marrying me off...
to that... that ten out of ten!
- Ten out of ten ?
That ass always got ten out of ten in
every godforsaken subject... what a nerd
Who wouldn't want to marry such a man?
- Then why don't you ? Spare me
Now get out of that outfit
and help your mother with the cooking
l've called them to lunch tomorrow
l want things to be finalised
before the evening tea hits the table
Enough. Don't make me hurt you
Why are you taking them off?
- You don't know why ?
lt's time you realised that you can't
live like you want to anymore
You'll have to adjust to
your new family's ways
You'll eat, drink, walk, sleep
the way they want you to
Look, l'm your mother.
All l want is to see you happy
Forget all of this
You're leaving this for a new world.
- lt feels like l'm leaving the world
The more you think about it
the more you'll hurt
Just do as l say.
You'll learn to be happy
Mummy, if l request Papa'ji not to
marry me off just yet, will he listen ?
The facial cream is on the washbasin.
Don't forget to apply it
Tea... piping hot tea...
A little extra milk
never killed a cow.- Sir ?
l said, two extra teaspoonfuls of milk
never killed the calf's mother. Pour
There's more milk than water in it, sir.
- More milk, l said
Hey give back my glass
Catch it if you can
Your name sir?
- l'm what you'd call Raj Kapoor Tiwari
Where's your seat here, show me...
l'm not on your list...the other one.
l talked to the ticket checker, paid him
Oh, so you've paid him a bribe
No, no...- Give me your address
Why do you need my address ?
Do you see that berth number ?
Take a look.- Number seven
Coach FC1 , berth number 7
Always reserved for...
the Fursatganj staff going to Lucknow.
l've been using this berth for 3 years
The entire railway division knows that.
How could anyone have given it to you ?
Could you tug that chain for me please ?
Trust Finance & Chit Fund Company
Loans, chit funds for every need
You think you're the first person
to come up with this idea ?
We spend eight hours a day in offices
like this, chewing tobacco, eh ?
200 out of every 1 00 finance companies
dream of a scheme like this...
but trip over their own two feet...
trying to find 500 investors
to chip in a thousand rupees each
The answer to my next question
is on your face but...
l'll ask you anyway... Mister, where
are your 500 investors ?
What if l tell you l have them ?
Where...?
Here
l've slogged it out for a whole year, sir
l've gotten together 500 investors from
my town and the neighbouring ones...
willing to put up a thousand rupees
each in any good finance company
Where are you from?
Fursatganj
Fursatganj ! Where l was once
Not one finance company...
will waste five minutes over
a list like this one
Talk of investments
Small town-guys have a habit of
dreaming big. No ban on dreaming
lndulge yourself
But next time,
come up with a scheme that...
a thousand others haven't thought up
before you. Get it ? Now excuse me
Where are you going, lady?
- To enter the contest
You can't go in.
- lf l can't go inside...
how do l take part in the competition?
Let me in. l've come really far
l said, you can't go in.
- l say, l have to enter
Can l help you ?
- Yes, myself Vimmi Saluja...
l've come to enter the contest.
- You're too late
What...?
- The entries closed two days ago
You mean the contest's begun?
- No, not yet
Oh, that's a relief.
- l said, entries have closed
But the contest hasn't begun!
- l said ''the-entries-have-closed''
So open up for two minutes,
l'll quickly squeeze in !
You're from some village?
Miss Quickly-squeeze-in !
This is no village fair
to squeeze-in-slip-out when-you-wish
This is the Miss lndia contest,
but what would you know ?
Oh c'mon Pammi, forget it
One minute... would l know what ?
- The desire and the ability...
to become Miss lndia are two very
different things. So go home...
and start a beauty parlour.
- Why not beauty-parlour yourself ?
Excuse me ?
Ever watched your figure ?
At least ten kilos overweight...
with black-dyed hair and
desperately-curving-lipline...
with miles-thick lipstick. You know all
about make-up. Beauty parlour's for you
What a bitch
Listen...
Yes?
- Please come with me to the toilet
lt's right at the end of the platform
and it's really dark
Come
Weren't you on the
Jhansi Mail this morning ?
Returning? Here on business?
- Yes l came for the Miss lndia contest
So how was it ?
Good... very good
l got through the first round
Good... good... Miss lndia !
And you ? Here on business too?
- Oh no... no...
Work is something
l don't really believe in
l came here for a meeting
There's a finance company here,
they want to buy my scheme
l had to come personally you see,
it's a matter of millions
So, you're becoming
a model soon?- l guess so
You'll become famous.
- Yes... l guess so
People will buzz around you
like bees around honey
Yes... l guess they will
Why are you crying ?
l didn't mean to insult you
No, don't take me otherwise
l belong to a decent family,
l wouldn't dream of it
Calm down, everyone's watching
Poor thing... she's in grieving
l was only sympathising...
Everything's fine
You'll be the first girl to cry after
making it to the Miss lndia contest
l didn't make it anywhere
Aren't you ashamed of lying ?
Actually, l lied too...
the manager of the finance company
didn't quite buy my scheme...
l think he doesn't have the drive
Bloody idiot
Foulmouthing... me...?
Escort her to the loo
and then get abused for it ?
l escorted you !
Who do you think you are ?
You mean if you go back now...?
- Wedding bells...
That's too bad. - Very
Then ?
l'll run away.
- You already have
So, what'll you do now?
- What'll you do ?
Whatever l do, l'm not giving up.
And l'm not going back home
Then, where will you go? - Kanpur
Why Kanpur?
- The company has a head office there
l'll show my scheme to senior officers,
l'm sure they'll get it
Why don't you come
along to Kanpur? - Who me...?
Miss lndia contests are held all over.
Maybe they'll allow you to enter there
You got to find a way into the contest,
else what use was running away ?
So long, l guess the next time
l see you it'll be on TV
l guess so. Thank you.
And good luck for your big meeting
Thanks but that was superfluous. l only
need to make a presentation and...
voila ! l'll have 1 00 finance companies
running rings around me
See you
Unbelievable. Got to admit...
very few people have brains as sharp
l say, just once in a whole year,
let me meet just one such person
But two in a single day, unbelievable!
Would you believe...
just half an hour ago, another man
came to me with an identical scheme
Who?
- Manager of our Lucknow branch...
Mr Qureishi ! lmagine... a rare gem
lay buried in my own backyard
He got a 1 0,000 bonus on the spot !
He even had a list of 500 investors
Unbelievable ! What a man !
- Where's he staying ?
Landmark Hotel.
- ln Landmark ! And why not ?
The 1 0,000 bonus ! Give me as much
l'll go to live in a five star too
Next?- Vimmi Saluja
Address?
- 2/5 Ballygunj, Pankinagar
One minute...
Doesn't Pankinagar fall within
the Lucknow district ?
lt does?
- Yes, Lucknow district
You didn't fill up the form in Lucknow?
- What difference, here or there ?
l was passing through Kanpur
so l thought l'll get it over with
Very good
Please step outside
Sir'ji, just a matter of an address...
- Go away ! Rules are rules
Please...- Get lost
Oversmartness
Look, l can't bend the rules
But if you wish...
l can forget rules for a while
Yes sir!
- But nothing comes for free
Sir, l'll do whatever you wish !
Very good!
Once you're Miss lndia...
you'll have all the wealth,
all the fame your heart ever desired
But l? l'm still stuck to the same
... chair and table
Oh sure...
l have nothing right now...
but l promise, when l'm Miss lndia...
l'll pay you...
everything you'll ever want
You're mistaken. You have everything
l'll ever want... right now
l won't force you. Registration closes
in five minutes. Think it over
You'll find me at the same table
What's your name?- Jajjan
You make tea?
- No, l serve tea
This world we live in boy,
has two kinds of people
One, those who serve tea.
And those to whom tea is served
The faster you become one of the latter,
the better the life that you'll live
Has somebody hurt you ?
Two teas and chips
Two?
Why ? Problem ?
- No. But who's the second cup for?
lf l drink two cups,
will it start a war?
God, this world we live in...!
Get a hold on this kid
lt's no use. - What ?
No use being earnest, unwitting fools
getting shoved in stinking little towns
Then...?- Bombay...
the only city in all of lndia where
a man is recognised for his worth...
the only place where you can start from
the pavement and end up in palaces...
where ambition isn't pushed around,
but cheered, egging you on
How're you so sure?
- How...
if Dhirubhai Ambani, Ratan Tata, Birla
had been in Lucknow-Kanpur...
they'd be swatting flies in
Ambani General Stores, Tata Flour Mills
And Birla Tobacco Stall. Bombay...
gave them the recognition they deserved
Look where it got them...
So you want to go Bombay ?
You can come along too.
What'll you do here ?
All the top models are in Bombay. Damn
this narrow-minded small-town mob
lt's the place for Miss lndia, no?- Yes
A ticket to Bombay,
how much would it cost ?
Not that l have that kind of cash
l got the cash, don't worry.
- What...?
We've seen where truth has landed us.
Now let's say what they want to hear
And what's that...?
- Oi Jajjan, where's Landmark Hotel ?
One whiskey...
- Which one sir ?
lmported. How much for a Black Label?
- Four hundred, sir
For a bottle ?- No. 30 ml
Small peg
l'll try an lndian whiskey for a change.
And don't forget the peanuts
Some pretty suave people
you got walking into this Gazal Bar
One Black Label
Sir
Sir ! You here ?
Fursatganj ! All of Lucknow seems to be
pouring into Kanpur today
Slick ! What are you doing here ?
- You'll be seeing more of me here
What do you mean ?
- My scheme got rocking
Which... the same one ?
- No... it was unworkable
You tipped me off in time.
l could've wasted another good year
This is another scheme.
- Which is this ?
l explained this scheme, they offered me
a two per cent stake in the channel
What channel...?
- A news channel
News channel
Nowadays this news channel business
is taking off like a rocket
ln 3 months, they're giving investors
a 300 per cent return on investment
Cigarette ? - Really ?
How much... is the investment ?
- At least 1 00,000
Won't they take a little less ?
l mean, l could invest too...?
Why don't you have a chat ?
Give me an introduction
This is Mr Qureishi
- Q.Q.Qureishi
Q.Q.Qureishi, a very dear friend.
Whatever l am today is because of him
Mr Qureishi would like to invest
in the channel
How many millions ?
He's not like other investors...
this is just a friendly gesture...
about ten thousand ?- Ten
Ten...?
Fifteen... ?
But you're aware,
it should be at least...
Ok, all right,
now how can l refuse you ?
One request, this remains between us
... let this be our little secret
No, no... !
- Promise
We must be in Delhi by morning
So you take the cash from him...
and fetch us a receipt from my room
ln the meantime, if he has no objections
Mr Qureishi can give me company
Yes ?
Well ?- No... l mean no problem
Ten ?
Fursatganj, don't forget the receipt
Would you like to
dance with me Mr Q.Q.Qureishi ?
You dance really well.- Thank you
Where's the ladies' room ?
- Thank you
The washroom... where is it ?
- Bartender, where's the washroom ?
Run
What d'you think of my acting ?
Better than yours ?
Who conned him to your table ?
- Who made the sucker dance ?
l'd love to see Q.Q.Qureishi dancing
Hey, the cash
Some sample
Your share. - You keep it
lt's your share.- Not a gift
Just bank it for me till Bombay.
l can't manage money
We had fun though, no ?
Lots...
Move it. Sit in the bus
Passengers for Dehradun and Ambala,
your bus is leaving
Name ?- Bunty
And the Mrs ?
Babli
Bunty... Babli... seats 2 1 and 22
Get inside
Bunty... Babli... what the hell...?
- Nothing... move on. 2 1 and 22
What do you mean nothing?
- Sit down, l'll explain
When l was a kid l always blamed
Bunty for all the mischief l did
And we've just stolen money. So...
- But... what the hell is Babli ?
Why, what's wrong ?
l don't have a problem with Bunty
You look like your Bunty !
But Babli... she sounds like a fat slob
Fat or thin, now it's sealed.
- You could've asked me
Ask my wife her name
in front of a bus conductor ?
Who are you calling your wife ?
- l didn't say that, he thought so
And you let it pass ! Now everyone
in this bus thinks l'm Bunty's wife
What are you doing ? Everyone will
think Bunty's wife is a shrew
Stop it !
- You stop it
l'm not talking.- Suits me
Babli, big deal
At least we managed enough
to get us to Bombay
This stash won't last us
a week in Bombay
And...?
And... l think we'll need lots more
if we want to make it in Bombay
Where will we get so much money ?
- The same place we got this from
You mean another... ?
Are you mad ? What are you saying ?
- l'm not saying a thing. Bunty is
And l'm doing what Bunty's saying ?
- Who are you to do ? Babli will
Babli ?
But l am Babli ! - Sure
You are when you are
You aren't when you aren't
Say, what are you now...?
Bunty. You...?
Babli...?
TmG
Babli Bose, Food lnspector.
l'll inspect your kitchen
We hear, the beer is adulterated here.
- Tony, a chilled beer for the sahib
One step, two step, he steps it up
swings it, pumps it, struts his stuff
Meet Bunty
Minute by minute, she turns it up
spins it so you can't get enough
Meet Babli
Spinning like tops,
orchestrating rip-offs...
they'll clean your pockets,
cock a snook and be off
There ain't a legit soul
from who they never stole
When they dig, they dig so deep
you can't get out of that hole
Bunty Saluja, Tourism department.
Unclean rooms. Got to inspect
Unclean ? How many days of inspection ?
- Three
Bunty And Babli
They maybe two...
but they're too much
Tough-2-catch, too fast-2-touch
Consider it your's
Take it away...
fly away, she's yours
What model number is this ?
- Model number can take a hike !
Why isn't your man back yet ?
- What man ?
Man... means husband.
- Husband ! What crap. You bloody fool
Love is wild like pigeon wings
Tantrums trip on diamond rings
Don't you blink
You might see their shadows pass
Tea cups clink. Tea cups crash.
Forgive, forget, they have a fight...
wipe their mouths
and take full flight...
come, come, come on, come on,
one step, two step, swing it Bunty
Bulandshahr is abuzz with
the amusing misadventures...
of this daring duo
who call themselves Bunty and Babli
People seem to be in awe
of their ingenuity and audacity
Would you like a room or a suite ?
No, l don't want just a room
l want the hotel...
we're here to buy this place
l never thought l'd sell this place.
But your strong background...
and this mind blowing offer...
l'd have to be a lunatic to refuse
How long are you here ?
A week maybe...
- Stay here then... as our guests
This hotel's as good as yours.
We'll discuss details over the weekend
No, doesn't look good. We can't stay
before we've signed the dotted line
l won't take no for an answer
Well if you insist... champagne ?
Searched every inch of Mussoorie sir,
l can't find them
What do you mean ? And their stuff ?
- They even stole ours
Damn them
Come away, come away
All our sparkles fly
right across the sky
Then we sight the morning light
Float up high
Witness the magic of Guru'ji
People running after you like this
... it's a heady feeling
What...?
- Makes me feels like l'm an achiever
They walk wrapped in perfume mists
Hold the world in love-locked fists
You won't see them flit about
till they want you to, and when you do...
he slides with a swagger.
- He's Bunty
She glides zig-zagger.
- She's Babli
Their tales are lore...
been told a score times and more
And will be sung forever more
l can't see any tunnel here...
- We've paid a hundred bucks apiece
Where's that Bunty guide ?
Spinning like tops,
orchestrating rip-offs...
they'll clean your pockets,
cock a snook and be off...
there ain't a legit soul
from who they never stole...
and they dig so deep
you can't get out that hole
One step, two step
Swings it, pumps it, struts his stuff
Oye Bunty
She turns it on, spins it
so you can't get enough. Oye Babli
Bunty Aur Babli
Bunty and Babli
They maybe two but they're too much
Tough-2-catch, too fast-2-touch
l'm so hungry l can't think straight
And you will shut up and eat
whatever's available. No tantrums
Makes you cry ?
What's to cry about ?
- None of your business
Look, what l meant was
you can't get pizzas out here
All right, l'll get whatever
you feel like
Tell me what you want
Who...?
- l want my mummy
But...
out here...?
l miss her
You miss her a lot ?
Go on, get it over with
Over ?
Not over ! l'm missing her,
not laying an egg ! Over !
What do you miss ?
When l was little...
Papa'ji would talk about taking us
for a holiday, far away from Pankinagar
But in all my years of waiting,
we never saved up enough for a holiday
You want to send some money home ?
Do you want to call them ?
Come...
No one's saying anything
Then why are you wasting your breath ?
- l don't know why... l think it's Vimmi
Who's this ?
Some nut
Papa'ji
lt's me... Papa'ji
Vimmi, my child...
where did you disappear ?
l'm okay Papa, l'm fine
Vimmi my child, where are you ?
l can't tell Mummy, but l'm fine
Look dear...
No Papa'ji, don't ask me to come back
now... l don't want to come back
But l really love both of you
No, my child, listen to me...
- No Papa'ji. l'm hanging up now
Bye...
l love you both very much
You want to call home too ?
No
Folks at home
must be worried about you too
No one worries about me
What are you doing here ?
Wondering where he's now
... how he's doing
Do you think l was too harsh on him ?
- You were right in whatever you did
Have your tea, it's time to go to work
Enough ? Satisfied ?
lf you manage money like this in Bombay
in no time, you'll be back...
in your punk-whatever-town.
- Pankinagar, you bloody idiot
Wherever, but you're finished.
- What's left to count ?
You've blown it all up.
- l have, have l...?
Expensive dresses, shoploads of
makeup just fell out of the sky ?
They came from the same place as
your watch, designer shirt, jeans...
and... this deodorant that smells like
turnip pickle gone bad
They fell off the sky, they did
Now what ?
l've been thinking...
Let's... do it one more time ?
- No...
we've pooled enough to get us to
Bombay.- Vimmi this world we live in...
has two kinds of people. One...
those who collect enough and those...
who'll never have enough. Myself and
Tata-Birla-Ambanis are the other kind
That's why they're where they are today.
And once we're in Bombay...
we won't get another chance. So...
let's take one last crack. Just once more
You think so ?
l know so. So l say so
Who says so ? You or Bunty ?
- Bunty's always saying so
Today a little of me is with Bunty.
- Oye Rakesh... my sweet bloody idiot
This one.
- No problem
There's just one problem
Just tell me.
- l'm leaving for Mussoorie tonight
Oh, that is a beautiful place
- l know
Tomorrow l have an inauguration.
- Your inauguration ?
Not mine... my hotel's
Oh, l see
Look Mrs...- Miss...
Miss... earliest we can deliver
would be by tomorrow morning
lt's closing time, you see ?
And we can't stay open for one machine
No, no... not one machine.
- Then ?
All.- All...?
But if the mall isn't open...
- No... l'll open up myself... l mean...
l'll open it up myself for you
Lovely
Sixty thousand
You take cash don't you ?
- l take anything you say
Let's shop
Easy brother, easy. The stuff inside
is real precious
Sorry for troubling you so much.
- You can trouble me as much as you wish
Please visit our hotel sometime.
- Sure
Your machines are now yours
Here's the balance amount
Thank you very much
- Mention not
May God send customers like you
my way every day
l pray we come by
shops like yours everyday
l have the same...
We seem to share similar tastes.
- l wish we find more in common
Mehmood ! Let her rip.
- You sound like he's after us already
lf he isn't, then he soon will
Oye Bunty, you gave him a licking ?
300,000 worth of shades
400,000 in watches
700,000 in electronic items
Deal
Time for a Chinese lunch. Come
l can't count any more
The incredible incident at the
renowned Center One Mall in Bareilly...
has confounded the police. Sources say,
the perpetrators of this heist are...
Bunty and Babli whose capers have
already made headlines in many cities
Even as investigations proceed, by now
Bunty and Babli must be far far away
Tomorrow morning ! Bombay.
- That soon ?
Before you've brushed your teeth.
This train gets there like a bullet
Good. We can get to work
the minute we get there
You're hunting for the top models ?
- Like you're catching your Tata-Birlas
Your share
Always splitting cash
at the drop of a hat ? What's with you ?
Let's just get it over with, no ?
So tomorrow...
you get on with your life,
l'll get on with mine
What'll you do without me ?
l mean, on your own... in Bombay ?
Hog the whole bathroom ?
You'll have complete freedom too, no ?
Nobody will be getting on your nerves
Well you didn't bug me that much.
- Really now ?
The way you fought, l would have to be
the meanest man in the world
l can't believe, by tomorrow morning
l'll be in Bombay
All these dreams, all these years...
is everything finally coming true ?
Flap your wings, come on let's fly
Flap your wings, let's taste the sky
TmG
Balle-Balle on a Sundae-Sunday
Flap your wings, come on let's fly.
Flap your wings, let's taste the sky
Let's set the streets of Juliet on fire.
Dance with Romeo in the streets of desire
We explode with the light
Burn the dance floor, girl
Nach Baliye
Dance the Balle
Want bangles on your wrist, love ?
- Nach Baliye
Want jewels in your hair, love ?
Run anklets around your feet, love ?
- Nach Baliye
Give me bangles on my wrist, love
Weave jewels into my hair, love
Run anklets around my feet, love
Love to watch you baby,
turn around
The red carpet of dreams
unfurls for us to walk on
Fate's now a little toy,
to toss, to roll, to rock on
Take your bets now, gamble your life.
Fate's at my feet. Ready to ride ?
Then come...
take my hand, love...
l'll give you the ride of your life
Then take my hand, love...
give me the ride of my life
Let's set the streets of Juliet on fire,
dance with Romeo in the streets of desire
We explode with the light
Burn the dance floor, girl
Dance the Balle
Clap your hands everybody,
everybody just clap your hands
Day doesn't sink into night here
These roads stay awake, alight here
Tip-toeing upon my eyelids are dreams
that never sleep
Then take my hand, love...
l'll give you the ride of your life
Attention
Train from Delhi to Bombay is arriving
on platform 36 instead of platform 1 2
Bunty-Babli's largesse for the poor
Con duo named in several heists
Bombay's really crowded, no ?
Everyone's here to make
their dreams come true, no ?
What's this stench ?
Must be fish, no...?
Where do you think
fashion shows happen here ?
Let's get you into a taxi
- And... you ?
l'm going back.
- What !
Look, l don't want to stay in Bombay.
- What do you mean ?
l just... wanted to be really famous...
a name to be reckoned with...
a name in the headlines
Vimmi, for the first time in my life
l think l have a talent no one else has
l realise now, l never was Rakesh.
l've always been Bunty...
l've always enjoyed being him
To tell you the truth, l never had
the perseverance it takes...
to become a Tata or Ambani,
nor the calibre
Anyway, doesn't matter now.
l think l've discovered my destination
And l'm on my way towards it
Look...
this is what l want to do...
all my life, freely
But you please become a model,
a supermodel...
so take care
All this... you did it all alone ?
That's not what l meant. - Then...?
Without you...
- You can't walk one step, you know ?
Wants himself in headlines !
Who wants to read about you ?
No one's interested in reading
or publishing a Bunty-minus-Babli
Truth is... without me, you could've
done nothing and you never will
Your taxi...
Tell me... can you ?
Yes
No
Can you live without me ?
Yes
Then why are you screaming taxi-taxi ?
- Because you need to go
Yes...
- So tell me... where ?
Where you want to go
Who says so ?
You or Babli ?
What do you think ?
Must be you
So will you do something about it ?
lf that's the case then
l must do something about it, no ?
What the hell !
l didn't mean that
Wasn't me. lt was Bunty.
- Everyone's staring
We're in Bombay.
No one looks at anyone here
Think it over
l won't let you rule over the bathroom.
- Done
No more sleeping alone on the floor.
- Sounds good
What about all the modelling dreams ?
- That's Vimmi's problem
But you...?
- l've become Babli
Forever
You know what it's worth ?
Not five paise. lt's a fake
Who...?
- What...?
What's your name?
Mehmood
You're a comedian ?
Let's start by making you laugh ?
Okay, two jokes for you
One
Mrs and Mr Flea come out
after a matinee show
Mrs Flea says,
l'm tired today
Mr Flea says,
honey don't worry, l'll hail us a dog
You are that dog...
the one they rode for the hike
Now spill it, did you go
to Center One that night or no ?
No sir
This here, is my second joke
Where are those two now ?
Long time... gone
Names...?
Bunty y Babli
How old are they ?
Bunty's around 23-24
Babli is 20-21
She was really sweet, well mannered
and intelligent, sir
Even the boy was all heart, great guy
That's quite something, sir
No, you asses are quite something
To think that petty criminals...
booked for cheating, misdemeanour,
malfeasance, fraud and perjury...
are quite something
And not just you, the whole lot of you
from this generation is quite something
Right and wrong, good esteem and bad,
good deeds and bad...
you've forgotten what sets them apart
But l can tell the difference.
And l'm going to teach you fools too
The newspapers say that for
boys and girls in schools and colleges...
these two crooks are role models.
- So they want to be role models ?
Fine...
then that's what they'll become...
l'll make them a fine example
of a cure for this generation
What did you say their names were ?
- Bunty and Babli
This Bunty-Babli better watch out for me
We'll never ever cheat on each other
We'll always place each other
before ourselves
OK
We'll never ever break
each other's hearts
And if we do so accidentally, we won't
burst into tears without warning
Okay, we will never eat or drink
anything without each other
Except early morning tea
You wake up like a queen at noon
l can't wait that long
We'll give each other
the same amount of love forever
Why ? We can give more !
l'll love you even more tomorrow...
more the day after and so much more
the day after the day after
We'll cut off all ties
with those who don't understand us
Except our parents.
- Your parents
We'll be Bunty-Babli
for the rest of our lives
And we'll live out all our dreams.
- Except...
Except...?
- Leave that to me
okej
Now the groom may kiss the bride !
- Oye Rakesh just married !
Look...
right at the outset of this marriage
l want to tell you all about my past
l don't want any issues later
ln school, when l was in Class Two,
Mukesh used to sit behind me
He used to tug at my plaits
And you know...
it used to make me giggle like crazy
These boys are all scoundrels
They'll try their luck
with every cute girl
How true
How lucky l am,
you aren't like those boys
Rakesh... you're such a good boy
Sweet boy
So... what l was saying was...
now that you are my wife...
my mate in joy and sorrow...
for all my days to come...
and nights... understand ?
Asleep ? On your wedding night !
This world we live in
has two kinds of people...
those who aren't married
and those who are
So...?
So you belong to the latter, no ?
So?
So marry me now you fool
TMG
The clouds have torn
My sky has flown
l see my skies breaking free
of the earth at the horizon...
soft, slow, on tip-toe
bit by thieving bit...
soft, slow, tip-toeing my love
Do you see what l see...
the earth flows like a river...
earth in water, water in earth
dissolve and begin to shiver
Then my sky breaks free
of the earth at the horizon
No consciousness of what l am
l have no sense of what l'll be
This time now seems unreal
This can't be happening to me
You slowly dissolve in me
l slowly fade into you
Our feet stop, pick up a dream
Our paths shift, it's coming true
The sky turns over lazily
on it's cloud bed
lt just might melt,
rain down to kiss the ground
The earth dips its toe tips
in a water well
lt just might find feet
roll up, start walking around...
soft, slow, on tip-toe
bit by thieving bit...
Say the word and l stop.
Say the other and l move
lf this is madness that consumes me,
let it be a madness too
Say the word and l stop.
Say the other and l move
A stranger to my destinations
l go where you want me to
Soft, bit by thieving bit
Softly, my love
Babli is Bunty's and Bunty is Babli's
Each other's forever they'll be
Each other's forever...
- They'll be
They began their lives...
in small sleepy towns,
towns they detested
Not for poverty, need or misfortune.
Only for fun
Turning to crime for fun?
l'd never ever heard that before
News of Bunty-Babli's capers
poured in from all quarters...
dripping into my ears
like red hot molten iron
Girls and boys in schools and colleges
began to idolize them as new age heroes
Constantly breathing down their necks,
l even started to think like them...
what next, their next sharp turn...?
My hunches were hitting bull's eye...
and l was inching closer to them
with every passing day
They took their infamy for success
and quickly jumped from cons to scams
Scams no one had ever heard of
or imagined before
Okay, how about Kerala ?
- Too hot
Manali ?
- No, it is too cold
Jaipur ?
- lt's too dusty
Ladakh ?
- lt's too lonely, Harry
How many times am l gonna tell you,
it's a damn historical monument...
not a hotel which l can rent
That's your problem Harry,
you said if we came to lndia...
l could get married wherever l want.
This is what l want
You are impossible
Am l... l am ?
- Yes
Really ? Fine !
Do you see what l see?
- l'm not blind
Do you hear what l hear ?
- l'm not deaf
Are you thinking what l'm thinking ?
- l'm no mind reader. Get to the point
Protesters... thirty. Taxi drivers...?
- Four
School children ?
- Twenty. With one teacher
Newspaper ?
- Agra Times
Minister's office.
- Very good !
And a wedding bash.
- Oye Rakesh ! A first round knockout
l want to marry there Harry,
not put it in my living room
l told you it's not possible Kate
Selling Taj...
- Never, never
Government don't be...
- Clever clever
My car... Mercedes... Mercedes...
- Mercedes stuck in traffic jam
Students protesting Taj sale.
- What sale ?
The Taj is on sale.
Sir this is my Mercedes. Please sit
Please sir... the government is selling
the Taj. We won't let them sell it
Extremely sorry sir, l apologise
Today's newspaper sir ?
Thank you so much, sir
ls the Taj Mahal really up for sale ?
- Yes sir
By who ?
By him, sir
Excuse me
Hold on
No sir, it is not possible.
We cannot sell Taj Mahal to a foreigner
Even if the price is high ?
- No price is too high for Taj Mahal
How about 100 million dollars?
- No sir
1 50 million.- No sir
175 million.
- Sir, l told you, it's not possible
200 million.
- Well...
250 millon
Why don't you speak with her?
- Who ?
Phoolsakhi-ji
Who is Phoolsakhi-ji?
Minister in charge of
purchase and selling of the Taj Mahal
Where's the typist ?
She's down with viral fever.
We're getting another typist
Get her quickly.
- l'll be in the office all day today
Let's pack in as much corruption
as we can today
Of course.
- The typist is here madam'ji
Sit !
My niece's doctoral thesis.
l want it typed out by this evening
Of course, it's me. Go on
What... l'm coming right away
What's the matter ma'am ?
- Riot outside my house ! Hurry !
You keep typing l'll be back in an hour
How long have you been in government ?
- Not very long
And the minister ?
- Not very long either
Sir...
You brought the other money ?
l can't believe ! Someone is actually
selling the Taj Mahal
Nor can l believe !
Someone is actually buying
This ass is going to get kicked
Crowshit on your egghead
He'll be crying for help in two days
How do l look ?
- Very fine
How are you madam ?
Would you believe
l've been dying to see you ?
Madam, this is Mr Harry Epstein
He wants to buy the Taj Mahal
Exactly
l'm not selling
But madam, we had a deal...
- Why are you late ?
But ma'am...
Shut up !
So you can't sell the Taj Mahal to me ?
lt's all a big mistake
And you have wasted my time
One minute
l said l can't sell the Taj Mahal
but it doesn't mean you can't have it
l don't understand
You can lease it on rent
For how long ?
Five years
Ten
Ten ?
Lease document ready for five.
interested, not interested ?
lnterested, interested
Why are you protesting ?
- Because we have grievances
What grievances ?
- Meet our demands or else
What demands ?
The revolution...
- Long live the revolution
Never mind that,
but what are your demands ?
Down with tyranny
Whose...?
- Every tyrant's
Five years
All Harry Epstein's
For a price of 250 million dollars.
- Good doing business with you
And here is your fee
5 million Rupees, cash
Tell me your demands.
- Quit lndia
Quit lndia, quit lndia
Quit lndia...?
- State your demands or l'll arrest you
We demand that Ms Kalasakhi...
- But l'm Phoolsakhi !
Tell them !
- You've got the address wrong
She is Ms Phoolsakhi. Now get out.
- Okay. Sorry. Fine. Relax. Don't mind
Okay then, goodbye.
- Thank you madam
See you.
- Namaste
Which country are you from ?
- Oh, all of them
Your guests should be here soon
Goodbye
What happened to this elevator ?
- Could be stuck somewhere
lt's coming.
- Let's go
Finished ?
- Nearly
lt sure is nice of Mr Bunty to throw us
this wonderful wedding party
And you ! Thank you,
it's a dream come true
Not possible
What do you mean not-possible,
l own the Taj Mahal
ls he nuts ?
He says he owns the Taj Mahal !
Poor thing,
God can really be cruel sometimes
Open the gate before l fire you
... dismiss you
Dismiss ?
He says he'll get us dismissed
Doctor ? You need one ?
We call doctor ?
No doctor ! You talk to Mr Bunty
He wants some Bunty fellow
What Bunty...? Hey wait a minute
are they Bunty and Babli ?
So finally you arrive !
They sold the Taj and scooted while
you stood by and watched it happen ?
Tomorrow when you sell it again
l'll still be left watching
What !
- Look madam...
a bull doesn't budge
until he sees red in his face...
and it takes a scam to prod me into
action. l just got the news, no ?
That's no way to talk.
- Really ? And how did they talk ?
Go on, file your report about
descriptions, characteristics
Stop staring at me and do it
No one could've pulled off this caper
without the help of insiders
Who could it be ?
- Could've been you, madam
You left her alone in the room
at a perfect time
Corruption happens at the top floor.
But one has to climb from the ground floor
There's a saying amongst us policemen.
Orderlies make more under the table
See son...
you shouldn't have gone to the wedding,
that too in a new car. Getting it ?
Hey trumpet
Yes sir ?
What's the most requested
song nowadays ?
Babu'ji, slow it down now
Stand up here
Play
l heard you took an American
to his wedding altar
No, sir
l know their names.
l want to know where they are
Harry says, he was so smooth,
and convincing. Harry's no fool
And you believed ?
- l did
lt was in the Times of lndia.
- All newspapers say...
all Americans have sex all the day,
l believe ?
Don't look at it, you hear me ?
Don't look at it
Sir how about leaving ?
What can we possibly get to know here ?
Here you learn
to what lengths a man can go...
for the smallest of things
Get the serial numbers of the currency
that he withdrew from his bank
Tell me joke
Non-veg
Tired of turning wheels ? Now watch
how the wheels of fortune turn
l didn't see a thing. What can l say?
l'm a simple honest man
God ! This one turns out to be honest!
Wheel back that car...
go on... back out...
go away, far away
There. Stop
The longer the distance,
the more it looks like an accident
Don't move or l'll shoot.
- Sir, what are you saying ?
l told you ! l saw nothing.
- No one's ever seen...
what's about to happen right now
Come on, slam the car.
- No... please
Slam him.
- Please ! No...
l saw, l saw! l saw everything
Turn off the engine
Stand straight
See no evil. Speak no evil. Hear no evil
but if you can profit, grab it
Gandhi'ji would've come here personally
to whack you for being so honest
Who else was in it with them?
Go on, give him every detail
What's wrong ? Why are you sulking?
You're upset with me ?
Moron, the Taj got sold, not your taxi.
Like some nuts ? No ? Suit yourself
There was no corner of the country
Bunty and Babli hadn't been to
And every newspaper
was cheering their ingenuity
But l was dying to see them
behind bars
6 MONTH LATER
No there's no mistake about this order.
Your assignment is being changed
But l've completely
committed myself to the case
Bunty-Babli's case is being assigned
to the federal agencies
To whom ?
- Federal investigation
God !
Our politicians have become honest?
The feds have time for Bunty and Babli ?
They have your sympathies?
- Not those two
My sympathies are with the feds.
- You think the feds can't get them ?
Why ?
- Because they can't think like them
And you can?
l'm beginning to feel
we're related somehow
From tomorrow, you're taking charge
of the gold at the airport
Very well sir
You're the boss
l'll take charge of hell
if you want me to
Anyway what's the score?
- What ?
l found myself a night-watchman's job.
This is how l got to bide my time
Dashrath Singh...
lf there's anybody who'll lay a finger
on Bunty and Babli, it's me
You find this funny ?
You can do this yourself the next time
l won't be able to do this
even if l tried, love
But you can make a mockery of
those who do ?
Ok, l'm sorry
- What idiot could've made you a father
You
One rum, large
You don't need to pay sir
Did l mention l'm a policeman?
- Hear me out, sir
The gentleman out there is hosting
food and drinks for all guests tonight
Who...?
- The man in black
They're buying this restaurant
No way. We're picking up the tab
for everyone tonight
Not tonight. Tomorrow
From tomorrow, this hotel is yours
to do as you please. But tonight's on me
Friends, cocktails and dinner
for everyone on the house
Vodka
Whiskey
Cocktail?
Gin
Rum
Flying to the moon?
- You're selling the tickets ?
You've just bought yourself
a one-way ticket
l don't believe much in buying tickets
but yes, l do want to fly to the moon
You're a man in a hurry?
Somewhat
There's this one place in which
men-in-a-hurry usually end up
You see...
- What ?
This world we live in
has two kinds of people
l see.
- One, the kind that listens
And the kind that talks.
l belong to the latter
So sure of yourself ? What do you do?
- Cleaning
l'm in the cleaning business.
We clean out places
What kind of places ?
- Any kind
So you like tidy places?
- No, l like tidy sums of money
lnteresting man.
Where are you from?
- Allahabad
Aha, you look that type
Sir, one more large ?
Bring it on then
What's happening here ?
You're smoking in front of your baby?
- How the hell can he see me ?
Babies know everything.
- How can they know everything ?
Stop it !
l get the feeling l'm her baby
And he who is he ?
l... am...
- He is...
Whoever, doesn't matter. Come on
Women... are like this only.
- How and how do you think women are ?
Oye, don't stoke my anger.
- Hello, what's happening here ?
A fight can't you see?
- That l can, but why ?
Private matters of husband-wife!
How meddlesome !
Please stub that out
You look like a long lost father!
Ought to be setting an example for him
And you better come along.
l'm checking out the rooms in this hotel
Don't take too long
Don't come back in an hour or two.
Spoilt the mood for no rhyme or reason
You seem to be much fallen-in-love
You've never fallen... in love?
Once, a little
What?
A little
ln a summer of Delhi
l came upon her
Every single day on bus number 481 ...
l would fall all over myself
to vacate the ladies' seat...
and she would sit down
with the sweetest smile
For a whole year...
- You never spoke ?
When our eyes were saying so much
how could words dare to interfere ?
But...
l can shower her with gifts, can't l ?
So every week, l'd fall over myself
to give her my gift
And she...
- Would smile ?
And take it
And l'm sure that one day, in return for
all my gifts she would give me...
that one big gift l've been
waiting for.
- So did the gift arrive ?
Winter arrived
On the 2 1 st of December...
wrapped in a maroon shawl
and a warm smile...
she stepped into the bus.
Radiance on her face and in her hands...
a Golden Bakery box.
lnside that box...
were the world's most beautiful
heart shaped... you know...
heart-shaped pastries
And then
for the first time in a year...
she spoke her first words to me
Please...
would you distribute these pastries
to all the passengers
l just got engaged
Ei handsome
- Yeah?
What happened ?
She's calling you
Who is ?
Tonight's your night
Those pangs you feel in your heart
have pained me too
Why not drown our pains tonight?
Nice
Rare are those moments in life
when desire calls
Come into my arms,
or come and slit my throat
Oh forget it...
this give and take of hearts
takes a lot of heart...
and doing it so boldly for the world
to see... it's a woman's art you see
ln this winning and losing
of hearts what are men worth ?
His ruthless gaze...
tore up the street...
took me apart
lt ran a razor's edge
down the willing side of my heart
TmG
l fall to restless pieces...
don't look at me that way
l fall to restless pieces,
A townful of men in ruin
surrenders to what l say
stretch with desire, l take my bow
l stretch with desire...
come touch me now
Night eyes...
night eyes... your night eyes...
The moon sleeps inside those night eyes
Night eyes, your night eyes
Night falls inside those night eyes
Night eyes, my night eyes
We are one inside twin night eyes
Night eyes, your night eyes
The moon sleeps inside those night eyes
These sighs you swore,
wrote them in kohl
Come to life inside these eyes
That kiss you left on my handkerchief
l knot it until it dies
Oh your words are wisps
from incense bowls
You waft in lazy
like the warm wind rolls
l bow, l stretch... come touch me
l stretch with desire, l take my bow
Night eyes, my night eyes
You're a shadow inside my night eyes
These eyes take me by surprise
Ask private questions, brook no lies
Hide under those veil-like lids
The curtains behind which she shies
No curtains hide my pain,
no lies try to guard me
l hurt only when
she gives her word not to scar me
Night eyes, your night eyes l was
stung when l sung to your night eyes
Night eyes, your night eyes
The moon sleeps inside my night eyes
You are mine
in the memories of old stone cities
Our songs still echo
in those forlorn cities
From the south gate arch
to where the north gate lies...
you and l are lore set in stone cities
l hear the call of the saint on the wall
And swear
by the black beauty of your eyes
l'm the guardian
from evil your eyes never had
l'll suffuse them with smiles
so they never look sad
Our bodies, they ache
Our lips, they quake
Come touch me, oh touch me,
oh touch me now
Tonight is the night,
the night is tonight
Tonight's the night,
oh night-eyes
l love the way you sway
Text: By RahelSurshi :)
By RahelSurshi
Madam, l am your only Adam
Night eyes...
oh the dark of her nights in my eyes
Why do you dole out free drinks?
Why give free drinks, you fool!
How will you run your hotel ?
Anyway...
l enjoyed your company
l feel satisfied and a little in love
And it helped me forget those two
Forget them... you've nothing to do
with those scoundrels
Generally...
l don't take to strangers too well
But l don't know...
l don't know why the two of you
have touched my heart
We've done what...?
- Touched my heart...
you could've been my children
You haven't told us your name.
- You haven't told...
My name is Dashrath
Dashrath Singh,
Deputy Commissioner of Police
You're a police'wallah?
- What did you think ? Balloon' wallah?
Why what's come over you ?
What's it ?
- Sir, Rickshaw' wallah...
Sit in the rickshaw
Go on, take him home.
- Yes, take me home
lt's very late.
- Very late at night
Take me to the airport
... no not there
l'm going to Police Lines.
- Go on, quick
Oh my God, the very same Dashrath
Singh the one who's been after us ?
My baby almost had a heart attack!
That was close, let's get out of here
Get out ? The fun's only just begun
- What are you talking about ?
Look, he never knew what we look like.
He still doesn't. But now...
we know who he is
and we also know that...
he's in charge of the security
of the gold stashed at the airport
By God ! You are...
- Vimmi, if we don't...
steal the meat
right from the lion's den...
what did we achieve?
- Your hunger's getting out of hand
Now we're a threesome. We'll need
more food... what do you say ?
You'll get us killed someday
lndia's Central Bank doesn't keep
it's gold in any one place
To protect the gold from
fires, floods or earthquakes...
the cache is split over
four different cities
Depending on the requirements
of various banks...
this gold is shuttled by air between
these four cities once every week
How they cracked this confidential
information, they haven't divulged
But what they did that day
no one could have ever imagined
Not even me...
Delhi-Mumbai, 9.1 0 pm tonight.
Korpal, Puneet, Mr
Delhi-Calcutta, 9.40 pm.
Sharma, Vandana, Mrs
What's this other ticket for?
- Backup
Why the Air Traffic
Control number?- Backup
A back up for everything?
Oye Rakesh, is there one for you too ?
Yes
Who ?
You
Smart
Call back the Jet airways flight
Mumbai. The bomb is ticking
What nonsense.
A bomb on the plane ?
Jet 9W31 2. Yes Delhi Control ?
Turn back and proceed for landing
on emergency runway number 2
There is a bomb scare
Delhi Control is this a joke?
Bomb on board, he says
Jet 9W31 2. Turning back
Which runway?
- Number 2. Bomb squad is on the runway
The caller's number. Get it now
Go get the number from them. Now !
We can't have the number
lt isn't under our jurisdiction.
- As long as the gold is on board...
this plane, the bomb, this airport,
everything is under our jurisdiction
How many people knew about the gold?
- Four bank employees
Are you implying the news was leaked?
- Give me the key to the box
But we are not permitted to open it.
- Give me the key
Now it's your responsibility.
- The bomb might explode any time, sir
The bomb has exploded. Send message to
headquarters. l am assuming command
DCP Dashrath Singh here...
Surround the airport area
Locate persons who do not have
any reason to be here at this hour
Take suspects into custody
and inform immediately
They received the bomb scare
from this number
Dial
Ringing
Orange Maruti Swift 5700
Vimmi we'll have to ditch this car.
They've spotted it. Get out !
Stop... taxi
Stop... please
Papa'ji, please help us ! l'll give you
more money than you ever imagined
Son, for this job, l won't take money
even if you give it to me...
come my child, get up,
you'll do fine
Have faith in god. Faith prevails
Sir, what are you saying ? Policemen
in every hospital and nursing home ?
We won't have men for policing the city.
- She's in labour. She's about to deliver
She goes at dar for a moment
Every child born in Delhi tonight
will see a policeman's face...
before anything else
That Dashrath Singh figured me out.
- How are you so sure?
l know. l saw it in his eyes...
Then...
in no time every hospital in Delhi
will be crawling with policemen
Which hospital
do you want to go to son ?
The biggest...
the biggest hospital in Delhi
Not a hospital or nursing home,
they'll go to a nondescript clinic
lf l know that Bunty, he'll definitely
take Babli to the biggest hospital
Vimmi, don't be afraid
This hospital is packed choc-a-bloc
with newborns and their mothers
lt'll take them ages to check each bed.
But you please hurry it up
lt isn't in my hands, bloody idiot !
l told you
you'll get us killed someday
Hush
But hey, what life did l have
before l met you ?
ls everything all right?
- Yes
Papa'ji... if you weren't here today...
- There would have been someone else
The Lord up there runs
a regular courier service
He always provides for ones in need
Where are you going ?
You can't go in
Pointless... he must've taped
the gate downstairs. Walk
Those two have fled the hospital
but they haven't fled Delhi yet
Seal Delhi, sir
Papa'ji, all that you've done for us...
- One honest man would do for another
Papa'ji, you're kidding me
By now you must have figured that
we aren't half as honest as we seem
l don't know what you've done
to make these people hunt you down...
but l see a simple honesty
in your eyes... take care son.
God bless you
For the next week or so
they'll be baying for our blood
We'll return afterwards... but
where have you hidden the gold ?
What's your baby, a boy or a girl ?
What will you name your baby ?
Before you think of a name
you need to see the baby at least ?
A day has gone by, have you
even taken one look at your baby ?
Did you hold your child in your arms,
even once... once even ?
Vimmi, you know we didn't have any time
for these. Had l stopped for all this...
all three of us would've either been
jailed or killed by now
Some reason for celebration !
The day he is born... his parents die
Cursed fate to be born with !
- Not his fault, is it ?
That's what l'm saying!
What wrong has he done...
to deserve parents
who can go to jail anytime...
leaving him to rot on the streets
What are you trying to say?
- Enough
l won't do this anymore.
Neither will you...
Then what else can we do?
- Anything, whatever everyone else does
lf we had to end up doing
what everybody else does...
why did we ever run away from home?
- Because we were wrong
Now we're not free to live as we like.
Now we're responsible for one more life
How's he going to grow up?
- How ? With us, that's how
With us?
And which school will he go to ?
You know this world we live in
has two kinds of people. One...
who waste the best years of their lives
in schools and colleges. And...
the kind who school themselves. Like us.
We taught us to do what we're doing
Which is what he'll learn?
- Of course !
And then he'll go to jail someday?
- Have we ever been to jail?
We very nearly got thrown into jail
l don't want my son
growing up behind bars...
or dying young on the run
Do you remember agreeing on
all our marriage vows except...
We'll be Bunty-Babli
for the rest of our lives
And we'll live out all our dreams.
- Except...
Except...?
- Leave that to me
Okay
This is the exception Rakesh
You're getting over-emotional
about this motherhood business
But now l am whatever l am.
Now l want to hear your decision
Choose. lt's either this life
... or a life together
So what have you decided?
What'll l do without the two of you ?
Those marriage vows
weren't mere words
Fursatganj or Pankinagar?
ls it you that's saying this or... ?
Bunty and Rakesh. -Both
What ?
Tickets
Since when are we buying tickets ?
- From today
Why become so damn honest ?
Oye Rakesh, you're in love
Oh all right
Rakesh my boy, this world we live in
has two kinds of men. One...
the kind that thinks twice
before getting married
And the kind that thinks afterwards
like you, you idiot
Two tickets for Fursatganj
Name ?
Rakesh Trivedi, Vimmi Trivedi
Bunty and Babli
You've had a long run.
You must be tired
Can we have some water ?
Die of thirst dog !
Not for me. For the two of them
You won't believe me but we quit
being crooks half an hour ago
Absolutely right, l won't believe you.
- But if l insist l'm telling the truth ?
l'll start doing right now
what l had planned to do to you in jail
Why are you looking at me like that ?
- He's telling the truth
Guaranteed by you,
lndia's biggest bonafide liar ?
l'm not lying
A dog's tail insists it became
ramrod straight half an hour ago ?
You're as old as my father... no one's
had the cheek to talk to her like that
So you respect your elders now, do you ?
- And why shouldn't we ?
Now don't tell me you pray
first thing every morning too !
She does
So...?
- So what !
Now you pray to your heart's content
in jail ! lt's all your fault...
now suffer.
- My fault ?
Who's idea was it to go straight ?
- lt was for a good cause...
do you want your son to go to jail ?
- So where's he going now ?
Now l see how the two of you
have been fooling people for years
Pappu is hungry
Pappu ?
When did we start calling him Pappu ?
Got to call him something no?
You're thinking of the gold all the time
Let's step outside for a while
l'm not going anywhere.
- Up
Darned luck. No one ever caught us
when we were in the thick of it
But the moment we quit...
- Why did you get into all this ?
l wanted to become someone important.
- And... you became ?
You won't understand.
- Why...
why won't l understand ?
Because he never did.
- Who ?
My father
He's just like you
You're trying to con me again
May l...?
- A smoke ? Sure...
Where are you going ?
lf she sees me smoking
she'll scream
The child will stay with the mother
What's the use of crying now ?
Should've considered this beforehand.
- What else to do ?
Become a ticket collector and
collect ten rupee bribes all my life ?
You can come in
We'll have to make a phone call
to your home or mine
We certainly can't take him with us.
- No, it won't come to that
l'll figure something.
- And con ourselves out of this one too ?
What else to do ?
Take with me to jail, the very son
for whose sake l gave up everything ?
What justice ! Jails are for reforming.
And here, three people are being jailed
Text: By RahelSurshi :)
Two of whom have reformed
and a third who's completely innocent
Don't worry Vimmi. l'll crack a plan.
- What plan Rakesh ?
We've run out of plans
Vimmi do you have any idea
what jails are like ?
How will you spend
so many years inside one ?
Let's do something,
l'll take the blame for everything
Then you're free to go home
to Fursatganj with the baby
All you wanted was to become a model
l dragged you into this whole thing
You can't even make a cup of tea
for yourself. ln jail... how ?
l'll manage Vimmi,
don't worry about me
Have you ever managed to do
anything alone ?
ln any case,
Bunty is nothing without Babli
Get up
Unlock yourselves...
l can't do it...
We're nearing the railway signal
on the outskirts of Delhi
The train halts there for two minutes
The two of...
The three of you can get off
and go wherever you wish
No one recognises
Bunty and Babli except me
And no one ever will
Sir...
- Shut up. Not a word
Or l just might change my mind
Get going
That's enough
Whether it was my life's biggest mistake
or their best con act, l didn't know
But policemen are human too,
believe it or not...
we wear those uniforms only on our body,
at heart we're as vulnerable as babies
l believed l had destroyed Bunty-Babli,
so l let Rakesh and Vimmi go...
because l think the law needs
to destroy crime, not lives
The bank's gold was recovered from
the spot Babli had indicated
The recoveries continued
for months afterwards...
Monies and valuables
stolen by Bunty and Babli
l think they had told me
the truth about going back...
to live respectable,
honest lives like their parents
Rakesh'ji could you perhaps
increase the pressure
What a joy
This world we live in
has two kinds of Pappus. One...
the kind who obey their parents
and get to eat chocolates
and the kind that doesn't
and gets locked up inside toilets
You are...?
- The first
My darling baby
But he didn't even drink his milk.
- He'll eat the chocolate
What good are chocolates?
You and your fads
No, l'm feeling cold...
- Forget the cold. Be fashionable
What are you teaching Pappu ?
To speak the truth
and pray every morning
Where's my son ? One of his friends
is waiting downstairs
Friends and folks in Fursatganj
find all the time for fun
You fix the name of this city.
l'll fix this friend
My son is genius from...
childhood
l am very lucky
l got a daughter-in-law
who is very very smart
lt's such a joy to know that
our son and his wife...
have done things so important that
your department still remembers them
Never told folks at home
what all you achieved ?
Maybe you should tell us
Nervous already ?
A scam is in the offing
Huge scam
Sir...
l swear by my son,
l've given it up
l've no idea of
what scams are happening
For three years now,
l'm following a work-home-work routine
This scam has got to be stopped.
- Then go ahead and stop it
We cannot stop it
Who else can ?
You
Then save me from this
respectable-dignified life ! Please
Who's saying this ?
You or...?
- We both
l'm through
lf l make mango pickle
one more time l'll die
lt's killing me, Rakesh
Keep the faith
Hace tiempo me dijo que estaba
en el negocio de la limpieza
Once upon a time he told me that
he was in the business of cleaning
Text By RahelSurshi =)