New Delhi's National Sports stadium..
The stadium is filled to the brim.
Only 2 minutes left in the
World Men's Hockey Championship..
India is one goal behind Pakistan.
Vijay, pass it here!
Indian Captain Kabir Khan, Asia's
best center forward pushing his team
Come on! Come on!
Suspense in the audience.
Tension on the faces
of the officials..
Like every lndia-Pakistan match,
this match means so much
more than the game itself.
Only 1 and a half minutes now
and lndia will have to
fight quickly to save itself.
Ball with Pakistani
defender Waseem.. Scoop!
But lndian defender Uttam Singh
snatches it.. India is now on attack!
And a penalty stroke for lndia..
A breath of life
they desperately need..
But who will take this stroke..
Ball! Ball!
Saini has the ball, but Captain
Kabir is taking the stroke himself..
Maybe a good decision.
India's best player
is its last hope...
Coach, is this the same team
that defeated Pakistan last year?
No comments.
Do you not think our
team is taking it too easy?
Please, please, no comments.
Hey, look, it is Kabir!
- Kabir!
He is here!
- Kabir.. Kabir.. Kabir,
do you have anything to say
about such an embarrassing defeat?
Do you really believe
Pakistan's performance was better?
Maybe. - Why did you take
the penalty stroke yourself?
I made a mistake
Rumour has it that the Pakistani
players are your good friends..
you were the only lndian to
congratulate them after the match..
Excuse me!
People are saying..
there is a rumour that you..
or someone else in the lndian team
has deliberately thrown this match?
Excuse me!
Do you think we lost
because someone sold out?
What! What did you say?
Kabir Khan, has
someone sold out their team?
Sold out! You piece of..
How dare you..
How can you disrespect the media!
Disrespect the media!
You son of a.. Come here.
You do not know how
to treat journalists!
You bloody -.. sold out
Come back here!
You just witnessed a
frustrated captain of the loosing
team attack the media violently.
His outburst cannot
hide the fact that there..
..is definitely
something fishy going on.
We have our answers.
But it is now up to
you to decide whether
Kabir Khan has played
dirty with the country or not.
Satyavrat Yadav,
National Stadium, New Delhi..
News from the world of sports.
Pakistan has become the
new Hockey World Champions
after defeating lndia by one goal.
Today the Chairman of the
Hockey Association denounced
Kabir Khan, declared he
did his country wrong.
And all this is thanks to you..
the lndian public.
We have two special guests..
Down with Kabir!
What do you think? Did
Kabir Khan fix the match?
Do not know if he fixed the match,
but we lost because of him.
And what would you say?
These people should
be hung upside down.
And you?
These kind of people should have
moved to Pakistan during the partition.
Down with Kabir!
The public is upset with
the team's performance.
And Kabir Khan has
conveniently disappeared.
He was not at the hockey stadium, nor
the Sports Authority of lndia Campus.
Where is Kabir Khan?
Do not look back mother, let us go.
How can I not, Kabir..
Your grandfather saved every
penny to build this house..
Your father's first pay check
went into making these windows..
I stepped into this
home as a young bride..
Whatever happens, I know all these
people will stand by us, trust me.
My master
TRAlTOR
Do not look there, son.
You can close your eyes if
you can not bear to see it..
I want to see everything.
TRAlTOR
Come son. Let us go!
The third colour of
your being, that was l
Papa, papa, I want to see
what a traitor looks like.
Come, see!
Your tune was the rhythm of my life
Just some food for the road..
Do you want us to be
thrown out of the neighbourhood?
My divine master, you are my pride
My master, my life is yours to take
So, what have you decided?
Uttamji, you are always
harping on the same thing.
What should we do about the coach?
Hey, why don't you
become their coach?
The Women's Hockey World Cup
is just three months away.
The team cannot just go
without any training..
No matter how much you
train them, they will loose..
The lndian Women's hockey
team has never achieved anything
and it never will.
It is a government trip.
Why do you not go as their coach?
The team will be out in a
couple of matches. Exit!
You and your wife
could enjoy a holiday.
I do not get it - why do you not
take women's hockey seriously.
And we do no get why
you take it so seriously.
Uttamji, lndian women
are born to cook and clean.
They cannot run
around in short skirts.
How can an Association
member say such things?
It is because we are
in the Association
and have travelled around the
world, that we can say such things.
Look, you have done your part and
selected the top 1 6 lndian players.
Punjab, Tamil Nadu,
Jharkand, Andhra, Railways.
You have even been to
remote Manipur and Mizoram.
But now where will you
find a coach? From the moon?
Is this also the girls' fault?
No, It is not the girls' fault.
It is the fault, of people like
you with expectations from them.
No sponsors.. no viewers..
no TV coverage, nor media..
Now which coach will want to jump
into this mess to ruin his career?
Is there anyone? No one.
There is one man.
Who?
Kabir.
Kabir Khan.
The Kabir Khan who..
Yes that one.
Since when has he developed
an interest in women's hockey?
He even left men's hockey years ago.
No one has seen him
for six-seven years.
You can see him now.
Where?
Outside. In the reception.
Do not attack the opposing
team's goal but their minds.
You will win the goal automatically.
Sir
- Hmm?
You have been called inside.
Sir
- Kabir.
How many years has it..
Seven years, three months.. ten,
eleven, twelve, thirteen
7 years, 3 months, 14 days.
What.. what were you
doing all these years?
I was preparing for this meeting.
He wants to be the coach of
the lndian Women's Hockey Team.
You are not a child Mr. Kabir Khan.
You know in a country like ours,
a women's team exists just
as a formality, not a reality.
Your reputation is already..
And you wish to redeem your
name by coaching this team.
A team that is not fit to play
against European high schools.
This is exactly the team I want.
I do not understand..
I do not think you would.
So shall I consider myself hired?
In any case, you do
not have another coach.
I have done all I could,
but you should think about it.
I have.
Kabir this not a team.
It is a graveyard.
Why are you burying in it?
This team will never get
a better coach than you.
But think about yourself.
I am thinking about myself.
You have changed.
You have changed a lot.
I have not changed. Nothing has.
You know we did not lose
that match because of you.
You did all you could to
score a goal against Pakistan
But they scored against me, my
team, my country.. and my family.
Everybody is allowed one mistake.
Everybody?
Kabir, why have you come back?
To help this team to
win the World Cup.
Which is impossible..
Is what needs to be done.
when are your 1 6 girls coming?
They should reach here tomorrow
morning from their respective states.
States.. nothing has changed.
There were states then,
there are states now..
There you go..
Well ma'am, once again it looks like
the Association has
dumped all of lndia on us.
So these are the best?
That's what they say.
Wasn't she the
goalkeeper for the Railways?
What was her name?
Vidya.. Vidya Sharma.
Heard she got
married and quit hockey?
Well she's here..
1 00 rupees? My foot! Is
the meter for decoration?
The meter is broken, you
will have to give me 1 00.
I will give you 1 00 slaps!
- What sort of talk is that?
The kind you will understand! Take the
50 or I will shove the hockey stick!
Don't get angry.
Your head will
explode one of these days.
But grandma, you are not
saying anything to him.
Is he my baby or are you?
I am.
- So?
Cool down, come, come.. drink it in.
Hey! What the.. you brats!
Hey Komal!
These pansies! Thought
I'd show them how to play!
You haven't come
here to play with boys!
No.. just wanted to check out
whether these Delhi dudes can play.
There's no way I'm letting my
girl play in a big city like Delhi.
Come on. Let's go,
get back in the car
Oh come now! We have come this far..
Let her do what
she wants. After all,
she will be playing a home
maker for the rest of her life.
I will never give up playing!
Oh yeah? What will you feed
your husband when he is hungry?
This!
Enough! I don't want
my girl playing hockey.
Once she slips out of our grasp,
who will ask for her hand?
Let them try!
Gul, your grandfathers,
your father, your brother
all have excelled in
this game, my dear.
Now it is your turn.
Don't let the lqbals down.
Name please.
- Ho?
Ho? Name. What is your name?
Soimoi.
I asked for your name.
Not your medical condition.
Soimoi.
Is that your name?
- Ho.
Ho again? Your full name..
name! Name!
Soimoi Kerketa. She
doesn't understand English.
And you are?
- Rani (Queen)
Have you escaped from an asylum?
What do you want?
Rani Dispotta.
Are you from the travelling theatre?
The stadium won't be
available till the new year. Go away!
Ghamorni.. state board.. Jharkhand..
Oh dear!
These two are hockey players!
Ho, ho, ho!
Name?
- Nethra Reddy.
So you are a Madrasi?
Telegu.
Tamil.
Not Tamil, Telegu.
Same thing. What's the
difference between Tamil and Telegu?
The same difference that is
there between Punjabi and Bihari.
Oh really?
Can I go?
What?
Ho ho!
Man! Look at that vanilla ice
cream amidst all this chocolate!
Must be heading to a
disco or a nightclub..
Looks like they lost their way.
You think they are players?
Definitely players. But not here..
Ya? Wonder what
the going rates are..
Why don't you ask them? They
won't get our language anyway
Hey, how much are those melons for?
What the.. They understand Hindi!
Thought they were
Chinese or Nepali..
Molly Zimik, Manipur.
Mary Ralte, Mizoram.
Wow! You have come from the
furthest reaches of lndia.
You are our special guests. Welcome!
What.. are you not happy?
Would you be happy being treated
like an alien in your own country?
Bindia, Aliya how are you?
Pretty fit.
How's your injury Gunjan?
An injury madam will take
its own sweet time to go.
You are the senior players.
Behave like one.
Be respectful around the new coach.
Respect, madam, will
take its own time to come.
Sukhlal! Become older!
My name is Kabir Khan. I'm the Coach
of the lndian National
Women's Hockey Team..
which I have been
told are you girls.
All the players here, Krishnaji?
Yes sir. Only one's missing..
Uh, Preeti Sabarwal
Reporting time was 10 am, wasn't it?
Excuse me!
Is this the
registration for the women's team?
The registration for the lndian
National Women's team is over.
Bloody hell! I'm Preeti Sabarwal.
Bloody hell Preeti Sabarwal!
You are very late. Try next year.
Sorry?
Next year.
- Next year!
Everybody, fall in line please!
Ho?
Come on everyone, line up.
She is a good player, sir.
I will be the judge of who is a
good player or a bad player Krishnaji.
Thank you.
You.. you can't keep out
a state team captain..
Which state team's captain are you?
- Chandigarh
Is this the Chandigarh team?
No.
But I'm a captain of a state team.
And I'm the coach of the
lndian National Women's Team.
I cannot hear or see
the names of states.
I can only hear the name
of one country - lndia.
And in that team, there is
no place for late comers.
Everyone understand that?
OK..OK, kit up.
Kit up and do 10
rounds in exactly 7 minutes.
If you are done in 7 minutes,
come join the team.
If not, take the
train back to Chandigarh.
Sir, 7 minutes!
Sshhh, Krishnaji.
Now each player will step
forward and introduce herself.
You!
Balbir Kaur, Punjab
Again.
Break away from the
team and step aside.
Komal Chautala, Haryana
Out!
Molly Zimik, Manipur
- Out!
Nethra Reddy, Andhra Pradesh
Out
- Rachna Prasad, Bihar.
Nichola Sequeira, Maharashtra
Out
Vidya Sharma, lndia
Hmm?
Once more loudly.
Vidya Sharma, lndia
Thank you. You are on the team.
Anyone else who is playing for Punjab,
Himachal, Tamil Nadu, Railways?
Understand this once and for all,
because I won't repeat it.
This team needs only those
players who first play for lndia,
then for their teammates,
and then if they have any
life left, for themselves.
Not those who are playing for a
Government job or a Railway flat. Hmmm?
Ho!
Ho? Let's try one
more time. Come, please.
Balbir Kaur, lndia
Komal Chautala, lndia
Molly Zimik, lndia
Nethra Reddy, lndia
Rachna Prasad, lndia
Nichola Sequeira, lndia.
Vidya Sharma, lndia
Gul lqbal, lndia
Rani Dispotta, lndia
Soimoi Kerketa, lndia
Raynia Fernandes, lndia
Mary Ralte, lndia
Aliya Bose, lndia
Gunjan Lakhani, lndia
Bindia Naik, lndia
Preeti Sabarwal, lndia
Come on, move it, move it
Didi(elder sister), didi! You
are Bindia Naik, aren't you?
You hold a National
record of 42 goals!
So?
I am so happy to meet you!
Yay! Go dance then!
On the list this is my bed.
There's the list. Go sleep there.
Forget it Molly!
Correct.
Hello! I am Nethra.
Vidya.
I know. You saved 4 goals in
the South Zone tournament.
Didn't save them,
just happened somehow.
It was all luck.
Only good players have good 'luck'.
Whoa.. what's this?
Ho?
What is this?
'Moke daayar se laglak'
She is saying a branch scraped her
while travelling on an elephant.
You came to Delhi on an elephant?
No, only till Gha-morni. (morni
- peacock)
Peacocks? What peacock?
Peacocks, elephants..
You live in a zoo?
Jharkhand. We are from Jharkhand.
[Jhadi=bush]
Oh! Lots of bushes there?
Jungle. It is a jungle there.
Jungle? Are you Junglees?
You eat snakes and scorpions? I
hope there aren't any in your bag?
Are you upset?
Alright! Here
- you sleep on the floor.
What are you doing?
Sorry?
Nothing to be sorry about..
move this..
What the
- What do you think you're doing?
This is my bed.
Did you not see
this big bundle here?
So?
So? I put it here first,
so the bed is mine.
Just because you dumped
this bundle, it is your bed?
Of course! Haven't you
ever been on a state bus?
I have reserved this bed first!
It is mine on the list.
Oh you.. what the..
I will smash your face!
Hey kid!
Get here.
C'mon!
There is a time and
place for every fight.
Save this one for another day
- when you have the upper hand.
Get out!
Come. Be on this side with us.
The travelling theatre
would have been better!
I am told that from
the 250 million girls
in this country you are
the 16 best hockey players.
You're lucky, but also unlucky.
Because now I'll be the judge.
For me, you are only 16
girls who dabble in hockey.
Don't expect anymore.
You'll regret it.
Ten kilometers. Everyone Come on!
Come on, girls!
Training us for a
marathon or a match?
Hey!
Running at 4am won't make
us better hockey players.
How dare he treat national
players like this! We're not kids.
Does he think we
don't know how to train?
Move, you..
Take your positions.
What's going on?
What's the problem?
You are playing right in.
But sir..
I think you will
play better as right in.
But.. I have always played
center forward for our Haryana team..
Ok, go! Play for the Haryana team.
Everybody in position!
What is it?
Coach sir has instructed me
to play on the forward line.
Go home and play.
Listen
- push her out and take her place.
But the coach has asked me
to play in this position.
So if the coach asks you
to jump in a well, you will?
But the coach..
Look, coaches will come and go.
But you will be with us, right?
Yes, but coach..
See, she's leaving to
drink water. Grab her place.
Don't take my name.
What's going on?
I play forward every year.
Yes but in this team
you are the centre..
This team or that team it
doesn't make a difference.
It makes a difference to the team.
You're a senior player,
a strong player.
The team needs you at centre half.
Go to your new position.
Sorry.
Hmmm.
Out.
What..
Sit out and let the
others play.. Out!
Move!
Good goal! Very
good Preeti Sabarwal!
Come on everyone, back to one!
Komal! Pass the ball!
I'm free, dammit, pass the ball!
Komal! Komal!
What was that?
I scored a goal sir!
Out!
But you didn't see
what that girl was up to!
I saw everything
that's going on here.
When she scored the goal
there was no one around her,
But when you scored, she was there.
And the only one in
the scoring position..
Out!
Everybody can only see the
Memsahib but are blind to her faults.
The British have gone but left
behind their Memsahibs in cities.
Just step in my village once!
If I don't tie you up with the
buffalo's tail, you can change my name.
Coach took Memsahib's side.
He's only a coach, not God.
Come let us rest for a while.
Hey!
Out..
So chowmein! Get angry once more and
They will pour chilli
sauce on you and chew you up.
Come, come here!
Take it, take it, take it, damn you!
Moka! Moka (Pass to me!)
Stop it, stop that, stop the ball..
You piece of.. go kill
yourself or I will kill you.
The bloody..
What happened?
Did you not see? This
witch let them score a goal!
You know she can not
understand Punjabi.
She should have learnt
it before coming here!
She was only supposed to have
learnt hockey. Which she has.
Apologize to her.
I have never apologized
- not even to my father!
Out..
What!
Out! Out!
Why do you not tell her off?
She is not worth talking to
I have always said
- do not play with Junglees!
You look very angry.
You looked like you
would break her head..
Should I break yours?
Sir, how long should
these girls be benched?
Don't know.
I do not think anyone can teach
these girls to play hockey together.
Teaching them hockey
is a long way off.
I need to teach them
something else first.
Good evening!
What is going on?
New sleeping arrangements?
Old.. according to the old list.
So? Tell them the list tore..
come on, go to your old place.
No girl will stay with
another girl from her own state.
It is the Coach's order.
So let him say it. Who cares?
Everyone else has agreed.
If you have any
problems speak to the coach.
Bake in sun all day,
switch beds at night..
Is this a National
camp or a refugee camp?
Why doesn't he make every
one sleep on the benches?
How are you?
I have had enough, please come back.
I cannot come.
It is uncle Samir's sister's wedding.
Mom and dad asked me to call you.
Rakesh you know this
is the National camp-
But Vidya..
Look, family comes first,
games later..
But, father-in-law..
Look, you insisted,
so we let you play.
Now we are calling you, so
come back by the next train.
Yes.. but l..
Rakesh please understand.
I cannot come.
I have waited a long
time for this camp.
Vidya, you are a saint.
But I am not.
I cannot keep waiting. The
wedding is day after tomorrow.
Come if you want or forget it.
So?
They wanted a
traditional daughter-in-law..
..grandchildren, the
whole work from me..
..but all I have is
this hockey stick.
Oh! Is this how you scare them away?
If you want, you can go
home for a couple of days.
If I go now, I will not come back.
It is either this side. Or that.
But.. When you
were getting married..
I told them everything.
They were thrilled then..
I had a job thanks to the sports
quota as well as a government flat.
So now?
They have gotten used to the flat,..
..now they want somebody
who will take care of it.
You think It is crime to
play hockey in this country?
No, no you can play politics,
cricket..
you sure can play cricket!
But hockey?
It is a little difficult.
Have you heard of
Mohammad bin Tuglaq?
Is he cute?
He was an emperor
- five hundred years ago.
Crazy guy! Drove everyone mad.
Stopped making gold and
silver coins for copper ones.
Out in five years.
That is how this
coach is going to go.
Thinks he can do anything.
If you have such a sharp brain,
why do you not use when you play?
He will be out in a few days.
The Association will kick him out.
The system does not work like this.
The name suits him
- Tuglaq.
Molly, Balbir,
Komal,
Bindia, Aliya -
You are benched.
So till we do not play by his
rules he will not let us play.
Tuglaq has lost it.
Alright. We are no less.
We will now play
only at the tournament.
Sir! Hey sir!
Sir, I would like to play too.
Ok, Ok.. I am really sorry.
Sorry
Hey, ok enough.. come on,
accept my apology
Accepting it, or should I hit you?
Sorry.
Really sorry.
Actually, she is not a bad player.
When she whacks the ball hard,
it takes four girls to stop it.
Admiring your enemy?
Please do not pull my leg, didi.
The coach has already
stopped us from playing.
And then..
Oh man..
Oh.. oh!
Come didi, let us play..
If we play, we will play in our
own positions. Shut up and sit down.
God, look there is
bull chasing her..
You've already scored your forty
two goals. I haven't even started.
Sir let me also get a
pardon from the memsahib.
Hey missy, do you want
to accept my apology?
Or do you prefer going to the jail?
- What?
Look, if you do not
pardon me, I will fight you..
in the fight either I will smash
your head or you will smash mine
and we will have to go to jail..
Anyway.. so tell me do you accept my
apology or should we go to the police?
Time is up. Come on!
Krishnaji, is anyone injured?
Ok, now we will
reverse the play order.
Defenders will attack
and attackers will defend.
Sorry sir!
Go attack! Ball on the centre.
With all your heart! Come on!
In the World Cup final,
the team lost to Pakistan.
Wasn't he the team Captain?
Captain?
He was Pakistan's captain,
in an lndian uniform.
What are you saying?
It is not only me. Everyone says so.
So how did they make him the coach?
This is lndia. Anything is possible.
He mentioned taking
us to the World Cup.
He has already
sold his country once.
This time he may
just sell us as well!
You guys will keep scrubbing
shoes for the rest of your life.
Come, see who is downstairs.
- Who?
Take a wild guess
Is it a film star?
Abhimanyu Singh!
You are kidding!
What!
Go see for yourself. Bro
is here to meet someone.
He maybe your 'brother'!
But who is he here for?
Come! Let us see!
Let us go
She is a sly one.. did not
tell anyone she is his fianc?e..
Coach has given her
leave till tomorrow morning..
Wow!
Leave till tomorrow morning.
Why, whatever will
they do all night long?
It is confirmed.
They are making me the Vice Captain.
Bullshit!
Really? I do not believe this!
I knew it. How long will
these clowns hold out.
Vice Captain of the
lndian frikkin cricket team!
Now you watch how l
teach all these seniors.
You see who rules this team now!
Get out of the way everyone!
It is my turn now.
Why do you not quit all this now?
Quit what?
Your silly stick & ball game
Come on baby, forget about it now.
Forget about it and do what?
Do what? Live it up!
Be with me! Travel
the world with me.
Live life king-size, with the King.
As the wife of the Vice
Captain of the lndian Cricket team!
Wife?
Oh, forgot to tell you.
Had a chat with your dad
over drinks yesterday.
I told him I am all for it.
He said we do not want
to delay it anymore.
So it is all fixed.
Anyway, my career is all set.
And what about my career?
What?
What about my career?
What career?
Abhi, I am in the lndian hockey team
Yeah but that is not a career,
Preeti. That is just a stupid game.
So is cricket
Preeti! I know you like to think of
your little dribbling and
stick work as a big thing.
But let us face it
- it is not exactly cricket is it?
Look at her enjoying herself!
Damn it, let us go play.
Come on, we have been rotting on
this same bench for the last 7 days.
We are players, not
Association members who sit around.
Come on. Come on!
I will show him my game!
If he is not forced to
make me a forward again,
my name is not Bindia Naik.
Or his is not Tuglaq.
Sorry sir, it will not
happen again. We are sorry.
Sorry
Ok, you can play center half.
Thank God sir. The
situation is under control now.
No, Krishnaji. It is just
about to go out of control.
Right! Left! Right! Left!
Faster! Faster! Faster!
Run faster! Move.
Faster! Faster! Run faster!
I mean FAST!
Right, left, right! To the ball!
Ok, let's go! Right! Left!
Pass the ball! Make a pass! Pass,
pass, pass, pass, pass, pass PASS!
Thank you.
Trap and pass! Move the
ball ahead! Come on, move it!
No player will keep the
ball for more than 5 seconds.
Can you count? 5-4-3-2-1!
Faster! Faster! Run faster!
I mean FAST! Quick, quick!
Faster, faster,
What is your problem? Do you not see
the ball, or are you afraid of it?
Want to practice with a
tennis ball for a few days?
Left, right, left!
Leave the ball, sit!
Go, right!
Go to hell!
Trap, look and pass! Stop,
look and move it ahead..
Do not move yourself forward.
Move the ball forward!
Do one thing pick up the ball.
PlCK lT UP! Put it in
your pocket and go home.
Go play on the Chandigarh team
from tomorrow. No need to play here.
And you! What are
you so angry about?
Raise your game first
and then raise your voice.
Once more if I hear you shout out,
you will be out!
Hey you! Why are
you the center half?
Because you are the senior
most player in the team.
Your job is not to push the
forward line but to teach them.
And one more thing.
There can only be one
bully in every team.
And for this team, it is me.
You! Call this a pass?
You are only good enough to
plough fields in your village.
Forget about hockey!
And why are you standing around?
Go get the ball!
Right, left, right,
Ieft, right, left! Relax!
Nethra!
Krishnaji! Give her water
and take her out! Quickly!
So! You are lndia's best players!
You will go to the
World Championship! Hah!
To raise lndia's flag!
The Association is right.
How will this lot ever play hockey!
They cannot play as
one team. How the hell..
..will they ever win
a World Championship!
What are you staring at?
She is unconscious not dead!
Krishnaji! Take her away! Out!
I had said it on the first day.
This team needs only those
who first play for lndia,
then for their team mates
and then if there is any
life left, for themselves.
Let's start again.
Right!
So! Did you see what happens when
you let the coach think he is God!
The blood will not stop.
I warned you guys.
Do you want to eat something?
Wake up at 4am, run for 20 km. And
on the field, he does not let us play.
What kind of a camp is this?
Does it hurt a lot?
Here! It hurts here.
He insulted us!
Hit with the ball!
He knows damn well you
cannot speak English.
But you have to learn it!
What you have not learnt in your
whole life, learn it in a day!
Else get out of the team.
Hey, he cannot throw you out!
Do not worry, I will teach you.
How can he cut you out of the team?
What do you say Aliya?
No freedom to eat, to move around
and when we play, he insults us.
This is not a primary school. Each
girl is a National level player.
A champion from her state
- that is why she is here.
If there is any failure
amongst us, It is him.
Sold his team out in the World Cup!
Was thrown out of
the team, the country.
What else can I say? I am
ashamed to say any more.
Does it hurt?
I have a spray..
How is Nethra?
OK. The doctor says she will be
back to practice in a couple of days.
Practice? Have you lost it?
From now on, there
will be no practice!
There will be no
practice from tomorrow!
Look here..
You look here! We know you like him
but you should also realise
that the team is on this side.
It is time you choose
which side you're on.
Yes.
Definitely.
I have thought about it.
Now only the Association can
decide how this team should run.
The way teams have
always run in this country.
Or the way Tuglaq wants it!
Let us sign this.
Now, it is either
the Coach or our team.
Sign this, Gul!
Sir..
Hmmm? Have some..
Wasn't that too much?
They are girls after all.
How much can you push them?
If you look for the
strength of boys..
I am not looking for strength.
I am looking for team spirit.
You do not need strength to make
a team. You need team spirit.
But sir, at this rate, you
will become their enemy.
If by making me an enemy
they can become a team,
then it is a small
price to pay, Krishnaji.
Why are you not on the field?
What is the matter?
The team does not want
to practice with you.
What rubbish!
We want a new coach.
I will give you one -
Why Krishnaji? Why will you hit us?
We are not the ones
who sold our country!
Quiet!
- Sir!
7 years.
After 7 years I came back to hockey,
with the belief that this time
I will beat the one thing that
defeated my team once and for all.
But today, once again,
I have lost to it.
You do not have a problem with me.
You have a problem
with the fact that instead of
making you play against each other,
I am forcing you to
play with one another.
Because I have forced
you to think about..
..your team before you
think about yourself.
Forced you to play for lndia
before you play for your own state.
Fine. You have won. I have lost.
But I am not sorry loosing to you.
I am sorry I have
lost to my country.
Which even after taking my blood,
sweat, my love,..
..my life, does not believe
that I played for it once.
And I will play for it all my life.
I resign as the coach of this team.
Please, just think it over, Sir.
You have worked so hard.
Today is my last day in this camp.
Before I leave, I am
taking the staff out for lunch.
You are welcome to
join us if you wish.
No obligations.
Hi beautiful! Come on,
join us babes! Hey come on!
She's red hot ya! Hey baby, hey!
Harassing girls, are you? Try it!
Hey! Hey, how..
Balbir!
Hit him!
Do not let him go!
Not from behind. Have guts
to attack from the front.
You see, in hockey
there are no cowards.
Is this a team or an army of devils?
I told you, Krishnaji.
It is not strength, but
spirit that makes a team.
For the first time, l
have seen team spirit.
Sir.. I was just..
just trying to say that..
I mean.. Iet
sleeping dogs lie.. I mean..
Hey tell him!
Sir what she means.. what we all
Tomorrow morning, 5 am sharp.
I want everyone on the field.
Chak De! India (Go lndia!)
Y
Come, come, come.
We will run two
more kilometers today.
Come on guys!
Do something, do something
My veins are bursting
O please do something
Do something, do something
For talk and sermons bite the dust
It is time to do something
Be stubborn if that is what it takes
Do or die
- all is at stake!
Chak De! India (Go lndia!)
In the fighting kite,
in the riot of might
In the games and the fair,
in the bumpy trains so bare
In the sweetness of sugarcane,
in the clothes of the rich or vain
Seek and you will find,
heat that bricks bind
A colour has emerged, and
it is spreading converged
This colour of the reign,
is embedded in your veins
Stand immovable, invincible,
obstinate in times of trouble
Scraped and scarred,
move on even if marred
Be stubborn if that is what it takes
Do or die
- all is at stake!
Chak De! India (Go lndia!)
How can you go?
Why?
Because we are getting married!
What?
You can not go on the 25th, we
are getting married on the 2nd
What?
I have fixed the dates after
discussing it with your parents
And me? Do you not need
to discuss this with me?
What is the point of discussing it?
You want to get
married to me, do you not?
But, not like this! I need time.
What for?
I am playing for
the World Cup, Abhi!
Have you gone insane?
You want to postpone our
wedding for the World Cup?
What if it was your World cup?
That is a totally different.
It is the Cricket World cup.
It is really important.
This is really important.. for me
More important than our marriage?
I have to go. Good night!
Go. Go play the World cup..
If you loose you
will become my wife.
If you win, you
will become my wife..
It is not like when you come back,
the whole country
will remember your name.
One thing I promise
you Mr. Abhimanyu..
This will definitely happen.
The team is shaping up well, sir.
The captain of this
team will be Vidya.
Congratulations, Vidya!
Give it a break.
I have nothing to say to you.
For the first time something
good is happening. Take part in it.
You already did!
The way Bindia is using her brain..
Do you think it is right
for her to be on the team?
I do not know Krishnaji..
but it is also not right..
..to keep the most
experienced player off the team.
I do not think we can..
deal with her
We cannot win without her either.
Is this not your
World Cup silver medal?
What are you doing with it?
Trying to scrub it into gold.
If I ever need to sell
it in the flea market,
at least I will get a good price.
Mr. Kabir, it is best if you
forget about the World Cup.
And tell these girls as well.
The ones who you have
given such high hopes too.
But our deal was to train
this team for the World Cup.
It was not like we signed on a legal
document you cannot hold us up to it.
You discussed it in
front of me, Mr. Tripathi.
We will discuss it in
front of you once more.
Look, on one hand,
there is the lndian men's team
which at least gets a bronze medal.
And on the other, there
is this team of misfits.
But this team is
ready for the World Cup!
Tomorrow if they are ready for
the moon, we should send them? Huh?
This team can not go the World Cup.
It is decided.
Be honest. Tell us
you are taking money..
..from the Women's team
to give to the Men's team.
You guys are athletes.
Why do you want to get involved
in things that do not concern you?
Shall we?
But Mr. Tripathi!
Let us have a match.
What?
Yes. Let us have a match.
Between my team and your team.
You mean Men's
team v/s Women's team?
I mean between my
team and your team.
If we loose, we loose. But
if we win, then - World Cup.
Think about what you
are saying, Mr. Kabir.
Do not make Pandavas' (lndian
mythological characters) bet
You will be left standing naked.
It has already happened to you once.
All right. Day after morning.
But we need time to train!
Day after
- yes or no?
Mr. Tripathi..
Day after morning. We
will meet on the field.
Even your team needs to practice
Come out..
Shit!
We will never win. And
by some chance, if we do..
Chance! Huh!
Imagine how many
goals we will loose by.
And once we lose,
it is over forever!
What have you done, sir?
We are like sitting ducks.
Ducks? I have belief in this team.
Does this team believe in itself?
Come on! Let us go.
Look, you are not
playing against these boys.
Come on, get ready! Hurry!
Do not think
- here let me have it.
Do not think you are
playing against 1 6 boys.
You are fighting
everyone in this country
who thinks girls can
never match up to men,
cannot hold a job as well as a man,
cannot make decisions like men..
You are fighting each
fool who has forgotten that
if a girl has given life to him,
she can do anything. Anything.
It is a huge match
perhaps bigger than you or me.
And that is why I should be
telling you play fearlessly,
play together, play
with all your might,
play like this, play like that..
but I will just say one thing
Chak De!
Do they know how to play?
Good morning, ladies & gentlemen!
Good morning sir!
But sir! That was a foul!
Very good! Well played!
Good job boys!
Come on! Come on girls! Well played!
Don't tire yourselves running!
Smaller passes!
Should we stop if
you have had enough,..
..Mr. Kabir? Or do
you still want to play?
The match isn't over yet.
Your girls could not
even reach the boys' half.
You cannot expect
anything from them.
Mr. Yadav what..
Well, he's right Krishnaji.
We always said it - These are
good old fashioned lndian girls -
How will they run around
in shorts and mini - skirts?
Yes, Mr. Yadav,
tell them like it is.
What can you do? You will fall
flat on your faces, you'll see!
Oh, Mr. Yadav! You have fallen!
Will you get up by yourself?
Or should I ask the
girls to give you a hand?
Oye!
Chak De!
Attack, girls!
Yes!
Go Komal!
They played well! Good defence!
Good job! Well played girls!
Should we (send them) sir?
Send? Where? Oh, this?
Yes.. send them
Yes! Kabir! World Championship!
Y
When could I imagined
that this would happen
When did I ever believe, but
it has, it has indeed happened
Pinch me, I am not in my senses
Hold my feet, they
are soaring in the air
Are my feet on the clouds,
or is this a land of illusion
Now it has taken off,
our boat has taken sail
It is the taste of
the sky, after eons
My trembling heart beats hard,
is it day or night?
You have finally been magnanimous,
God! Thank you!
Are my feet on the clouds,
or is this a land of illusion
Now it has taken off,
our boat has taken sail
The mates have embarked,
the paths are unknown
But we can do it, l
know there's a way
The dreams we saw blindfolded,
we live today
Are my feet on the clouds,
or is this a land of illusion
Now it has taken off,
our boat has taken sail
Greetings from Kapil Verma!
Welcome to Melbourne's State
Hockey and Netball Centre!
In the World Women's
Hockey Championship,
today lndia are playing 6
times World Champions Australia.
The teams are greeting each other -
Australia exudes the
confidence of World Champions..
The teams pay their
respects to their flags..
A deep sense of pride in the eyes
of Coach Kabir Khan and his team..
Excitement in the stands..
Teams are raring to go
and the match begins!
Australia has the ball.. Back pass!
A long scoop, straight
to lndia's 25 yard line..
Left the lndian defenders behind..
cross pass.. and GOAL!
And perhaps the fastest goal in the
history of the World Championship!
From the very first minute,
there's pressure on the lndian team..
It is alright!
Lots of time. Come on!
Coach Kabir trying
to bolster his team..
but one more strong attack
from Australia and goal!
Goal!
The witches kick! Hey,
that's not fair! Anyway..
India, Australia's goal.
Hey! That big moose kicked me hard,
did you not see that?
India, careful!
Balbir! Don't argue! Just play
Go get your eyes checked!
You need glasses!
Be careful! Australia's ball.
I'll show you!
Hey, that's completely wrong!
Totally unfair!
What is she saying?
Go back to your goal. - How go back to
your goal! Wrong decision is there!
Calm down!
- Wrong! Wrong!
Sir, what is she doing?
She will get a card!
If you open your mouth one more time,
you will be off. Go back to your goal!
You go back, you idiot!
A yellow card and the
way out for Balbir..
and a penalty corner for Australia..
could be dangerous for lndia
What a pig headed referee?
Is she a pig headed idiot or are
you? We are left with ten players now!
Krishnaji, give her water..
And penalty corner specialist Abernathy
has been waiting for this moment.
Push, trap, hit and goal!
A last ditch attempt to save
the match by Coach Kabir Khan..
Didi, where should I hit it?
Any where you please
Didi, please!
Don't ask me. Go ask your captain?
Seems a move is made between
senior Bindia Naik and Soimoi but..
some confusion between the players..
and once more Australia scores
And in the second half, Australia
- 5, lndia - 0
Indian centre forward
Preeti Sabarwal on attack..
with her is Right in Komal
Chautala.. - Preeti! Pass!
both playing the World
Championship for the first time..
proving a challenge for Australia..
Preeti's off! Dodges one defender,
another one..
keeping the ball for so long..
Komal's ready.. but Preeti..
doesn't pass..
Komal pass!
What are you doing, Komal! Pass!
Pass Komal! No one on this side!
A precious
opportunity lost because of..
..the lack of coordination
between the lndian forwards..
And the old lndian
attitude strikes again!
Good save, good save!
Yeah?
- They are playing defense.
Get the Coach to use
the Dutch tactic..
Ho! Ho!
A minor confusion.. Looks like Soimoi
does not understand the referee..
And one more penalty
corner for Australia.
Match over! Australia - 7, lndia -
0. A shameful defeat for lndia..
Well played! - How did you ever
make it to the World Championship?
Bindia!
Bindia.. What were you up to?
Me? Where?
What were you doing on the field?
Nothing
You are not going to play
any more in this Championship!
What's so special about her?
What?
Tell me, what does
she have that I don't?
Who?
Your captain, Sir.
If we have to get down to it,
why don't we just spell it out?
Neither of us is naive here
- neither you, nor me..
I can do all that she is
doing to be a captain..
And much more..
Now tell me, why
can I not be captain?
You have just
answered your question.
A team that is not fit to play
against European high schools.
And you wish to redeem your
name by coaching such a team.
..Association denounced Kabir Khan
- declared he did his country wrong.
These kind of people should have moved
to Pakistan during the partition.
Someone has sold out?
Papa, papa, I want to see
what a traitor looks like.
Down with Kabir Khan!
Allah.. bring me strength
and bring victory closer
..it is almost certain that lndia
will be out of the Championship.
There is one chance of survival -
defeating England in tomorrow's match.
But looking at lndia's
form it is highly unlikely.
Very good! Pass to Aliya!
Come here! Come here everyone! OK!
Now we are making the
same mistakes again. Water..
So, set piece A6
- From Balbir to Rani,..
..Rani to Molly, Molly
to Gul, Gul to Preeti,
Preeti to Komal, from
Komal back to Preeti,..
..from Preeti to Komal
again and Komal to goal..
Set-piece A6
- does everyone remember?
Yes sir!
- Good! Repeat it!
Preeti to Komal, Komal to Preeti,
from Preeti to Gul to Komal.. uh..
That's B6
I will beat the crap out of
anyone who cannot remember.
Balbir..If you do not
control your temper,..
..the situation can
get out of control. OK?
Yes sir. - If it becomes a team
of ten again, there is no hope.
Is there anything left, now?
- Plenty..
Ok, let's begin all
over again. Everybody!..
..20 minutes more!
Concentrate on defense! Go!
Full power! Play
with all you've got!
Greetings and welcome to
the World Championship..
..in Melbourne where England is
playing in Group A for 2 points,
but lndia is fighting to
stay in the Championship.
Good! Let's go!
The UK Coach has promised to
beat lndia by..
..even more goals than Australia.
Maybe that is why there are
not too many spectators around.
UK has gone on the attack immediately
lndian players struggling..
Half press forward!
Komal Chautala blocks..
Great job Komal!
Balbir, Soimoi! No6
Today lndia seem to
have better coordination..
..but the UK
forwards attack once more -
And lndia saves!
- Yes! Good!
Hey!
Foul!
Balbir!
Keep calm!
I got hurt here! Ok, fine,
guess it's a part of the game
That's rubbish!
Good Balbir!
Thank God, she didn't hit her!
20 minutes left in the first half
- England gets a..
..penalty corner.. could
be dangerous for lndia.
Go!
And lndia has made no mistakes.
I am confused. Which
one of them is Didi?
Chak De!
Second half
- lndia has not given up any goals.
But hasn't scored any either.
Preeti come on! Fall back!
On the double!
Save!
Well done! Well done Gunjan!
Last 3 minutes of the match..
both teams goalless.
England is trying hard to score..
But lndian defender Soimoi has the
ball.. Soimoi to Mary.. to Preeti.
Pick it up! Pick it up!
Preeti I'm free! Pass!
Pass Preeti..
And goal! Unbelievable!!!
Wow! What a goal, Sir!
She made the British..
..forget their English!
Great job Preeti!
Jesus! Bloody hell!
What was she doing?
Last 20 seconds of the match..
And with this final hooter,
the unexpected has happened!..
..India has defeated UK by 1-0
Managing to stay in the Championship..
and get a new lease of life!
Well played!
- Congratulations!
Well played! Well done!
It's a good thing..
..you controlled
your temper, Balbir!
Let's go girls! Come on!
The future may be
unclear but for now,..
..India has retained itself
in the World Championship.
India v/s Spain!
Do something, do something
My veins are bursting
O please do something
A superb goal by Komal Chautala!
Do something, do something
For talks and sermons bite the dust
It is time to do something
Be stubborn if that is what it takes
Do or die, all is at stake
Chak De!
Chak de! Ho Chak
de lndia!(Go lndia!)
Keep it up!
Didi, can I get some water?
Shall I give you a kick instead?
Give the battle cry of war
and give it again and again..
Don't lag behind in
the race, my friend,
Iet them pull you
back as much as they can
Won't budge an inch. Bull headed,
you think? Yes I am!
The scraping, the squeazing,
grating of life, be done with it!
Preeti has sprinted ahead. Buck up
Komal, Get even in the next match.
Do or die, all is at stake
Chak de! Ho Chak
de lndia!(Go lndia!)
Surprising everyone
with its sudden rise,
Kabir Khan's team is
playing a match that..
..may stop it in
its tracks tomorrow.
If lndia wins, It enters
the semi finals and if..
..it loses, it is
out of the World Cup.
Tomorrow lndia plays Argentina,
a team well known..
..for its rough play
and injuring opponents.
Hey! It is a foul!
One second! She's hurt!
Krishnaji, go to her!
Gul are you alright?
Water! Here drink this!
Stretch, stretch..
From this moment on, I don't
want to see the ball in our half.
Balbir, you play your game.
I'll...I'll beat these girls!
So beat them. If they hit one of us,
you hit 4. If they hit 4, you hit 8.
Rough them so bad that they're scared
of picking up a hockey stick again.
Sir - Don't let them dare come
in the way of Preeti, Komal, Nethra.
Attack them. Don't stop
attacking them till they break.
Or you break!
Forward up!
Yes!
Chak de!
Yes! Yes!
The lndian team coached by
Kabir Khan has reached..
..the semi finals
of the Championship.
We are in the semi finals!
Did you ever doubt it?
But now lndia will be up
against South Korea..
..a team that hasn't let a
single team reach its goal.
Man to man marking?
Ya. A player behind each player.
This is Korea's game.
We will be paralysed by this game,
leave alone scoring goals.
Who can crack this kind of game?
There is one player.
You were right. You do have
something that she just doesn't.
And that no other
girl on this team has.
Take this.
Why?
Because right now lndia needs
its most experienced player.
Only you know how to
break man to man marking.
The match is about to begin. Go.
Go and break it.
As expected, Korea's
man to man marking..
..has paralysed
the lndian forwards..
Aliya Bose, Preeti Sabarwal, Komal
Chautala - no player can move an inch..
Mary!
Substitution! No.5
Bindia Naik on field..
There's a sudden shift..the game
seems to be changing direction..
Defenders Bindia Naik and
Gunjan Lakhani are on attack -
They are playing in a unique
style..Korean players are confused..
And goal!
Chak de!
Yes!
We won!
India has reached the
World Championship Finals!
By the sound in this stadium,
you can guess what..
..the state of the
lndian team must be.
And what state its Coach must be in..
who couple of months ago was stopped
from bringing his team
to the Championship.
Who could have guessed that one of
the world's best center forwards
would score such a
smashing goal in World hockey
without even lifting a hockey
stick or entering the field..
Hi Bill!
- Well played!
You are definitely
going to be the Highest..
..Scorer of the World Championship.
But you have got competition. See!
8 goals. Komal's ahead once more
You idiots! You have your own
World Championship going on.
Hello.. Sukhlalji! Speak up!
Amazing Krishnaji! These devils
have been raising quite a hell!
With your blessings, Sukhlalji
The travelling
theatre had come by, didi..
I made it very clear
to them that this is..
..the lndian women
hockey team's ground.
It is waiting for its team. I'm
not going to give it out to anyone..
Now there will only be
hockey practise here.
Hello, here! Speak here! Oof!
Hello! I am really missing
your curd rice, Sukhlalji.
If you guys win the World Cup, child
I will make curd rice
for you all my life.
Don't lose now. Don't lose.
We will not, Mr. Sukhlal. We will
lose our lives, but not the game.
I was your third colour once
Your tune was the rhythm of my life
You were my master,
you were my pride
My master, my life is yours to take
What are you doing here, sir?
Look. It is the first time I've seen
a foreigner raise the lndian flag.
We have reached the final.
Is it a dream?
What do you think?
It must be a dream.
It is your dream, isn't it?
My master, my life is yours to take
Thank you very much
for being here..
..Tonight is the night for an
official reception for the finalists.
The Federation of lnternational Hockey
is holding a dinner in their honour.
So that tonight they can
forget about winning or losing
and just celebrate that they are
the two best teams in the world.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the six times..
..World Cup champions,
the team from Australia.
Oh.. Sorry! Best of luck!
Yes, yes..Happy Diwali!
What's she saying?
She's saying..watch out for the
fireworks tomorrow - Excuse me!
Do we have to wear this?
It is a pain..
Do you care for a drink?
- No, thank you
What is it Nethra?
Nothing..
What is it?
- What do you mean?
I mean why did you call me here?
Me? You're the one who called me
Did a mad dog bite me?
No way I would call you!
I have called you.
You.. but why sir?
To tell you that tomorrow we
are going to lose the finals.
What? Why?
Why?
Because tomorrow, two of our players
are going to play for Australia.
No, no, sir, it is not like that..
What do you think? That the
Australian coach and team are blind?
You think they haven't
figured out that lndia's..
..main forwards do
not pass to each other?
You think they will not
take advantage of this fact?
Sir, whatever I do is for the team..
Komal, you cannot fool me, at
least do not try and fool yourself.
You fought with you father,
mother, brother,..
..your village to come
here and play hockey,.
But now you are playing at
something else. Even you know this.
Tell her sir. She's the
one who started it all.
And you are the one who
will finish it tomorrow?
Is that the plan?
And you, Preeti Sabarwal,
Chandigarh Captain..
You lost your senses
to join this team..
But now you have
lost all sense.. Why?
Neither of you is a child.
You know very well
that if you do not play..
..together for the
same side tomorrow,
we will never win the finals.
Once upon a time, an
lndian team had lost a final.
You don't know what it is
like to bear that cross..
But when you do, it
will be too heavy to bear.
Neither of you has the
strength to bear it.
Nobody has the strength to bear it!
You both know what the
problem between you two is.
All I know is that whether you
both play on our side or not,
the rest of my team will
play together against Australia.
And if necessary
against both of you as well.
The ball is in your court.
Do you want to play with
your team or against it.
Whatever happens, I will
score the most goals..
What are you trying to prove?
I am not trying to
prove anything, Komal.
I just want to show a foolish
boy what a woman is capable of.
I will score the most goals,
no matter what happens.
I want to see you try and do it.
Y
And tonight is the night that
everybody has been waiting for.
The night of the Women's
Hockey World Championship finals.
A match that is
completely unexpected.
Because tonight we have current
and 6 times World Champions Australia
playing against lndia - a team
that has risen like a juggernaut.
A team that has won the
hearts of many with its..
..dazzling display of
determination and skill.
But winning hearts and winning the
World Cup are two different things.
And this is the ordeal by
fire of Coach Kabir Khan's team.
By what strategy,
what skill, what magic
will this team from lndia beat the
game of the six times World champions..
Girls!
Seventy minutes.
Seventy minutes is all you have.
Perhaps the most important
seventy minutes of your life.
Today, whether you
play very well or badly,
you will always remember these seventy
minutes for the rest of your life.
Today I won't tell you how to play.
All I will say is:
Go! And play for all you're
worth in these seventy minutes.
Because in the days to come
whether life goes well for you or not,
whether you have
something to call your..
..own or not,
whether you win or lose,
these seventy
minutes are something..
..that nobody can
ever take away from you.
Nobody.
So I thought,
I will not tell you how
to play today's match.
You will. By playing it.
Because I know that if
in these seventy minutes,
each player of this team plays
the best hockey of her life,
then not even God can take
away your seventy minutes.
So go!
Go and steal those seventy minutes
- from yourself.
From your life. From God.
From anyone who did not
have any faith in you..
Go and steal your seventy minutes.
Chak De!
Go Aussies!
Come on girls!
Towards the left side!
In the very first minute,
lndia has shown that
it will not play this
match as an underdog team.
Just how important this goal
was for the team's psyche,
is reflected in the look of
pride on Coach Kabir Khan's face.
What the hell just happened?
They have..
..changed something.
Find out what it is.
Australia's counter attack -
And save!
Australia is not a team to
take things lying down..
and its the attack could
be a danger to lndia..
Gunjan to Komal..
Komal pass!
Nice dodge..
Komal! Pass to Preeti! Pass!
Preeti Sabarwal has scored
8 goals in the tournament,
Half time
And somehow lndia has managed
to hold on to its advantage.
But the second half has always
been Australia's strong point.
Australia's strong attack..
India under pressure..
Reverse hit..
and goal!
A pass..
- Move with them!
Once more, Australia on attack..
Push.. and goal!
India-1, Australia-2.
Only a few minutes
left and Australia's..
..strategy is to not
let go of the ball..
and kill lndia's chances
of scoring an equaliser..
Australia has the ball..
but lndia has snatched it!
Go Komal!
Come out! She won't pass!
Preeti!
Show the idiot!
Thank you!
Move back!
Emily! Get out there!
Come on! There is still time!
And end of extra time..
smiles in the lndian camp
Because now they will face the
Australian team in a tie breaker..
For lndia it means a genuine
chance to win this tournament.
Because now, the winner will be
decided by a penalty shoot out.
Each team will have a chance
of hitting 5 penalty strokes..
And the team with the most goals
will become the World Champion!
Didi, now everything is up to you.
Save us Vidya didi!
Preeti, Aliya, Bindia, Mary,
Nethra.. Come! Quick! Come here girls!
You girls are taking the penalty.
Remember one thing - don't attack
the goal but the goalkeeper's mind.
You will win the goal automatically.
We can win it. Come
on girls! Well done!
Sir, if Komal can take my stroke..
Komal! Quick!
Preeti wants you to take her stroke.
Alright, let's get this going!
Come on everyone! All the best!
Australia-2, lndia-2.
India's first striker is right
out Nethra Reddy from Andhra
Come on Nethra!
Goalie ready?
Yeah!
Striker ready?
And lndia has
wasted its first chance.
Every missed
stroke can prove costly.
Now it is Australia's turn.
Defending the..
..Indian goal is Vidya Sharma,
lndia's captain
Australia's No. 1 Sarah Abernathy.
Goalie ready?
Ready!
Striker ready?
And goal! A swift ground shot
that can leave any goalie stumped.
India-2, Australia-3.
Aliya Bose..
Come on Aliya!
Another miss!
Opportunities wasted and
the Cup grows further away
Striker Sheryl Jones..
Goalie ready?
Striker ready?
And another goal!
Australia is growing stronger..
Now to stay in the game lndia
will have to stop every stroke..
..and convert every
stroke into a goal.
At this crucial moment,
we have Komal Chautala..
Centre forward from
Haryana and the team's right in.
Come on Komal! Just hit it!
Aussies!
A beautiful strike and goal!
India manages to save itself.
India-3, Australia-4
Vidya Sharma ready once more..
Rachael Taylor ready..
No room for mistakes..
And a great save!
India-3, Australia-4
There is still hope
for lndia, but to win,
it will have to convert the
next two strokes into goals.
India's next striker, penalty
shoot out specialist - Mary Ralte.
A great scoop and goal!
Making lndia on par with Australia..
But Australia has
two more strokes and..
..India, one.
- Come on Vidya didi! Save it
Australian striker Emily Jones.
India's last chance.. It is
imperative to score and that is why
experienced Bindia Naik
will take this stroke.
Come on Bindia didi!
Maybe this is what
they call experience!
We come now to the last
stroke of the penalty shoot out.
If Australia scores, the
shoot out will continue.
But if Vidya saves the goal, then
this lndian team will make history.
India-Pakistan
Just one penalty stroke between
lndia and the World Championship..
India is one goal behind Pakistan.
But Captain Kabir is
taking the stroke himself..
Why did you take the
penalty stroke yourself?
You do not know what it is
like to bear that cross..
She will hit on the left
- her stick is turned to the left.
But her foot is facing right
- She will hit right.
Left, no right, no left.. Oh my God!
She is going to hit
straight into the goal!
Vidya! Look at me!
Look at me, Vidya
My master
I was your third colour once
You were my master,
you were my pride
My master, my life is yours to take
And now Ladies & Gentlemen, we..
..present to you the new
World Champions, Team lndia..
Jaya Hind! (Hail lndia)
By becoming World Champions,
the lndian Women's hockey..
..team has made
every lndian's heart sing
And the man who gave lndia this
victory is none other than Kabir Khan,
one of Asia's best Center forwards.
The thrill of our victory
is singing in the blood..
..of thousands of
lndians waiting here
at the airport for the man
of the moment - Kabir Khan.
But he does not seem to be
here in this moment of glory..
Where is Kabir Khan?
What do ex - players
have to say about the man..
..who returned to
the game after 7 years?
As long as players
like Kabir Khan exist,..
..Indian hockey can
hold its head high.
Brother Khan has proved that
there is no greater motivation..
.. than playing for your flag
Kabir Khan - the spirit of lndia!
Kabir Khan - the pride of lndia!
The credit of winning
this trophy, is being..
..given to the team's coach
- Kabir Khan
And what does the man on
the street have to say?
There can be no one more
respected than the man..
..who raised the
status of our National game.
He makes you feel proud
to be an lndian. -..
..Kabir Khan has showed us
all who a true lndian is
Kabir Khan - the spirit of lndia!
Kabir Khan - the pride of lndia!
TRAlTOR
Chak de! Chak de lndia!(Go lndia!)
Chak de!
O Chak de!
I was your third colour once
Your tune was the rhythm of my life
You were my master,
you were my pride
My master, my life is yours to take
So Preeti has no clue that
you are going to propose..
..to her before the entire country?
No, she has no idea.
What if she says no?
Preeti.. will you marry me?
Preeti, tell us, will
you marry Abhimanyu?
No
She's only joking. Move!
What was that?
The truth.
Where are you going?
To my team.
But what about us Preeti?
You and me?
Us? We never existed Abhi..
it was only you..
But now even I exist. I
don't need to be your wife.
Have a good life, and learn
some sportsman spirit if you can
Preeti has refused.
What is your plan now?
This is for you.
How are you mum? How are you dad?
I just want to say one thing Komal.
If I ever stop you from playing again,
just give me a couple of
whacks with this very stick.
No dad!
No, Komal. If anyone
else's father stops..
..her from playing,
whack him as well!
When his daughter
makes a name all..
..over the world, he
will forget everything.
Dad!
Madam!
Madam?
- Mr. Sukhlal!
Call us an army of devils,
Mr. Sukhlal.
Now that the rest of the
world calls us by that name,..
..why are you shying away from it?
What do you want 400 rupees for?
Just because you
brought me to the airport,..
..you can't charge
me whatever you wish!
Don't get so angry!
You are going to..
..self destruct with
anger one of these days!
Here, drink some water! Be calm!
And brother, please
don't charge us extra.
Come along peacefully now. You won't
get anywhere by having such a temper.
Congrats Vidya..
Thank you!
Come on, everyone is
waiting for you, especially Dad.
He says that his daughter-in-law
has made him really proud.