I thought this time
you'd be captured...
or that I'd lose you.
To whom?
Roma?
The disc which you gave the police?
It's a fake.
There was nothing in it.
Don't worry sweetheart...
now I rule over the Asian underworld.
I am the King!
It's been five years since that day.
And I... Don... rule
over the Asian drug trade.
The King.
Now my target is Europe.
The European drug
cartel is aware that...
I will takeover their market
by undercutting the prices.
Once I establish my
presence in Europe...
they will be out of business.
You speak to me like that again...
I will have my man
here slit your throat!
How dare you speak to me...
I speak the way I want.
Gentlemen...
gents...
This is Jimmy Coogan...
this cartel's boss.
He has brought everyone together...
so that they can set aside
their personal issues...
and decide about my fate.
All those in favour of killing Don?
Very well then!
I learnt about this
meeting a little late.
Every heart is beating fast
guess who is here
Don.
Jaruwan says he is grateful
to see you at his door again.
I'm not here for Jaruwan's door...
but for my consignment.
There goes your consignment.
Damn!
Now I'll have to drive the boat.
You aren't going anywhere, Don.
What brings about this hospitality?
Jimmy Coogan.
If we want to enter
the drug trade in Europe...
your life is our ticket.
And I guess he is
the ticket collector.
Hello big boy!
Any last wish?
Which restaurant in Bangkok
serves the best italian meal?
Meaning?
Well, after killing all of you,
I was hoping to go for
a good italian dinner.
You know, spaghetti bolognese,
a glass of red wine...
No? What?
Nobody likes italian?
What a shame!
See you around.
Hi!
Good evening.
- Hi Roma!
Hi!
Is this the file I'd asked for?
Yes.
Thanks.
It's him!
Any plans for tonight?
Nothing, why?
Because it's your birthday.
We should celebrate.
My birthday?
It's not my birthday today, Arjun.
I know.
Actually it's my birthday.
Oh my God! I'm so sorry...
I completely forgot!
Happy birthday, Arjun.
Thanks.
Just a second.
Hello...
I'll be right there.
Okay.
Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
You wanted to see me, sir?
Yes.
Have a seat.
Roma, do you know how long
I've served in this department?
37 years.
And in these 37 years
I've worked on 186 cases.
I've worked with very
brave and able officers.
But I know I'll miss you the most.
I'm sorry, sir?
I'm retiring, Roma.
What?
- Yes.
I wanted to tell you myself.
Come on, I'm not dying!
Come...
walk me to my car.
Sir... you could reconsider
your decision...
I don't want to.
What about Don?
He is the only one who got away!
He is your responsibility now.
And I know you will do it.
Good evening, Mr. Malik.
Don?
Put your hands up!
Up where I can see them.
Take it easy guys...
Down on your knees!
Really? I'm wearing white!
Shut up and get down on your knees.
I am very happy to see
you too, my wild cat.
Watch it!
Why is every one so angry?
Absolute immunity.
Drop all charges against me.
In Malaysia and in every country
where there's a warrant out for me.
You're a wanted man in every country!
How can I convince them all?
Really?
My mother would've been
so proud to hear that.
Proud?
She would've shot you herself!
Mr. Malik, you didn't know my mother.
Immunity or nothing!
Don, that's impossible!
I could probably save
you from the death penalty.
That's all!
The names of my clients, my
suppliers, every one involved...
for all that
information and evidence...
your offer is quite small, Mr. Malik.
Do something about it.
You know...
Make me an offer I can't refuse.
Okay.
If you don't cooperate with us...
believe me, along
with the prison term.
You'll also get the death penalty.
We all die, Mr. Malik.
Perhaps going to jail now
will be to my advantage.
I've waited far too
long for this day.
How does it feel... to be in prison?
Yeah, it's okay.
I'm unhappy with the
uniform colour but...
you don't look happy either.
What is it?
Your unexpected change of heart...
why are you putting on this act?
In this trade, when people covet
your death more than your life...
it's understood that
it's time to move on.
I figured I'd do something
good along the way but...
you people didn't give me a chance.
Very sad!
Had we given you that chance...
...you would've provided us
with the actual information...
Isn't that right?
Yeah, that's right.
I've lied to you once before...
and I didn't like it.
Shut up!
Your anger belies
what is in your heart.
What?
Roma, all that happened...
most of all I regret that...
I betrayed you.
For once, I wanted to
see you behind bars...
and now I have.
So goodbye, Don!
If you let me live, it
would be your biggest mistake.
Welcome to hell, Don.
Shower 14's drain is clogged.
Inform housekeeping.
Still upset?
I'm here to offer my friendship.
Let go of the past.
Let go of what?
I've been trapped in this cage
for five years thanks to you!
You're here because
of your ego, Vardhaan.
You don't know how to change
with time and circumstance.
Come on!
Get up!
If you know, then
what are you doing here?
I've come here for you, Vardhaan.
With an offer.
Well, I have an offer too.
How about I cut you to pieces
and feed you to the dogs in here?
That will benefit
neither you nor me, Vardhaan.
Only the dogs!
And I hate dogs!
I'm on death row, Vardhaan.
Whether you kill me now or
the law does in two weeks...
it's all the same.
Think, Vardhaan!
I could have surrendered
myself in any country...
yet I chose this one.
Though I know you are here,
eager to kill me.
Don!
Get out of here! All of you... out!
Go on...
I've come to help you escape.
In exchange for?
You'll know when the time is right.
No, no...
You will tell me right now!
All you need to do
right now is to decide...
...whether you want
to escape or not...
If this is another of your tricks...
Trust me, no tricks.
What do I have to do?
Good.
Two days later, the kitchen
supplies are going to be delivered.
You see him?
I want that janitor's duty.
- Okay, but...
- Do it, please.
Okay.
Now what?
Now we wait till Saturday.
Why? What happens on Saturday?
My attorney will pay me a visit.
Any more questions?
Yes, one more. May I ask?
No! Got your answer?
Good night.
Tonight we get out of here...
you ready?
- Oh yes!
Hey, you want to eat my food?
- You don't want?
- Hate fish!
Help!
He's dying, we need help here.
He's dying.
Thank you... My friend is very sick.
Hi...
Hi.
Hope I'm not disturbing you?
No, not at all.
Are those for me?
Yeah!
- Come in.
- Thanks.
Who is this?
My brother...
Ramesh.
Your brother...
where is he?
He's dead.
I am sorry.
That's okay.
Roma, remember you
once told me that...
you didn't want to think about
anything else till Don was arrested?
I do.
Well now the situation is...
that your phone is ringing yet again.
I am sorry... just a second...
Hello?
When?
Mesmerising and alluring.
Is his magic.
He whose eyes are stars.
He who is adorned with diamonds.
O heart, is it true?
O tell me.
He is here.
Hold on to your heart,
say it out loud.
Guess who it is.
He is here, once again
Don
I'm the mystery that no one gets.
My moves are above everyone else
I'm deeper than the ocean
never standing still
I'm denser than smoke
that never stops rising.
Hold on to your heart,
say it out loud.
Guess who it is.
He is here, once again
Don.
You aren't like smoke,
you are the flame.
If I come closer to you,
I'll burn and die.
If it's me you desire,
what else will you get?
Where do I go next,
even I don't have a clue.
Hold on to your heart,
say it out loud.
Guess who it is.
He is here, once again
Don
Don.
Here! Now this is
what I want from you.
There's a safety deposit box in
Zurich's Russian Commercial bank...
that belonged to your ex-boss, Boris.
He gave one of the set
of keys to you and...
...the other to your partner,
Singhania.
I have one key, thanks to you.
Come to think of it, if you had
taken the key from Singhania...
either before
poisoning him or even after...
it would've been to your advantage.
What's in that box?
You will know when we open it.
Where is the key, Vardhaan?
Zurich Airport.
Baggage locker number 1-3-5.
Combination lock number 5-4-8-1-7.
Got it.
Sweetheart, take the
next flight out to Zurich.
We'll see you there in two days.
You trust this girl completely?
Ayesha.
Sorry?
Ayesha, my name.
You were saying...
I was wondering if a girl
like you should do something...
...as dangerous as this!
I'm not just a pretty face,
Mr. Vardhaan.
I have a lot of other skills too.
See you in Zurich.
See ya.
Welcome to Zurich.
Know him?
Fabian Kohl.
President of the
German Deutsch Zentral Bank.
Influential, powerful
and respected by all.
Not many know that the
position he has occupied
for the past eight years...
was meant for someone else.
Who?
When the committee was setup to
choose the bank's president...
their first choice wasn't Kohl
but someone else.
James Werden.
So why didn't
the committee elect Werden?
Werden was killed in a car accident.
Kohl was behind that accident.
Guess who helped him?
Singhania?
That's right, Vardhaan!
But Kohl's messenger
wasn't aware that...
Singhania had recorded
their meeting in this tape.
Are we going to blackmail Kohl?
Yes and no.
I will blackmail Kohl...
through the bank's vice-president,
J. K. Diwan.
The vice-president
of DZB is an indian?
Well sweetheart, we are everywhere.
Why don't we deal with Kohl directly?
A minister is more concerned
about power than the king himself.
Kohl's messenger to
Singhania was none other than Diwan.
What's on your mind?
DZB has its currency
centre here in Berlin.
And that is where they print
the 50 and 100 Euro bills.
How much are we demanding?
I don't want the money!
Then what?
I want the printing plates!
Why on earth would
Diwan give us those plates?
Blackmail or no blackmail,
he will be finished, right?
Right!
Therefore it's important
to keep Fabian Kohl and
Diwan out of the picture.
But how?
With Diwan's help I'll
break into the currency centre.
Even if you do steal the plates,
it's no big deal to make new ones.
Of course it's no
big deal, sweetheart.
But new bills don't
make old ones worthless.
By the time the bank
replaces every old bill...
it will be years.
By then... how should I say this...
we will be...
billionaires!
Yes sir? - Roma, I just had
a word with German interpol.
Roma, I just had a word
with German interpol.
Vardhaan and Don
were spotted in Zurich.
Don and Vardhaan?
What were they doing together?
That's what we need to find out.
The car they were travelling in was
found at a lonely spot in Berlin...
Leave for Berlin immediately.
Right away, sir.
I have spoken with the Director
of intelligence, Klaus Wetland.
He is attending a
charity fundraiser tomorrow.
Right.
- He'll meet you there.
All the best.
Okay, sir. Thank you!
Excuse me, gentlemen...
Mr. Wetland?
Roma Bhagat.
Detective Malik may have
spoken to you about me.
Yes, he did.
This is Detective Jens Berkel.
He will be working the case with you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Pleased to meet you.
Detective Malik wanted me to
personally thank you for all your help.
Tell Malik, he owes me one.
Big time!
I will, sir.
Good evening ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you all for
being here with us today...
and putting your heart
ahead of your wallet.
Would you please join me
to welcome here today...
our esteemed guest of honour...
the Vice President of the DZB...
Mr. J.K. Diwan.
We raise our glasses to your health.
Cheers!
- Thank you ladies and gentlemen.
Enjoy the rest of the evening.
Thank you.
What happened?
That man...
I don't know why but I
feel like I know him.
Only if he didn't look like he did...
I am sure...
Find him, Arjun.
It is extremely important because
if it wasn't for your support...
we would never be
able to raise any funds.
Your phone is ringing.
- My phone?
- Yeah.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Congratulations on
the new phone, Diwan.
The inbox has a video clip...
which I'm sure
you'll find interesting.
I suggest you see it alone...
or it could prove embarrassing.
I kept my word.
Now it's your turn.
Once Mr. Werden is
elected as president...
it will be
difficult to make our move.
Don't worry, it will be done.
I told you it was interesting.
Apart from this clip,
I also have a bank document.
It states that a million
dollars were transferred...
...to Singhania's Swiss bank account.
- Singhania? I don't know any...
- Signed by you!
It is your good
fortune that I am a nice guy.
What I want is no big deal for you.
There's a black car outside,
registration number BIU 103.
You have...
two minutes.
Who are you?
Don?
No autographs please!
Damn it! Get the car!
You are crazy!
Do you have any idea
what you're asking for?
Of course.
I want the information that
will help me get inside...
...the underground vault of the DZB.
Listen... if you want money...
please just name your amount,
you will get it.
What you're asking for is impossible.
Would you and Fabian
Kohl rather spend..
...the rest of your lives in prison?
The details of what I
want are on the phone.
And Diwan...
you have 24 hours.
Roma! There!
I see you... my wild cat.
Don! If I'm caught with you...
- Relax Diwan.
It is not just
difficult to catch Don...
It's impossible!
Roma he's gone.
Are you alright?
Everybody okay?
Step aside sir.
Police business.
Step away from the car!
It's my car...
Get out! Please!
Got any money?
There he is.
Times up, sorry Roma.
See you soon.
Hello.
A moment please sir.
Sorry, I have to go.
This will destroy us.
Do what ever you have to do Diwan.
I don't want to hear about
that man, Don, ever again.
Is that understood?
So Mr. Diwan...
how can Abdul
Jabbar be of assistance?
I've heard you are a useful man.
You've heard right.
What's the job?
You know of Don, of course?
Hmm...
He is in Berlin right now.
I want you to trace him down and...
you know...
Why?
Why do you want him killed,
Mr. Diwan?
You need reason or money?
Now you're talking!
Five million Euro.
Half now and...
the rest when I hand you his head.
That's not necessary.
I want it done. As soon as possible!
Vardhaan!
Now do you see why
we never get along?
It would be better if
instead of watching cartoons...
you were thinking about
the security at the DZB.
Really?
Even if Diwan does help...
stealing those plates from
the DZB won't be a cakewalk.
I know, Vardhaan.
We need a computer hacker to control
the building's security system.
My remote, please.
Thank you!
But who?
All our useful men are
either in prison or...
on the FBI and interpol watch list.
Relax Vardhaan.
I know just the guy for this task.
Hey! Watch out!
Are you crazy?
Thank you for coming, Sameer.
Not at all, sir, please... I mean...
I had to see for myself that
it really was you who called.
I'm just a big fan, sir.
Sir?
That sounds too 'honest'.
Call me Don.
I have a job for you.
The security system
at the DZB's currency centre...
is controlled by a master computer.
I want you to hack
into this computer...
so that it's under my control.
I'm really sorry sir... Don.
I don't think I can do it.
Really?
Is it the Sameer Ali
who at 17 hacked into...
...the Tokyo Stock Exchange
and stole 1.4 million dollars?
And then donated it anonymously
to 'Save the Oceans' foundation.
There's nothing to
prove that I did it.
And if there's no evidence,
you aren't guilty.
Isn't that right?
Toucha!
You've been quite low
key the past three years.
I'm sure love has
something to do with it.
Actually tell me...
I like love stories.
She is a...
she's very special.
I am sure she is.
But so is your talent.
It would be a shame not to
put it to use at right time.
I can't.
I promised Yana that
I won't do anything illegal.
If there's no evidence,
you aren't guilty, right?
Hey...
where were you?
I had the interview, remember?
Oh yeah, how did it go?
I got the job, Yana.
That's great, Sam.
How are you feeling?
I feel good.
A little bit tired... but good.
He's not troubling
you too much, is he?
No. He's very well behaved.
Listen, Yana... I have to go
away for a couple of weeks.
There's a software expo in Amsterdam.
My love, it's not about
what you thinking it is...
I'm done with that life.
What's important to me
is you and the baby.
And I won't let
anything come between us.
At 1:18pm...
there are two people in the car.
Exactly 6 minutes later...
Here, look carefully.
Only one!
That means the passenger got off...
somewhere between
Tiergarten Strasse...
and 17th Juli Strasse.
Probably someone saw
him get out of the car.
Possible.
I'll talk to Berkel.
If there's a witness, we'll find him.
Hello...
Diwan, I'm sure you are
impressed by my punctuality.
So, what have you decided?
I'm willing to give
you what you want.
Good.
Tomorrow morning at 8,
outside the Berlin Cathedral.
Now what?
You will do exactly
as he wants you to.
What do you mean?
I can't give him that information!
Who said it has to be real?
By the time Don figures it out...
he will be dead, Mr. Diwan.
Hello?
A sightseeing bus is
approaching from your left.
I see it.
It will stop in front of you.
Come to the upper deck!
Let's go.
Everything you've asked
for is in these discs.
The blueprints of the currency
centre, security protocols and...
all codes to access the building.
What about the safe
containing the plates?
That safe is in the
underground vault.
It can only be opened by
a passkey which is in...
...the custody of the centre's
chief technician, Dr. Schneider.
Anything else?
Apart from the passkey,
the safe also requires...
Dr. Schneider's
fingerprints and voice match.
Look honestly,
you've got to trust me.
I'm telling you the truth.
You have beautiful eyes...
I trust you.
Keep this phone on you.
You have a reservation
at the Hotel de Rome.
Stay there until my next call.
But what about the
tape and documents?
Relax Diwan.
You'll get what you deserve.
Take the stairs.
Karl, you stay here.
Yeah.
You!!
Jabbar...
Don may not keep in
touch with his friends...
but he always checks on his enemies.
Someone is following you, sir.
Thanks, Sameer.
You want this, right?
No, Don.
I want to kill you.
We seem to have a problem.
You see...
I prefer to stay alive.
I think you'll have to
change your intention.
I suggest you join with me.
Whatever money Diwan
has promised you...
I'll give you three times more.
Think about it.
I don't want to put you...
under any pressure!
We found someone.
That's great!
Someone at the station
has identified Don's car.
And he also got a good look
at the person who got out.
Super! Where is he?
He's with the sketch artist.
Okay, let me know when
the sketch is complete.
Alright then.
Arjun!
Good job.
Thanks.
Don...
Including Jabbar in our
plan was a big mistake.
- Really?
- Really.
Have you forgotten that
he was hired to kill you?
Don's enemies should always
remember that Don never forgets.
As for my mistake...
this Abdul Jabbar will be
our ticket to escape from DZB.
Meaning?
I mean...
My plan to get us
out of the building...
will be a success only if...
we sacrifice Abdul
Jabbar and his goons.
Hello sweetheart!
Is he dead?
No, but you are!
Don? - Diwan, being
stupid enough to give me..
...blank discs is one thing...
but to hire assassins to kill me...
now that will be your downfall.
Please Don!
Don please...
please forgive me!
I'm sorry I screwed up.
I'll give you what you want.
Anything you ask of me!
Where is the information I want?
I have it with me, Don. It's with me.
Open the door.
Knock knock...
Sir, did you order room service?
Say 'yes'.
Yes, I...
I ordered room service.
But you...
Give her the information.
I have got it.
As a penalty you'll have to do
another thing for me, Diwan.
Wait...
Wait for my call.
That's him.
I've seen him before...
Where...
He was at the charity fund raiser...
his name... the guest of honour...
J. K. Diwan.
- That's it!
The Vice-President of the DZB.
Isn't it?
Yeah, you are right.
But... what was he
doing in the car with Don?
That's what we have to find out!
Okay!
This building has
state of the art security!
But obviously that's..
...not news to you.
Can you control
their computers or not?
Since you have put your trust
in me, I can't let you down.
I can control everything
except the underground vault.
What about the vault?
The vault isn't linked
to the master computer.
It's controls are in
the vault's enclosure.
The electric supply to the
vault is from a remote source.
Okay, we'll deal with that.
We'll figure the
vault from the inside.
Sir...
Yeah?
You see...
I don't mean to
demoralise anyone but...
we should realise
what we're up against.
As soon as you enter DZB is
the first security check point...
metal detectors, baggage x-ray.
A little ahead is the lobby
with CCTV cameras all over
and these are
monitored round the clock
by security guards in
the surveillance room.
There's a door to enter the vault...
which can be opened by a password.
The stairs inside lead
to the underground vault.
At the foot is a metal gate
manned by two security guards.
If you manage to get past them...
you'll reach the first
entrance to the printing chamber.
The security guards
will have the key to that.
The real problem lies ahead.
The main vault.
It is a sold steel chamber.
The emergency procedure is to lock
the door and smash the controls.
I mean, it's
impossible to get through it.
Fine, we'll blow it up.
No way, sir. Please don't
even think of that. - Why not?
Because there are two
things that will happen..
...If you try to blow it open.
First...
a chemical gas will
release into the chamber.
The gas isn't lethal but it can
knock a person out for 12 hours.
The second thing?
The vault door and the safe are
separated by a 20 foot long passage.
Now the floor of this passage is
installed with a security system...
that is activated by
even the slightest pressure.
What happens if the
system is activated?
I don't know, sir. But...
if I were you, I
wouldn't even breathe
Karl, Jabbar and his
team of five will wait here.
Two of you go up and wait for us
on the fifth floor by this window.
Jabbar...
explosives, guns,
ammunition are your domain.
There is no night.
And no day here.
Is it the darkness.
This is Dr. Schneider.
I want his finger prints.
The eyes are
betrayed but nobody knows.
Wonder what is here and isn't.
Good afternoon, this is
Detective Baruah from interpol.
May I speak with Dr.
Schneider please?
Good afternoon. Dr. Schneider?
Yes, I am Diedrich Schneider.
- Thank you.
There are many fake ones
like this out on the street.
Could I have the test
results by say, Tuesday?
You could get it by tomorrow, if
you want. - No, Tuesday is just fine.
Thank you, Dr. Schneider.
- Here you go.
Thank you so much.
The eyes are
betrayed but nobody knows
I am Diedrich Schneider.
Wonder what is here and isn't.
All an illusion.
The eyes are
betrayed but nobody knows.
Wonder what is here and isn't.
All an illusion
Don?
How do we escape from DZB?
In the basement...
is the service exit.
Ayesha will wait for
us in a police van.
We will escape in that van,
smooth and easy.
That's it?
Yeah, that's it...
You've thought of something better?
No?
I thought so.
Then I guess we'll have
to make do with my plan.
Hello...
Diwan...
tomorrow at 3...
behind the Paul Loebe house.
And please...
be on time, Diwan.
Nothing can stop me now!
I know Don.
He can sacrifice you...
me or anyone else for his own gain.
Is that so?
Then what are you doing with him?
I...
wanted to figure his plan.
I won't make the mistake
of trusting him again.
And quite frankly Jabbar...
neither should you.
Why not?
Don's exit plan says...
you won't get out alive.
He won't leave this place alive!
Jabbar, calm down.
Not now, Jabbar.
Once we have the plates.
I must say Don's plan is pretty good.
Imagine, once we have the plates...
it will be raining money!
What about Don?
By the time the cops
find Don's corpse...
we would've escaped
through the service exit.
That's it.
Hey.
Hey... how are you?
I'm good babe. Good.
Just miss you.
I miss you too.
They're working you hard...
you sound tired...
Just a few more
days and I'll be back.
I'm really proud of you, Sam.
You know I'm doing
this for us, right?
I Love you.
Please take care of yourself.
Call me, alright?
The sketch does look
like J.K. Diwan but...
it is also a fact that we are
relying only on one man's memory.
I know sir...
but I think he is right.
Alright, fix an appointment with him.
Thank you, sir.
Roma...
- Yes sir?
Do remember that J.K. Diwan
is a very important person.
So, word your questions delicately.
I understand, sir.
Hello?
Sorry you had to wait
but I need to reschedule our meeting.
Go to DZB and wait for my call.
Hello.
- How was the drive?
Lots of traffic but it was fine.
I'm sorry.
Hello DZB.
Now what?
Now, we record.
Good Morning Mr. Diwan.
Here we go!
Sameer, can you hear me?
Yes, Don! Loud and clear.
Cameras... now!
Copy that.
I'm switching the live
video with the recording.
Did you see that? - Now they
will see what we show them.
What's going on?
Did you see that?
Must be a glitch!
Good day!
Hello.
- Good afternoon, sir.
I'm here for my appointment
with Dr. Schneider, please.
He is expecting you.
Good day! Interpol.
Oh shit!
Yes?
- Whatever you do, don't turn around.
Who is it?
Interpol officers Roma and Malik...
get out of there!
Thank you.
He will see you now
on the fourth floor.
Thank you very much.
Good day!
Yes, Patricia?
- Good afternoon, sir.
There are some officers here
from the interpol to meet you.
Send them up please... in 15 minutes.
I have the results of the analysis..
...on the
counterfeit bill you gave me.
Altogether...
there are 7 points which
confirm that it is a fake.
If you see the bluring
in the corner of the ink.
The third point which clearly
confirms that we are holding...
...a fake note in our hands...
is the microprint.
You see here the real one...
here's the fake one.
In the real note the microprint...
You'll come across a
ladder to your left.
Above that is the
elevator shaft ventilation duct.
Excuse me...
Mr. Diwan will meet you now.
I hope it crashes after I get off!
Bye.
Package 1 in position.
Sam, stop the
elevator when I tell you to.
Now!
Sir button...
The doorman at your
apartment block told us that...
on the 15th you left your
apartment at 11 in the morning...
and returned at half past two.
Is that right?
The 15th...
let me see...
Victor, where were we on the 15th?
Mrs. Bergman's fundraiser, sir.
And what time did we return home?
1:30 pm, sir.
Thank you.
I think the doorman's
memory is off by an hour.
Victor maintains a
record of my every activity.
And if he is saying I came home
at 1:30, then that's the truth.
Of course.
Thank you. - No, not at all.
You are most welcome.
If I can help you in any way...
please don't hesitate in
getting touch with me.
As you can see here and on
this fake one and as you see...
it is the less obvious point...
if it comes to faking a note.
Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Boom!
There has been an explosion!
We have to get you
out right now, sir!
Lock the vault immediately.
No idea where it came from...
Shut up!
Let me make some calls and
find out what's going on.
It's on the 5th floor.
All people must leave the building.
Come on go.
Don't worry it's okay.
Get in there! Get in there!
Go! Go!
Don't worry!
Hey! What are you doing?
What's happening?
I'll check with the centre.
Why are the gates being shut?
Let's go.
Okay.
Open the gate.
We are in the vault.
Get the hostages!
Sam, it's too bright in here.
Do something, will you?
Copy that.
Emergency lights activated.
You don't understand!
I am answerable to the
German government and its people.
Please, I must stay.
Hello?
Good evening, Mr. Malik.
Don?
It's Don!
I'd like to speak with Roma, please.
How do you know...
Oh my God!
God won't come here, Mr. Malik.
He is in the building.
Let me talk to Roma.
He wants to talk to you.
Hello?
Roma, Roma...
you aren't giving up, are you?
People might think you still love me.
What do you want?
I'd like to give you a last chance.
I want you to drop
all charges against me.
You've already seen one explosion.
I can set off other
explosions around the building.
And seeing you so close
to me is suffocating me.
So everybody... move
back a little please!
What is he saying?
If we don't move our men back...
he is going to
detonate another explosive.
He's bluffing!
- No, I am not.
Roma, tell Commissioner
Mueller to take a look at...
...the fire truck in front of him.
In 30 seconds it'll blow up.
Damn it! Move all your men back,
we have only 30 seconds.
Roma, Roma...
- What?
Hello...
is it me you're looking for...
What do you want?
- My wild cat...
Anybody comes within 100
feet of this building and...
I'll set off more explosions.
Understood?
Yes.
I'm watching all of you,
especially you...
so no tricks please.
And get this damn
helicopter to buzz off!
It's spoiling the mood, sweetheart.
Don!
Damn it!
The cops are going to be busy
deciding their next strategy.
Are all our men in position?
Yes.
And the bombs?
Exactly where you wanted them.
Very good.
Let's get to work.
The gas will be effective in
the chamber for 3 minutes.
I leave the rest to you.
Alarm activated.
Come on!
Get out of there.
- That was close!
- Yeah!
Where are the plates?
- You think I'd leave without them?
All good.
Pass me the bag please.
Thank you.
Sam?
- Yes?
Time to go!
Got it.
I told you I will never
forget what you did to me.
Even so you trusted me.
Plates, please...
bag.
Not very smart, are you?
You wanted to leave
me behind to die, huh?
Death will come, Don.
Not for me...
but you!
Jabbar, if you kill me how
do you plan on escaping?
What do you mean?
- I mean...
there is neither a
service exit in the basement...
nor is Ayesha
waiting in a police van.
You see...
I didn't have an
escape plan for you at all.
Jabbar!
That's a lie!
How did he plan on getting away
if he didn't have an escape plan?
Vardhaan...
perhaps you weren't paying attention.
I didn't have an
escape plan for 'you'.
You think you can get away from us?
Remember, Sameer said
he couldn't control...
...the electric supply in the vault?
He was lying.
Hey!
What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Karl? Karl?
What's going on?
Shocking behaviour, dude!
Find Don! Go!
Perfect timing, Sam.
Thanks.
See you outside. Switching off.
Good day.
- Good day.
Could you deliver this urgently.
Hello officer...
listen to me very carefully.
So, ready to go.
Yeah...
ready.
Thanks.
Drop the gun.
I said drop the gun!
Hands on your head!
You are under arrest, Don!
You got me.
I did.
Cuffs.
Hands behind you.
Ooh... kinky!
Glad you like it.
Because they aren't coming off!
It's over, Don.
Where are your partners?
You may search my pockets.
Where are they?
They aren't my partners...
any more, Mr. Malik.
What do you mean?
I mean...
Vardhaan controls them now, not me.
Vardhaan is in the building?
Vardhaan, Abdul Jabbar and his goons.
They are a dangerous bunch...
be careful.
Come on.
So you let your
heart overcome your mind.
Very sad.
It was a momentary
lapse of judgment but...
I realised I'm not like you.
You definitely are not!
I have a long life ahead of me...
whereas you and Yana
don't have a future.
Stop it! Take him away!
I'd like to speak to
the officer-in-charger.
Vardhaan...
It's coming from
inside the building, sir.
Give it to me.
Detective Malik here.
Hello Malik?
Vardhaan.
You better surrender, Vardhaan.
Why?
I have 25 of DZB's
staff as hostages and...
you know I won't
hesitate in killing them.
You are already in a mess,
don't try anything stupid.
No, no...
You'll be stupid to ignore my words.
In two hours I need a helicopter
that will take us to the airport.
And I need a plane waiting for us.
When we reach our destination,
I will set the hostages free.
Is that clear, Malik?
That's not possible.
Really?
Jabbar!
Vardhaan!
You hear that?
If firing into air
can have that effect...
Imagine if I had to
shoot one of them.
Two hours.
Do you know how Don
exited the building?
No, really sorry.
I was in touch with him
till he got out of the vault.
What was he doing in the vault?
So Sameer confessed everything?
Answer me...
where are the plates?
Vardhaan has the plates.
How did you get out of the building?
Answer my question, Don!
Why should I tell you?
The hostages could
die because of you.
I regret this is happening,
Mr. Malik.
But if you want my help...
then I want something in return too.
You are in no position to negotiate.
Well in that case...
I'd like to talk to Mr. Diwan.
Why?
I think he will empathise with me.
It's quite simple.
If I go to prison, so
do you and Fabian Kohl.
Look you can't...
please look...
Look we had a deal. I gave
you everything you asked for!
Trust me, this is my last request.
Promise.
He will help us.
Mr. Diwan has promised me
immunity here in Germany.
For some reason, I trust him.
In return, I'll help diffuse
the bombs and free the hostages.
What about the plates?
Don't worry.
You'll get the plates back.
Roma...
What?
I want you to believe that..
...this change of heart isn't an
act and as a show of good faith..
I'm ready to deliver
the discs to you...
which will put an end to the
drug trade in Europe and Asia.
Really?
Roma, strange isn't it?
Once again life has
brought us together.
You and I can never be together.
You never know.
Perhaps someday you
will realise that...
I'm no longer the same
Don that you despise.
Though a dog may straighten
its tail, it is still a dog.
No wonder I can't let
go of you, my wild cat.
What? Are you going to shoot me?
Don't tempt me.
Let's go.
Roma, please...
do you really need to do this?
Yes, I do!
- Why?
The S.E. K unit can do the job...
Will you just relax?
Stay with Mr. Malik, got it?
If anything happens to her, I will...
You will...
what?
Your team is very
concerned about each other.
Sweet!
Gentlemen... enjoy the swim.
Where's Don?
Forget him!
If he wants to live,
he won't come back.
Okay, which way now?
Follow me.
So, what's the deal
between you and... Arjun?
It doesn't concern you.
Thought we'd catch up. Is that wrong?
You? Besides yourself, you are
incapable of thinking about anything.
And you.
You guys take cover behind the door.
Herman, go.
Roma.
What?
When I said, I was ready to
give the police the disc...
how did you feel?
Your words no longer
have an effect on me.
I know...
but still you were surprised.
Roma, the fact is
I'm tired of my life.
Now I loathe people
like Vardhaan and Coogan.
I want to be free
from them and the law.
I want to be a free man.
Please...
forgive me.
Come on, we are clear.
Wait Roma.
There are security cameras outside.
Jabbar's goons can monitor
everything in the surveillance room.
This was your brilliant plan?
I had planted one bomb
in the there so that...
we could destroy all
evidence as we escape.
Karl!
Check where the blast happened.
All positions... report in.
Position 1, all clear.
Position 2, all clear.
Position 3 come in...
Position 3?
Ladies first.
No reply from the
surveillance room, Jabbar.
Don!
Karl...
bring me his head.
Ulrich! Sven!
Sven and Ulrich are dead.
You're welcome.
You are shot.
Merely grazed me.
Sorry.
- You okay?
We're good.
Stay down. I'm going
to check on the others.
May I ask you something?
Yeah.
What's the deal
between you and Arjun?
He likes you.
It's not difficult to
understand why he likes you.
And you...
Do you like him?
I don't need to answer anything.
You know what I think?
You don't like him...
because you still love me.
I don't love you.
Just checking!
Herman's dead.
And the bomb is still armed.
Karl, can you hear me?
Karl, come in...
Ulrich... come in... Damn it!
Something is wrong.
Jabbar...
detonate the bombs.
Let them know how it
feels to mess with us!
Try the other one!
It's not working...
Jabbar...
Let her go, please!
Please don't kill her!
Malik, if the helicopter
isn't here in five minutes...
this poor woman will lose her life.
Vardhaan...
2 hours aren't up yet.
20 minutes to go.
You're lying, Malik.
When I throw this woman's
body out of the window...
you'll know we weren't lying.
Jabbar, don't!
The police didn't betray you, I did.
Let the woman go.
I'm coming there.
Vardhaan, the helicopter
has left the airbase.
It will be here in ten minutes.
Trust me! If you shoot,
I won't be able to help you.
Ten minutes, Malik!
Don...
come here right now!
Just a second.
Philip needs medical help.
I think you should stay with him.
I'm going with Don, okay?
Good luck.
Thanks.
Roma, what are you doing?
It's not safe for you.
That woman needs me.
But it's too dangerous.
Vardhaan and Jabbar can't be trusted.
It's my duty to get
those hostages out.
Try to understand, Roma!
If something were to happen to you...
I'm coming with you.
That's it.
Let's go.
Well, well, well!
What a happy reunion!
Hello Roma.
Your weapons on the floor.
I mean really!
Do I need to spell it out?
Please remove
your bullet proof vest.
Vardhaan, the police is giving
you everything you asked for.
In return, at least let the women go.
No, not a chance.
I've realised that women are...
...more useful in these situations.
If we must let someone go...
let it be Don.
Sorry.
- Don't be!
I want to kill Don
and so does Jabbar.
And I'm sure you won't regret
if he is killed. Right?
Right?
Give her the gun.
Good.
Now...
kill him.
Amazing!
Now I've seen it all.
You seem to have cast
a spell on her, Don.
Anyway.
Let's try again.
Jabbar!
If she doesn't shoot Don
by the time I count three...
shoot her!
One...
Pull the trigger, Roma.
Two...
Shoot me, Roma!
Three!
- Do it!
So, both of you were under a spell.
You're next, Don.
Vardhaan, you seem
to forget something.
What's that?
Before Don's enemy can
make his first move...
Don has made his next move!
Is everybody okay?
No. Not yet.
Stay right there! Please!
Mr. Malik?
Malik here.
Mr. Malik, Jabbar is dead.
And you won't have any issue in
taking Vardhaan back to prison.
The plates and hostages are with me.
So now...
I hope you have the papers
for my immunity.
We have the papers.
Very good, Mr. Malik.
Send them in...
with Sameer!
Sameer?
I want to see that
traitor one last time.
She's alive.
Bring the file here.
Let him go! Now!
You better find a safe hiding place.
Because the day I find you...
you'll be dead!
You know where I live,
drop in any time.
Of course!
I know where you live.
Drop the weapon. Right now!
What happened to Roma?
Yours I believe...
do take care of her.
Here! Hurry!
Gentlemen...
is there anything
else I can do for you?
Where is the disc?
In the bag with the plates.
Can I leave now?
Once I check the disc...
Of course.
And how long will that take?
Take him away!
Good night, everyone.
Thank you.
Check this out!
What about these plates, Mr. Diwan?
I'll take them.
They need to be checked for damages.
Is it good?
- Good?
It's priceless, Mr. Malik.
You want Mr. Kohl
to become president...
he will be the president.
That's my responsibility.
Oh my God!
Remember I said...
'Don's enemies should always
remember that Don never forgets.'
The people who
wanted to get rid of me..
...are themselves in the docks now.
Jimmy Coogan, you are under arrest.
Jimmy Coogan and all his ilk.
The police had to accept that
it was because of my help...
...that Fabian Kohl was exposed.
Vardhaan got back to
where he belonged.
Now to take care of one last thing.
Yes?
- Package for Mr. Ali?
Yes, that's me.
Please sign here, sir.
Here you go.
- Thanks, - Bye.
Hello?
- Don.
I sent you a present.
I hope you like it.
I missed you sweetheart.
Where is he?
He's right here.
When I get out of the DZB,
hand me over to the police.
Sorry?
Don't worry.
It's part of the plan.
This disc has all the
information and details.
Here's what I want you to do with it.
Check this out.
The perfect crime!
Plates please...
- Thanks.
- Bye.
Everybody thinks the real
plates were destroyed in the blast.
But here they are with me.
Now what?
My enemies are
either dead or in prison.
And the police have nothing on me.
So now...
Now... I am a free man!
What about Roma?
Why did you have to save her life?
Roma is like a bad habit.
And it's not easy to give up a habit.
Forget about her sweetheart.
Imagine how rich we're going to be!
Really!
I still can't believe
you got out alive.
Remember this...
It's not just difficult
to catch Don...
"No one knows...
What is this restlessness?."
"There's pain in my heart."
"Who is causing it?."
"The one I am looking for...
cannot escape me."
"Somewhere...
someday I will find him."
"My enemy."
"It's not easy to find me."
"Whether you search
on land or the sky."
"I am here and I am there."
"You will never find my clue."
"Anyone who's looking for me."
"Won't find a clue."
"Their desires will...
remain unfulfilled."
"My enemies should know that."
"What's that fire in your eyes?."
"Take my advice,
don't ever let it douse."
"You look so charming
when you are angry."
"Stay angry as long as you can."
"Someday you will... face my anger."
"One day you will know...
what's in my heart."
"Let me tell you."
"When that day arrives."
"Those desires will...
remain unfulfilled."
"My enemies should know this."