I'm here now!
Can we hope for the same gesture
of humanity from Pakistan?
I can't speak to the Indian Army
General like this...
let's simplify this...
- Sir, General Bakshi has arrived!
Already?
- Should I ask him to go back?
Cameras off! No cameras
before the show begins
Are you in charge here?
- Yes sir!
Not anymore!
I'm Brigadier Shekhar Sharma.
The General's security
is my responsibility
Any problems with that?
- Not at all sir!
Good!
Capt. Vikram, Major Abbas...
over there
Major Karan
Come with me
Sir, security camera is in position.
- Good!
All positions secured?
- Yes sir. All positions secured
Good. Let the show begin
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to 'People's Voice'
I'm your host, Rajat Saxena
and today's issue is:
Project Milaap (Unity), a historic
step or a historic mistake?
The dawn of 15th of August,
our Independence Day...
will see 50 Pakistani prisoners
in Indian custody released...
at the Indian border
Let's meet the man
behind Project Milaap
Please welcome General
Amar Singh Bakshi...
the Commander in Chief
of the Indian Army
We'd first like to
congratulate you sir, because...
the Parliament actually agreed
to Project Milaap this very morning!
General Bakshi, do you really
believe that Project Milaap...
will lead to friendship
between India and Pakistan?
It's not so simple.
A chasm of fifty five years...
cannot be bridged
by releasing fifty prisoners
Then why Project Milaap?
- It's a step... to cover the miles
So according to you
they are all innocent!
None of them are terrorists
or ISI agents?
If we had a shred of doubt that
they are dangerous to India...
we would never have
taken this step
Most of them
are poor villagers...
who didn't even know
they had crossed the border
After all the border is not
completely sealed
They didn't even have weapons...
yet they have been in our prisons
for years... some since 1971
We feel it's time to
send them back home
But not everyone agrees
with you General
Some even want to stop you
Everyone has the right to
free speech in a democracy!
But some people
don't want to merely speak
Sir, I'm talking about Raghavan
The people would like to know
who Raghavan is...
and is it true that
he has sworn to stop Project Milaap?
Raghavan is a mask. He hides
his face because of his shame
He's a coward - a terrorist...
so used to violence
that he now fears peace
Project Milaap
will be successful
The prisoners will certainly be
released on the dawn of 15th August
Damn! Back up!
We need back up immediately
Come in
Major Ram reporting, sir!
I'm outside the studio
Maj. Ram, hold position for
two minutes! Back up is arriving
It's too late, sir.
I'm going in
Hello General. I'm Raghavan.
I'll ask you the remaining questions
So General, I'm sure Pakistan is also
releasing our poor villagers, right?
Exactly what
I was going to ask him!
When elders speak,
learn to shut up!
So General, what about
Pakistan's show of good will?
We haven't heard anything
from Pakistan yet
Then why are we being
so damn foolish?
Because someone has to
take the first step
If we all behave like you,
there will never be peace
We've thought about this a lot
And we are certain
that Pakistan will reciprocate
Pakistan! Pakistan is going
to laugh at us...
because they don't want peace.
- Why?
Don't the Pakistanis
love their children?
You do, General!
You love your daughter a lot
Too bad!
She will really miss you, General
No one can save you now
Ram!
Easy now.
You'll be all right, Sharma
Ambulance is on the way
I want to speak to my son
Ram...
Father...
- Father...
Please...
Was I a good father?
- Yes father, but right now...
No, tell me!
You're the best father
in the whole world
I'm guilty son!
- No, father
Ram, listen please!
There's something
I've always hidden from you
You...
You're not my only son
I have a wife, Madhu
And a son, Lakshman...
your step... your brother!
Who I haven't seen
for twenty years
It's been twenty years
since she left me
Twenty years I have lived
away from them
It's time I pay for my deeds.
- Don't say this father
I knew you'll forgive me Ram.
Your heart is big
But until she forgives me
I will not find peace
My family will remain broken...
scattered
Promise me Ram, that you will
not immerse my ashes alone...
that both my sons will
do my last rites
Where is father's family?
Son, they left
nineteen years back...
Because I came here, right?
Dear Shekhar, I know you consider
what happened between us...
ten years back
a big mistake
I stayed away from you as I knew
how much you loved your wife
But today I'm helpless
By the time you get this letter
I may not be alive
I leave our son in your care
Please look after him.
He is your son, too
What's your name, son?
- Ram Sharma, sir!
Madhu... please
It was just a mistake
It was just a mistake.
- Mistake?
After marriage
it's called Infidelity, Shekhar
I'm leaving. I can't live
with this lie anymore
Lie? Are you calling
our marriage, our son a lie?
And what about the one
who is sitting outside...
your illegitimate son?
He's a truth too
And if he enters the house,
I am leaving
Where will he go?
It's not his fault
You're right Shekhar.
It's my fault
for having trusted you
For my sake...
because of me, father
stayed away from his family
I will bring them home
They won't come home, son,
not till you're here
You can't go anywhere
at this stage, Ram
I need you till 15th August.
- I know, sir
But I made a promise
to my father
Then go ahead.
Project Milaap was his dream too
Ram, this is the photograph
Raghavan gave me
It's my daughter Sanjana,
in her college in Darjeeling
This picture was taken
from her college
A gun can reach where a camera can.
And it's my worst fear
Sir, why don't you call her back?
- Because she won't agree
Even if her life's in danger?
- You don't know my daughter, Ram
I haven't seen her
for two years
She hates me
Of course, it's my fault entirely.
I never let her come close to me
I wanted a son. A son,
who would join the army like me
That's why I never loved her...
like I would've loved my son
Today I can give anything
to catch her glimpse...
but she won't let me
Sir, can we not send a 24 hour
Protection Team for her surveillance?
Sanjana will never let anyone
in a uniform come close to her
If anyone does, she will run away
...she's done it before
So what do you recommend sir?
- I want you...
to go to Darjeeling,
under cover to protect Sanjana
I don't trust anyone else
I'm sorry, sir. It's impossible for me
to go to Darjeeling right now
I thought you may be interested
in this mission...
as there's another student,
Lakshman Sharma, studying there
Your father and I've been friends
for 25 years. I know everything
Call it fate or co-incidence...
but his wife Madhu and
his son Lakshman live in Darjeeling
You are now officially on leave
till 15th August
I've already spoken
to the Principal of St. Paul's
You are joining the college
from Monday
And what subject
will I teach there?
You are not going there as a teacher
...you will be a student
I'll look really strange
as a student, sir
I think I'm better off as a teacher.
- You can't stay with Sanjana...
all the time as a teacher.
- But I just don't look like a student
Besides, it's been ages since I
attended the national Defence College
Don't worry. Even the principal
will say that you are there...
to complete your graduation
which was left incomplete
But sir, the current generation...?
I've never even seen a civil college
I'll be caught in a day!
- Ram, no matter what...
Project Milaap cannot stop!
Those prisoners have to be released
on 15th August
But Sanjana's safety...?
No harm will come to Sanjana
I promise you, sir.
- Thank you, Major
"Like the winds sigh..."
"and the birds fly..."
"like the bumble bee's affair..."
"I roam without a care"
"I'm the queen of hearts!
What sadness is, I know not"
"With no fear,
I do and I defy"
"Like the winds sigh,
and the birds fly..."
"They can halt, they can try,
they can stop and ask me why..."
"but do I listen,
oh no, not l"
"I'm stubborn,
I'm crazy..."
"They say my mind is hazy..."
"but no one knows
where my dreams lie"
"Like the winds sigh,
and the birds fly..."
"Like the bumble bee's affair,
I roam without a care"
"I'm the queen of hearts,
What sadness is, I know not"
"With no fear,
I do and I defy"
It's odd, I've never seen my brother,
I've no clue what he looks like
But I'm certain
his eyes will be like mine
Actually I think he'd be
exactly like me...
calm, shy, decent, disciplined
And my heart says I will
recognize him instantly...
my little Lakshman
"Let the nymphets
come to lure me"
"And know that I'm no worker bee"
"For when I look into their eyes,
I'll steal their hearts, their minds"
"No matter how gorgeous..."
"they'll be mine
without a fuss"
"Like the winds sigh..."
"and the birds fly..."
"Like the bumble bee's affair..."
"I roam without a care"
"I may be mad, a little strange,
and wilder than most..."
"but the most lovable,
am everybody's toast"
"Like the winds sigh..."
"and the birds fly..."
"Like the bumble bee's affair..."
"I roam without a care"
Friends, it's a truly blessed day
as today we have amongst us...
the famous student
of St. Paul's, Lucky!
When I came to this college
four years back, Lucky was my senior
When we first got here,
Lucky ragged us a lot, didn't he?
In the canteen, he stripped me and
made me sing 'My heart will go on... '
He's as smooth as so charming,
smooth and perky
We wanna fail school
just like Lucky!
I love Lucky!
Despite having failed his class
thrice, Lucky is still with us
And God willing,
Lucky may fail again...
and bless our juniors
with his presence too
And now, the moment
we've been waiting for...
Yes, it wasn't easy!
To fail consecutively thrice,
is not an ordinary feat!
But friends, with hard work,
perseverance and dedication...
you can all get here
And if I have your blessings,
I will continue to be with you...
right here, in this college,
for eons to come
That's a promise
Don't you feel any shame?
- Shame, Sanju?
Just look at these faces,
full of love, respect
And I won't need to study
this year as well
I've got you to copy from!
- Yeah, right
Irritating!
- Sanju...
Lucky, is Sanju your girlfriend?
- Avoid, man!
When Lucky has a girlfriend,
the whole college will turn to her
Who wants to look at Sanju?
- Hey, I only look at Sanju
Do you think she'll be my girlfriend?
- Are you...?
Oh yes. Why not? What a face!
What muscles!
What style!
- Oh stop!
You're perfect!
- I know
I have an idea! Let's arm wrestle.
I'll beat you and impress Sanju, okay?
Meet me outside
Stop it. You'll hurt yourself, Percy.
- Pain's my middle name, Sanju!
You think you look cool smoking?
- Yeah, yeah
Please! Give it to me.
- Avoid, Sanju!
Hi Mini.
- Hi sweetheart
Where's your miserable boyfriend?
Right here!
Quit playing with fleas!
Wanna fight a man for a change?
Would love to fight with a man.
But I don't mind fighting you either!
Who are you calling a flea?
- Scram!
The loser gets punished!
- And Mini will kiss the winner
Have you gone mad, Sanju?
- What'd I do?
You lost, Lucky!
- Time for punishment!
Whoever walks in first
through that gate...
push the person
and make him fall down. Simple
Hey what if it's a teacher?
Or the principal?
Whatever... man!
It's the principal!
Scared, Lucky?
Come here! Where was I going?
Home, sir!
Hi.
- Hello
Can you tell me
where's the principal's office?
First floor,
third door to the left!
Thank you.
- You're welcome
Sorry man, it was a bet!
What's your name?
- Wanna complain to the principal?
Avoid being a pain!
I asked you what your name is
Okay uncle, if you don't like
your face I can change it for you!
C'mon! You think you are tough?
C'mon let's fight, uncle
C'mon, let's go man
Is he our new Chemistry prof?
- What...? Oh God!
C'mon man, you are mine!
- I'm sorry
Behave yourself!
We were just playing a game
Lucky, say sorry. C'mon!
- Sorry
It's okay
Can you take me to
the principal's office? I'm new here
Hey, did I not say first floor,
third door to the left?
He's deaf too! Come on, Sanju.
- Excuse me, Sanju
Hello. I'm Ram
And I'm Lucky.
Now beat it
Tough guy!
Mrs Kakkad!
I'm going to fail them all!
Uncle, leave my hand,
grab it later!
I'm off, bye!
- The hag bores us to death
Shameless!
What are you upto?
Lemme go, uncle!
Hi handsome! Are you
the new Chemistry teacher?
No... I'm a student.
- Student?
I could just die!
I'm Mrs Kakkad, the Hindi teacher!
Good morning, ma'am.
- Good morning
Meet me in the back side
when my period is empty!
I'll teach you everything
Oh! Such strong muscles!
What...?
- She means strong muscles!
Thank you. Thank you.
- Mention not
Finally I've found an oasis!
Very good ma'am! Excuse me!
- Sure
Everything is "squeezed" for you
Excuse me, sir
Major Ram Prasad Sharma, sir!
General Bakshi may have spoken to you
Of course. Why didn't you
tell me earlier?
Lieutenant Ram, right?
- Major Ram, sir
What can I do for you, General?
- Not General. Major
Look, no one except you know that
I'm not a student here
So no saluting!
- Right
No saluting
The thing is Captain...
please sit down
I had really wanted to join the army.
But I couldn't remember the ranks
So, what can I do
for my country, Sergeant?
Okay!
I'd like to be
in Sanjana Bakshi's class
Done! What else, Wing Commander?
And please stop saluting every second.
- Top secret, I know!
May I leave, sir?
- Bye, Cadet Ram!
Don't salute, please.
- Top secret
Sir, there is a student in
your college. Lakshman Prasad Sharma
Do you know him?
Just a distant relative!
You must know him
No, I don't.
I can't even remember names
Don't worry. Go to the ID office
at 9:30 sharp
You'll get all the information.
Okay? All the best
Over and out.
Tango and Cash!
Each man for himself!
- Okay!
Roger!
- Major, sir
Come on, Comrade
"Oh brother! Where art thou?"
"My dear..."
"I look for you..."
"night and day..."
"in every way"
"My dear..."
"I look for you"
"night and day..."
"in every way"
"Call me..."
"show me where
you're hiding"
"Where are you...?"
"I'm here feeling blue"
What do you say, Bro?
Hello.
May I sit with you?
You, here...?
- Hello uncle
The senior citizen bench is there.
- Shut up
What...? What are you doing?
Please make yourself comfortable
Three years of house-warming
should qualify this as your home
In fact, please consider
this your bedroom
Thank you, sir. You're too kind!
- That's me!
Sanju, a round cap today, eh?
I'll get you
a cowboy hat tomorrow, okay?
And why are you sitting?
Please lie down
In fact, on her lap.
I won't mind, and neither will she
You...?
Sit, sit
You're new?
- Yes sir
Then get comfy!
- I'm okay, sir
Relax. No, this isn't
a Temple of Knowledge
This is a club.
Am I not right?
Please put your feet up.
- No, sir
No I insist that you keep
your feet up. Please
Up...?
- Please
My feet...?
- Come on, please!
Okay, if you insist, sir.
I'll be fine
How dare you!
I'm going to set you right!
But sir...?
- Come with me to the principal
Follow me. I said, follow me!
Sir, if you walk ahead,
I'd be able to
Oh! You will teach me, eh?
Come on!
And quiet!
And no talking while I'm gone...
It's the principal
I was just coming to you
I want to expel this
not-so-young man immediately!
Go to my office and collect
your Leaving Certificate immediately
Mr Rasai, there is a new student
in your class. Ram Sharma
Sir, I'm Ram Sharma.
- Major!
I mean, Majoring in physics.
Follow me
Class! This is
our new student Ram Sharma
Ten years back due to
some family responsibilities...
he had to abandon his education
But now he's back to complete
his graduation
I want you all
to be friends with him
Now who will be his friend?
Sanjana!
I hope she doesn't know
you're shadowing her
No, sir. Not at all
How is she?
What have I done?
- She's different
Are you two friends?
Ram, I don't like being
compelled to be a friend
Fine.
- I choose my friends
And they are very special.
And you're not
Are you two friends, Ram?
Not yet. But we will be
There are two commandos
stationed outside the hostel at night
You don't have to worry
with me around, sir
Everything is just fine here
And father,
you don't worry too
I'm here now
I'll find them,
I'm sure they are close by...
near me...
Lucky, did you speak to anyone?
- Yeah. I've put an advertisement...
up on the notice board.
We'll find someone real soon
Fix the fuse, Lucky!
The lights keep going out
Did I not ask you to
And your dinner?
Welcome to Darjeeling, Raghavan
It was a choice I had to make
for the sake...
of my little brother's education.
I had to quit college
But I always felt incomplete
And one day as I ticked
'under graduate' in a form...
I decided that as soon
as my brother finishes his studies...
I don't want to hear your saga
I'm not interested in you
or your brother
Fine! Let's talk about you.
Where you from?
What does your dad do?
What's up, Sanju?
- Lucky...
Ram has turned into my shadow!
- Who? Our uncle?
It's the first time
a guy's after you. Enjoy, baby
What are you saying?
- Maybe she wants another guy, Lucky
Mini darling.
I'll be back in a blink
Hey micro-mini! Watch it
Hey Uncle!
Bell Bottoms!
Dude...
are you deaf?
- Selectively, yes!
What's up, man? Why don't you stick
with people your age?
Hang on!
There aren't any here
Is this how you talk to your elders?
- Look Mr Geriatric...
go do what old people do.
Sanju's my friend
So stop bugging her, or else...
Else what?
For you, I'll shut eyes and count
till ten... not the usual three
And when I open my eyes,
you better have disappeared
I think so.
- Thinking's good for you
Where are you running?
Am I a witch?
I'm coming... don't go away
Uncle, I hope
you've left for good
That's Sanju!
- You failed again!
Yet again! And this time
you've broken even my record
How did you manage
to get 3.5% in Hindi?
Tell you what, if you pass this year
I'll give you a "Cadabury"...
that too a milky one!
- Come again
She means Milk Cadbury.
- Yes, milk one!
Sweet boy!
And where's the other one?
Student name?
- Lakshman Prasad Sharma
Your name?
- Ram Sharma
Can't give another student's
information to you
Just find out if...
Want information? We'll take it out
from the college computer...
during the lunch break!
Piece of cake
How much longer?
- Almost done
This is a race between
Lucky and Vivek
Lucky, who is our favourite
And Vivek, who is a bit angry
So whoever runs upto the roof...
and gets the college flag
for Mini gets a huge...
Are you mad?
I'd just said race!
You guys will be rusticated!
Why? Are you scared, Lucky?
Done!
What's going on?
- Sir, a race is on
No one told me it's Sports Day!
Yeah! Race!
Lucky!
Lucky hold on! I'm coming!
Someone do something
Who's that?
Captain Ram!
I mean, I want to make him
the Captain of the Athletic Team
See how fit he is!
Come on Captain, come on
Who is this "Makko" man!
Ram turned out to be Rambo!
Let go, Lakshman
Don't look down. Let go
No! Are you mad?
I'll die if I let go!
Give me your hand.
- No...
Don't be scared
I'm here now
Let go
I didn't know you were so fit.
Were you in the army?
Hey, stop that!
You're okay now
No, no, why do you keep
calling me Lakshman?
Because Lakshman your name
But no one knows my real name
in the college
It doesn't go with the image!
You will not squeal, okay?
Okay. Image!
Stop trembling first
And what do you think of my image?
- Your image is set
Idiot! You freaked me out!
Didn't I say it's too dangerous?
What 'Okay'?
What if something had happened?
You didn't even think about
what your mother would go through
How do you know mom?
I don't. I mean...
you must have a mom,
- True. Everybody has a mom
Not everyone.
You are very lucky
Ram...
the other day I had said that
my friends are special people
Well, you are extremely special
What's that?
- Hey uncle...
Okay... come on
Youth! Wonderful thing
Isn't it, Khan?
- Yes, sir!
Such joy! Innocence!
Look at this boy
Has he even thought about
his future...
its dangers?
How it's rife with enemies?
No kid thinks
about these things, Raghavan
It's time to send another message
to General Bakshi
Shoot that boy
Shoot him
while Sanjana is around
And I want a recording of this!
Any problems, Khan?
But he's a kid
This is war, Khan.
Any war needs sacrifices
Our war was for the country
ten years back and still is
Remember?
We found some villagers
at the border...
who claim they got lost searching
for water. They are Pakistanis
You know very well that you are
standing on Indian soil
So get ready for a trial!
Are you Pakistani?
Don't be afraid. Answer calmly
Yes, sir
Trial over
Major Datta, on what basis
did you kill those eleven Pakistanis?
They were Pakistani spies!
- All of them?
Perhaps.
- Is it possible that...
some of them weren't spies?
- It's possible
And it's also possible that none
of them were spies
They were Pakistanis!
I feel ashamed of having ever
called you a friend
Ten years!
It's taken me ten years
to create my own army
I've handpicked each soldier
I never said it would be easy...
never claimed victory would come
without losing something
If blood must be shed,
then it must, Khan!
It could be ours, the enemies'
or a little boy's
"Who are you waiting for?
I'm here now"
"Just one look,
"Who are you waiting for?
I'm here now"
"Just one look,
"Why are you quiet,
why the heavy brow?
"If it's endless love you wish,
ask for it aloud"
"And you shall receive it,
for I'm here now"
"Who are you waiting for?
I'm here now"
"Just one look,
"When you think,
when you see..."
"how much I love you..."
"Don't stay silent"
"Tell me, you have
that special friend..."
"who will give you
his heart, give up his soul"
"And I will say, true,
for I'm here now"
"Who are you waiting for?
I'm here now"
"Just one look,
"Why are you quiet,
why the heavy brow?"
"If it's endless love you wish,
ask for it aloud"
"And you shall receive it,
for I'm here now"
"Who are you waiting for?
I'm here now"
"Just one look,
"If there's something
in your heart..."
"tell me"
"No matter what time
of day or night..."
"tell me"
"If problems plague you..."
"or you feel down and out..."
"tell me"
"If you have a wish,
a little want..."
"don't ever be apprehensive,
for I'm here now"
"Just one look,
I'm here now"
"Why are you quiet,
why the heavy brow?"
"If it's endless love you wish,
ask for it aloud"
"And you shall receive it,
for I'm here now"
"Who are you waiting for?
"I'm here now"
"Just one look,
I'm here now"
What is this now?
- The loser must face punishment
No look,
I just lost because...
Sit!
And I sit here till when?
Until a girl walks
towards you from there
Girl?
- And until you serenade her!
Girls, singing...
I've never done that
Someone's coming!
- I hope it's not Mrs Kakkad!
Sanju! I can't sing
What the hell am I to sing?
"I'm just a little brave
tin soldier, sing with me..."
I should have stuck to the army.
I need a fresh new song... yes
"Buffalo soldier
...in the heart of..."
I got it!
She's the new Chemistry teacher
Ram, don't sing
No singing...
Swan song baby!
Wow! What a lovely sari
"My heart is the moon"
"You are the moonlight"
Just remembered!
Her name is Chandni (moonlight)
"Why is the moonlight..."
"so far from the moon?"
Is it my imagination?
Or were you just singing to me?
No! 'I'm just
a little tin soldier... '
Whatever!
"You have no choice..."
"but to return to my sphere"
"So go where you will,
go my dear"
"Go on, my..."
Don't watch!
You won't be able to bear it
No way! Such behavior
in this college, I will never bear it
By the way, which song was it?
'My heart is the moon... '
- My favourite!
'You are the moonlight... '
- What song is this?
'Why is the moonlight so... '
So old, and a student!
Disgusting!
So young and a teacher! Amazing!
Colonel, do you know
who her father is?
No. Who, sir?
- How the heck do I know?
Admiral, I know she is relevant
to your mission...
No, no...
- But apologize, you must! Go now!
A moonlight!
And what am I an eclipse?
"Makko" man!
You?
How dare you enter
the staff room? No...
don't stop me... I will have you
thrown out of the college, get that?
You punk!
Hey, this was in the 'Matrick'?
- You mean Matrix?
Shut up fatso!
Ms Chandni, if you command me
I'll throw him out!
No, thanks
Shoot!
- Actually they made me kneel...
and so I did because I'm a brave
little tin soldier!
They said a girl will come
and then 'when I saw you I felt... '
'like a blooming rose,
like a poet's prose... '
'like a deer in flight,
like a full-moon night... '
'like an endless search... '
'like the flame of a candle
in a far away church... '
'I saw a girl... '
In front of everyone?
Every time I see her,
I want to sing!
Must be our Chemistry!
- Shut up! Madame Curie!
Go and get the tickets!
- And we'll get the chips
I'll have popcorn
Guys, please stick together!
This place is new to me...
I may get lost
"I'll get lost"
What crap!
Why'd you push?
- Sorry!
Hold this.
How long are they taking, man?
No mistakes, Khan.
I want Gen. Bakshi to know that...
the bullet could be
for his daughter too
Record it. The girl should be
in the frame
What did I do?
In a hurry, my friend?
Looks like
your friends abandoned you
What's to become of you now?
What is he doing here?
He's a student, sir
Since?
- About ten days old here
Really?
Major Ram has been protecting her
for the past ten days, and you...
Because of your stupidity,
Khan has been caught
Commander, give me a chance
No Captain.
You don't know Major Ram Sharma!
He's the best
My departed friend Shekhar's son.
Looks I'll have to deal with him...
myself
It's going to be fun.
Gentlemen...
I promise you victory, and
that we will celebrate it with Khan
Who is Raghavan?
Our commander.
- A terrorist!
A soldier who can die
for his country!
No! He can only kill
What war is he going to win
by killing a young boy?
And what war are you fighting
by garlanding the enemies?
We don't want war,
we want friendship!
It's shameful that you have
sold yourself to friendship...
and we have to do your job
You may be in the army
but we are the true soldiers
You and your army is useless!
You are fortunate, Khan, that you're
in front of an officer of the Army
If we were like you, then
you'd have been dead by now
We have orders to take him
to the headquarters
Put it on hold!
Keep interrogating him
Though, I doubt if he'll talk
Is my jeep ready?
- Sir, where are you going?
To college.
To complete my studies
If the atomic weight of Oxygen
is sixteen...
can anyone tell me
the atomic weight of Calcium?
The atomic weight...
- Oh please let them be
Your hair look beautiful
when you let them fly
Really! When your hair falls
on your face it's like...
'I saw a girl and felt..."
'like a blooming rose... '
"Now that you're here,
and so am I..."
"come a little closer
so I could try..."
"to tell you
how madly I love you"
"When I first saw you
and began to get to know you..."
"I lost my sense of time"
"The fragrance of your body
cast a spell on me"
"And I lost my heart"
"Why are you this beautiful?"
"It makes us all wonder
and believe in things like fairies"
"Though your beauty
pales them to a blur"
"So, why are you beautiful?"
"That makes one speechless.
I'm lost and in a mess..."
"I'm obsessed"
"I worshipped you,
I desired only you"
"When I first saw you,
and began to get to know you..."
"I lost my sense of time"
"Now that you're here
and so am I..."
"come a little closer
so I could tell you..."
"what magic came over me
when I first met your eye"
"My first thoughts of you,
when I realized you..."
"when I really saw you,
and began to know you..."
"I lost my sense of time"
"The fragrance of your body
cast a spell on me"
"And my heart slipped"
Violins are playing.
In college
Ram? With a teacher? These will
turn into your funeral trumpets
Look at that.
- You saw that?
Nobody can see that
I've had this up for so many days
with no response
This is the problem of our college.
No respect, no discipline
Whoever did this has had it
Lucky needs a tenant!
I'm here now
Are you sure you won't have
any problems with me at home?
No problems. Grandpa's room is empty
and money's a bit tight right now
And if you're around,
mom will love you
Mom will love me?
- She always wanted a son like you...
Clean. But got me instead!
You two will get along superbly
And wait till you
taste her cooking
Mom's cooking!
- Yeah, she has only two missions
One, to reform me.
Two, to feed everyone
And your dad?
Ram, you're my friend
and all my friends know this
Do not speak to me
about my father
Never
That's our home
Lakshman,
there's no electricity...?
I'm history! Mom had asked me
to repair the fuse
I'll go and get
the fuse repaired buddy...
you go and calm mom down.
- I'm coming with you...
I'll be back in two minutes!
- No Lakshman, how will I...?
Just two minutes!
But how will I...? Mom...
Are you back, son?
What took you so long?
And why are you so quiet?
I knew you'd forget again
Do you know how long I've been
in darkness? We have a blown fuse
Forget it, I'll scold you later,
but first take the Lord's blessings
Oh Lord, I hope
he passes this year...
makes his mother proud
finds every joy in life
Who...? Who are you?
I thought it's my son...
- I...
I'm...
This is Ram, mom, my friend,
and your new paying guest
Ram, this is mom
I know
He's just your type
Bless you, son
Ram...
here, have it hot
Enough, aunty.
I just had loads... please!
Enough already? You're young,
you need more. Come on
I'm not as young you make me out be.
If I continue eating like this...
I'll have a paunch in a week's time.
- Good! A little paunch is appealing
Oh no aunty!
- It's a sign of prosperity
I'll get one more
- No, no... absolutely not
Why? Aren't they nice?
It's not that aunty.
They say...
mother's hands create magic
no matter what
Yes. Lucky told me
I'm sorry, son
So, did your father bring you up?
Yes. He nurtured me,
brought me up
My father was... is
a really nice man
Never let me feel
my mother's absence
But yes, he could never
cook like this
Actually aunty, I am what I am
because of my father
You're very nice, Ram!
Your father must be a nice man too
Yes
Fathers are so important
Sometimes I feel if
Lucky's father was with us...
Aunty, if you don't mind my asking...
I mean, Lucky's father...?
We don't live together
We had a fight and I left home
But didn't he come
to take you back...?
Several times
It's been seven years now, Madhu.
Please come back now
Haven't you forgiven me yet?
It's not about forgiveness
any more, Shekhar
Even if I reconcile
with your infidelity...
I cannot bear to live
with that boy at home
Madhu, please
He needs me
Just him? What about me, Shekhar?
And is Lakshman not your son?
You will need to choose, Shekhar
Lakshman and I will
come with you right away
But only if you want it this way
Mom...
- His Highness has arrived
Lucky, you're a walking mess!
- Where are my shoes, mom?
Why don't you cut your hair?
And why're you a wearing doggy leash?
Your jeans are torn!
And your shirt... son, give it to me!
I'll stitch it up in two minutes!
- Torn...?
I sat up since morning with a blade
to get it this way and you say...
Mom, it's fashion!
- Don't call me 'mom', Lakshman!
Then don't call me 'Lakshman', mom!
Lakshman - I hate the name Lakshman!
Why? It's a lovely name.
Lakshman Prasad
And goes well with your image.
- Oh, don't you just love it?
Ram-Lakshman, seems like Mahabharat
started in this very house!
The Ramayan!
- Whatever! I'm off
Lakshman, you won't be able
to get up tomorrow as well
I will mom...
- Tomorrow's Tuesday
I have to go to the temple.
- And we will, mom
I know you won't wake up.
- Temples are so boring, mom
Ok, Ok, Ok!
I'll take mother... I mean aunty,
to the temple
Ram, you're godsend!
See, problem solved
May I call you 'mother'?
- Only if you eat my food every day
Then forget it, aunty
Bye mom!
He'll come back late in the night.
This boy hardly sleeps
Wake up. Wake up, you morons!
I had given you an assignment
on Physics 3 days back...
Heat and Pressure
And I would be delighted
if someone has not done it
Why sir?
- Because...
then you'll have to do
the same assignment five times
Why does he spit?
- Take out your homework
You too... you too...
And ah! Lucky!
Lucky!!
Homework?
- I have it
Trying to con me, eh?
- No, sir
Today we'll separate the wheat
from the chaff
One second, sir!
Yes, do search below as well.
Maybe you dropped it there
But if it's not there
I suggest you start praying...
as only Lord Ram can
save you today
I know that your homework...
is done!
I don't believe it!
And have you done your home work?
No, sir!
Got you!
I miss the army. I've to get down on
my knees at the drop of a spit-ball!
If anyone sees me here,
I'd definitely be court martialled!
You?
You're up to something again?
- No ma'am!
I'm going to have you expelled!
- No Ma'am, I wasn't singing
Then what?
Why are you on your knees?
I've been...
punished by Mr Rasai!
Really?
- Really
I know it is very silly
"Oh lord! This boy
is nutty as a pie..."
"why is it so hard
to make him realize..."
"that first the heart pines,
but slowly..."
"and only on the way one finds love,
then you fall freely"
Rohan, have you seen Lucky?
- He's in the library
Library?
You're Lucky, right?
Why don't you go and put it up
on the college notice board?
You're Sanju's boyfriend, right?
- Hey double battery, single power!
Sanju? My girlfriend?
Are you mad?
Lucky's girlfriend will be
the world's most beautiful girl
Not a plain Jane like Sanju.
Now buzz off
I have to study
My dad is not dead, Ram
I know
He never loved me
He always wanted a son...
who would make him proud,
join the army like him
Are sons everything?
And daughters mean nothing?
Sanju...
Even as a child I tried to be
my father's 'son'
And look, I've succeeded
No one even remembers
that I'm a girl
Sanju, you're fine the way you are
It's time we remind everyone that
you're the most beautiful girl...
not only in the college,
but the world
Come with me.
- No Ram, please
I'm here now
Yes Ram!!
- Good evening ma'am!
Can you make me
look exactly like you?
What???
- Yes... not me. Sanju
Hi Sanju!
- Hello ma'am!
Come on... Come, come!
See you Ram!
- When?
Physics assignment. Five times!
You did my physics assignment?
And five times? I don't believe it
I thought I'll do it thrice
but by the third time...
it actually started to make sense,
so I decided to the rest as well
By the way, you're welcome!
Oh, thank you!
I was about to say thank you!
I said, you're welcome. Just do me
a favour, don't tell anyone
I got a reputation to protect.
- Of course. School, Lucky and all
Actually, you can
tell Sanju about it
She keeps chewing brains. This will
shut her up for at least two weeks
You know what I mean...
- Yeah, I know what you mean!
You mean you like Sanju a lot
- Like...?
Yes. Like.
- As in...?
As in... you know as in...
You are crazy man!
- No, no! You are crazy about Sanju!
No, no! You are crazy!
- No, you are crazy about crazy Sanju!
Ram, when Lucky will fall in love
the entire college will hear violins
Sanju? No
Sanju... no way, Ram
Shut your mouth, uncle
"Love is such a tornado,
Love is such a storm"
"Love takes away the power
of every life form"
"Everyone in love is crazed,
anyone in love is in a daze"
"Love makes it all so difficult,
yet it's all so easy in love"
"Look at these visions, these
lovesick souls, these smoking coals"
"Look at the follies of love"
"The woes of my heart
having glimpsed you..."
"It's like a magical spell,
what can I say"
"The woes of my heart
having glimpsed you..."
"It's like a magical spell,
what can I say"
Check that! Like that!
"The heart is but a traveller,
and you are the oasis it seeks"
"The heart is but a canoe,
and you are its bank with mystique"
"What more can the heart desire,
if it has you"
"My heart is
a Ionely place, my dear"
"Come, I need your light
and your sparkly cheer"
Check that! Like that!
"Love brings all the joy,
Love has the power to destroy"
"It is its own limitation,
but frees one like the sky"
"In the Land of Love,
live millions of dreams each day"
"Lucky are those who get lost,
for love has shown them the way"
"Look at these visions pal, these
lovesick souls, these hopeful ghouls"
"Look at the follies of love"
Check that! Like that!
"I worship you"
"You are my prayer"
"If I have loved..."
"I have loved only this way"
"I have loved
only this way"
Check that! Wicked!!
"My heart is going insane,
you are its only balm"
"Why is my heart all aflutter?
Tell me, love, what is the matter"
"Let your perfume
waft over and find me"
"Let your hair rain
their dark clouds over me"
Check that! Like that!
"Sweetheart, I have
crossed the beyond..."
"Sweetheart, you and
only you are my dawn..."
"Sweetheart, alas. You can't see
what's in my heart"
"Sweetheart, you'll remember me
only when I fall apart"
"Look at these visions pal, these
lovesick souls, these hopeful ghouls"
"Look at the follies of love"
"The woes of my heart
having glimpsed you..."
"It's like a magical spell,
what can I say"
"The woes of my heart
having glimpsed you..."
"It's like a magical spell,
what can I say"
Hi Sanju!
Ma'am, it worked!
- I can see that
You're looking very pretty!
- Ma'am it's all because of you!
Thank you so much!
- You're welcome!
But you should thank
someone else for this
Ma'am, isn't he different?
Do you know he's actually older
than you are?
I do. But he's still my student
Hi Sanju.
- Hi
Sanju, I want to... I have
to say something to you
But I don't know how to...
- I know what you want say
Really!!!
That I'm looking really nice today
You feel this sudden
attraction towards me
Well, I did this all for you.
- Me...?
Well, I feel like I'm cheating you
Because this isn't the real me
Tomorrow when I go back to
my old clothes...
and when Mini comes to you
wearing those micro-minis...
Percy!
Lucky, do you know
the difference between Percy and you?
At least Percy's feelings
weren't for my clothes
What's up, Lucky?
- Nothing
You could talk to me
No thanks
Hang on... Army...
Food's here
Ram, are you interested in the army?
A lot.
Army guys are different
Don't you think?
I mean, their style
or anything...
My father used to say
"It's a man's life"
Medals on the chest,
discipline, guns, tanks...
giving up life for the country...
They are so distinguished
Aren't they?
Mom, I'm going out
Mom...
Mom why do you do this
to yourself.
Sorry pal, I hate the army
I'm not interested in their style
or their uniform
They and their problems
can go take a hike
Lakshman!
- Mom, you know I hate their display
What is all this 'uniform,
patriotic duty... ' all bullshit!
Speak with some respect Lakshman!
My father is in the army.
I know how much he has sacrificed
We never met for months because
he was protecting the border...
so you, me and people like us
could sleep peacefully
You know what...
Even my father's in the army
and he's sacrificed a lot
He's even given up his family
I haven't seen him
for twenty years...
not because he was
serving the country...
but because he left my mother and me
to bring up his bastard son
Lakshman, not in front of...
- I'm just speaking facts, mom
It won't affect him one bit
You know what...
My mother hasn't slept peacefully
for twenty years
It doesn't matter to him.
It hardly matters to army men
They have no feelings.
They are inhuman you know.
You don't believe me!
Dad, do you hear me?
I'm talking to you
Lakshman, please Lakshman!
- No, don't worry mom.
It won't affect him
He can't hear me
Can you hear me, dad?
He never hears me
Nothing matters to him, mom
Dad, I'm talking to you
You don't care, right?
When I fail, you don't care
When I don't come back home
in the night...
you don't worry about me, right?
Why don't you scold me when
I don't cut my hair? Scold me, please
Why don't I fear you
when I secretly smoke, dad... Why?
Do you care?
You love me?
Do you hate me?
Anything... anything
I hate you
I hate you, dad
And I hate that swine
I hate him, Mom and
I hate his bastard son!
Are you okay?
Can you both not forgive him?
It's too late, Ram
It's too late for him
What are you watching, Lucky?
The most lucky guy in college
Lucky really misses
his father a lot, right?
Yes. He is helpless, but you...
Life passes by and we get used to
living without love
Why don't we give love a chance?
Why don't we trust our feelings?
Why don't you speak to
your father, Sanjana? Give him a call
No, he always preferred
to keep me away from him
So now you're having your revenge?
Sanjana, people change,
love changes them
You fear that he hates you.
Perhaps he fears the same thing
Why do we fear the ones
we love so much?
Speak to him once, Sanjana.
Life's too short for hatred
How are you, darling?
It's me
I heard your husband
is out of town
Where are you calling from?
- From a booth opposite your home
What say?
Looks like someone wants to die
Gun, pistol... who are you?
Quietly come with us
Hi
Oh Ram!
I thought it was mom
So what are you giving mom tomorrow?
- Why? What's tomorrow?
Her birthday
Oh shit! I forgot again.
This is too much
Ram, kick me, I deserve it.
- Yes, you deserve it
Thank you
Ram, think of something quick
Done
Happy Birthday, Ma
You... you cut your hair?
- Avoid, Ma
I didn't know
I have such a handsome son
That's me. I love you, Ma
I love you too, son
Good morning class!
- Good morning sir!
Class, I have some good news and
some bad news.
The bad news is that Prof. Rasai
has resigned
The good news is that Prof. Rasai
has sent a replacement himself
So class please welcome
Prof. Raghavan Datta!
Greetings disciples
Who is this 'ciples'?
I leave them
in your care professor...
Raghav.
- Raghav, right. I'm off
My name is Raghav, and
you can call me by my name
No sir, no professor, because...
What an ape. Won't last a week.
Am glad I cut my hair!
I'll learn new things from you
I'm fascinated by
your generation's perspective
Who's 'Percy-pective' now?
We may have an age gap, but not
in our thoughts
Not much gap in age too, sir.
Right, Ram?
Hey Vivek, watch it
Ram
Sir
Did you fail, or start
your education really late?
Sir, actually Ram had to give...
- No one asked you
When elders talk, learn to shut up
Has your father not taught this much?
- That's not fair, sir
Interesting class.
Everyone speaks for each other
What's your name?
- Lucky
Stand up.
Full name?
- Lakshman Prasad Sharma
Sit.
Not you Ram
Ram, you look intelligent
and disciplined
Didn't you teach them
some manners?
Anyway, now that I'm here you will
learn everything. It'll be fun
Raghav... permission to sit, sir?
Any doubts?
What a horridly rude guy!
- Avoid Sanju
Avoid what? How dare he say
anything about my dad?
Will his saying anything
affect your dad? It won't, right?
But the guy's got attitude
By the way, you look really cute
with this short haircut
Sanju, will you be my date
for the Prom Night?
Lucky... I'd promised Percy
that I'd go with him.
Oh Percy. I completely forgot.
No problem. See you
Lucky, last few tickets left
for the Prom Night. You want?
No dude. Not going this year.
- What? Are you mad?
How can we have
a Prom Night without you?
Hi, Sanju.
- Hi, Percy
Sanju, I can't come with you
for the prom night
What???
Thing is I get bored
with you, Sanju
And what's with
this lipstick...?
So better luck next time baby!
But I think
you should go with Lucky
Percy, I'm so sorry!
Better luck next time Percy!
Oh Percy, you're so sweet!
Sweet? Who?
I'll be at the Prom with
the other teachers
Everybody check your transmitter.
And this time there should
be no mistake
I can't go to the Prom.
I don't know how to dance
- What?
Sorry.
- Okay. Dance here
Hello Papa
How are you, Papa?
Hasta La Vista, baby
Welcome ladies and gentlemen,
to Sports Day
Boys team in black
and girls team in red
What are you saying? Not Sports day,
it's the Prom Night
Prom...?
Welcome to the Prom Night
Like last year, no kissing
on the dance floor
Especially boys and boys!
Okay?
Ram, this is your chance.
Go ask Ms Chandni For a dance
No, no
- Come on, Ram! Be a man
No, I'm not a man.
I mean not!!
Ram, if you don't ask her to dance
with you tonight...
I won't speak to you.
- No, Sanju...
Me too, Ram.
- Lakshman...?
Me too.
Listen guys
The Major's attention is somewhere
else. You guys go ahead
Sir, we're in position.
We have the target in sight
"Everybody get down,
this party is going to town"
"Rambablula, Ram Bamboo,
there is only one thing to do!"
"Baby, baby, let's rock,
Dance all night long till 12' o'clock!"
"Hey fair maiden..."
"sometime, somewhere, secretly..."
"let's meet sometime in secrecy..."
"let's talk
sweet nothings endlessly"
"But please oh please
don't meet others similarly"
"Hey handsome..."
"sweet, naive and so rookie"
"Look, we're made for each other"
"Can you hear our hearts flutter?"
"But I hope no other
can hear our private chatter"
"Hey fair maiden..."
"sometime, somewhere, secretly"
"Hey handsome..."
"sweet, naive and so rookie"
"Now that you're here..."
"my dreams seem so close, so near"
"And if you feel generous..."
"the weather will be marvellous"
"Now that we are one..."
"everything seems like fun"
"Now that we're together,
say bye-bye to cold weather"
"The breeze is soft and dewy..."
"the night is lost and sleepy"
"What's come over us so slowly"
"We've lost our senses entirely"
"Just so you won't remember
anyone but me"
"Hey fair maiden..."
"sometime, somewhere, secretly"
"Hey handsome..."
"sweet, naive, so rookie"
"Everybody get down,
this party is going to town"
"Lets rock lets shock,
Gonna be together till 1'o'clock!"
"These wretched distances
lead to such restlessness"
"But if you come a little close,
you can have my life"
"If you're so restless,
then hear this, I confess"
"If you're in my heart, my dear,
how can we not be near?"
"Her eyes look down ever so shyly,
I caught it though it was so flighty"
"I don't mind getting a bouquet"
"But like a gentleman stay away"
"Just a few more days without me"
"Hey fair maiden..."
"sometime, somewhere, secretly..."
"let's meet sometime in secrecy..."
"Let's talk sweet nothings endlessly"
"But please oh please
don't meet others similarly"
"Hey handsome..."
"sweet, naive and so rookie..."
"we're made for each other"
"Can you hear our hearts flutter?"
"But I hope no other can hear
our private chatter"
Your mere touch nearly killed me
OK! Good night then! Bye-Bye!
- Bye-Bye!
Ms Chandni, you dance
very well indeed.
Thank you. Good night.
- Good night
Who is dropping you home by the way?
I'm a big girl I'll drive myself
home in my car.
True. But a lady should be
escorted to her car
Please don't take the trouble
- Oh no. I don't mean me
I mean your favorite student. Ram
Sir.
- Come here
Won't you escort
Ms Chandni to her car?
Really, there's no need for you to...
- No, no.
I...
- Actually
Please go with her
- Yes, sir
Target approaching door. Handle it.
I'm sorry you were
forced to escort me, Ram
I love it, ma'am.
I mean, it's my duty
You really dance superbly.
Where did you learn?
Actually, whenever I see you,
I feel like a fish out of water...
A nut without a cracker...
- Oh no. Not again
Actually Sanju, Lucky,
Vivek and Mini forced me...
Your sari is lovely
Ram, if you drive
as well as you dance...?
Won't you drop me home?
Ram!
C'mon!
- Ram!
Get out!
Stop! Put the gun down
or I'll blow her brains out
Ram, listen to him!
Down!
- Down...
Sorry about the sari, ma'am
It's no problem
Thanks for the lift, sir.
But you needn't have bothered
We would have managed.
- Don't be silly
How would you go back
home alone, and at this hour?
Son, you never know
who you might meet on the way
Sir, I get off here
Thank you, sir.
- Sure
Won't you get out and
thank your friend Sanju?
Go ahead. It's okay
Good night, Lucky!
Hold it!
What the hell is happening?
Ram, a gun...?
Sir, please just keep driving.
Move it!
What's going on, Ram?
- Towards the hostel! I'll explain
Pull over, sir
Sanjana, your dad is here.
Go and talk to him
I'm sorry, Papa.
- No, my dear. I'm sorry
Thanks for dropping us here, sir.
- It was my duty
So you're in the army?
Major Ram, sir
Major, impressive
Glad to know that country's security
is in such able hands
Any doubts, sir?
- Absolutely not
Good night.
- Good night
Papa... Ram...?
I had sent Ram,
for your protection
So...
you're in the army, right?
No... yes ma'am
You're here to protect Sanjana?
Yes... yes ma'am
So you never really were my student?
Yes ma'am... I mean, no ma'am
Happy Teacher's Day
Thank you, sir... ma'am
Ram! Come in, come in, Ram!
Sir, we should congratulate
Major Ram on his successful mission
Has he succeeded?
Very good
So you finally
found Lakshman Prasad Sharma
No sir. Sanjana Bakshi.
General Bakshi's daughter
General Bakshi? Does he want
admission to the college as well?
No, General Bakshi is not joining
Sir, I have a request.
- Feel free to speak, Maximus
I'd like to stay here a bit longer
Then you must have lunch and go
- No, I mean...
I'd like to stay in college
for a few more days
Then stay till graduation.
- Okay
But please don't
mention this to anyone
Top secret?
Sir!
- Of course. Anything for the army
Thank you, sir! Thank you!
Lakshman Sharma. Lucky, right?
His distant relative. Had come
all the way here to find him
Lucky me
You have 6 hours
Find out the relationship between
Major Ram And Lakshman Prasad
So, when do you plan to
tell your mother?
Even Sanjana has agreed
to protection
You must reveal your identity...
- I know, Chandni
But I'm apprehensive
So Lucky Sharma is
Shekhar Sharma's son
Ram's step-brother.
Sweet
Look Ram, if they find out
from elsewhere...
then they are bound to feel that
you deliberately deceived them
And once they know who you are
I'm sure they'll love you even more
I see. So once you found out,
you loved me even more, eh?
Any doubts?
Gentlemen, get ready for action!
Tomorrow Major Ram will leave
for a long exile
Keep watching dad,
this time mom will accept me
Lakshman will, too
Hello Ma
Lucky...
Mother...
I want to say some thing...
to both of you actually
Ram, you're Shekhar Sharma's son?
And you never even mentioned it to me?
The army officers told me
He's quite a wretch,
but a very dear friend
We were in the same college.
Can you give me his address?
Or a contact number?
Is everything okay, son?
Looks like I've come
at the wrong time
Goodbye
Mother I... I was just going
to tell you this...
Just don't say anything!
Not a word! Shut up
Mother, I hope you understand
why I behaved like this
One more word Ram and...
- No Lakshman. Let him speak
I do want to know
why he behaved like this
Tell me, why did you sneak
into our lives?
Did you think we'd accept you, and
forget everything?
Will I forget the twenty years
I spent like a widow?
Twenty years,
which will never return
Did you think that if you
escort me to the temple once...
and touch my feet,
everything will be set right?
No, Ma
Wounds twenty years deep do not
get filled in twenty days, Ram
Go, tell your father that
we don't need him anymore...
we're used to living without him
And this is his penance too,
to live without us...
and die without seeing our faces
Pack up and leave
There's no place
in my home for you even today
Just a minute, Ram
What were you hoping to achieve?
Why did you do all this? Why?
I had come here to fulfill
my father's last wish
You were right. His penance was
to live without seeing the two of you
And... he died without seeing
the two of you
He loved you a lot
Lucky, he gave me his ashes
I just wanted to untie the family.
That's all
Even though I knew
I would never be accepted
I'm sorry
"Bonds that break..."
"loved ones ache"
"I hope the miles finds a bridge"
"Why does this happen?"
"Why does the heart bleed?"
"Why am I tongue-tied?"
"I leave my dearest here and how..."
I walk alone, I'm here now"
"It's me who found love,
yet lost it"
"Here I am...
restless and unsettled"
Sir
Yes, sir.
What?
Sanju, look up.
Say hello to your dad
So what now, General Bakshi?
Sanjana's with me now
Are you still ready
to sacrifice her...
him...
and all the others?
I don't think so, Gen. Bakshi.
Project Milaap (Unity) is finished!
I have a few more demands
My soldier Khan's release,
a helicopter...
and my favorite student Major Ram
His education is still incomplete
Check the corridors again
- Sir
Breaking news this evening!
The Pakistan General has announced
that on 15th August...
they will reciprocate by returning
Indian POW's to India as well
If one extends such a warm hand
of friendship...
even Pakistan isn't so cold as to
not reciprocate
It's a pity that
we didn't take the first step
We've won. Now he'll have
to release those kids
Nothing has changed, General.
Pakistan can do what they want
You will not release the enemy
And by the way, I hope Khan
is near the helicopter...
and Ram has been tied up
Because Sanjana and her friends
have very little time left
But sir, didn't we say that
if Pakistan releases our prisoners...
An old habit of theirs. One hand
tries to put balm on the wound...
and the other hand hides a dagger
for the attack
Now you guys, get back
to your stations.
We're expecting guests
Call the Prime minister's office,
and tell him that...
Project Milaap has been
indefinitely postponed
Inform the
Pakistani Ambassador as well
No, sir
Sir, please don't do this.
- No Ram
There's a mother out there
who waits for her son
Tomorrow there will be
several mothers sitting outside
What will I possibly tell them?
That for fifty Pakistani prisoners...
I had to sacrifice their children?
Not fifty Pakistanis, sir.
It was you who used to say that...
it's not about ten Indians or
Pakistanis but thousands of soldiers
It's about the common people
in these countries. It's about us
It's a question of an enmity which
neither of us chose voluntarily
I know, Ram.
I understand this very well
But maybe we need to wait
for that friendship a bit longer
Sorry sir, but how long?
Today, after eons, Pakistan has
extended a friendly hand towards us
If we retract now, it would mean
another fifty years of enmity
And this time sir,
we would have chosen it
What happens to those children, Ram?
- Don't worry about the kids, sir
I promise you. Tomorrow, before dawn,
all the kids will be free
Please cancel your order, sir.
Prepare for Project Milaap
Didn't you ask if Pakistan was ready
to release our prisoners too, Khan?
You believed that Pakistan
would laugh at us...
but Pakistan is reciprocating.
Like us, Pakistan also wants peace
Yes, Pakistan is
releasing our prisoners
Now what can Raghavan achieve
by killing those innocent children?
Whatever he's doing,
it's for the country, Major Ram
No, Khan. Major Raghavan Datta,
ex-army, court-martialled...
is doing nothing for the country.
Nothing
Did you know that he had son
who was killed in Kashmir...
by terrorists such as you
But Raghavan believes that
Pakistanis killed him
Raghavan is doing nothing
for this country
He is just carrying out
a misplaced vendetta
It's just revenge, Khan.
- Impossible, Major Ram. You're lying
Raghavan had said...
- Raghavan lied to you, Khan
Didn't you say your war
is for the country?
Well, tomorrow the gun will be
in your hand
Choose. Will you fight
for you country or for Raghavan?
You lost your home, your husband
because of me once
I won't let you lose your son
I assure you,
Lakshman will not be harmed
I'm here now
Ram...
I want both my sons back
Khan...
Are you okay?
- I'm fine, sir
Major, I thought you are
the very best
I was right in front of you
and you couldn't even recognize me
Let the children go, Raghavan
You've got what you wanted and
Pakistan is also cooperating with us
Yeah, yeah. I heard
It is this naivety
that will sink us eventually
No Raghavan. People like you
will sink us
You only know to hate, shed blood
You are so used to violence that
you can't bear the idea of peace
But there will be peace,
there will be understanding
And there will be friendship
- No friendship with Pakistan, Ram!
Only war.
And one result. Pakistan's defeat
Only then can the blood
on their hands...
wipe away all the blood shed,
our soldiers, my son...
who had nothing to do with the war.
Why did the Pakistanis kill him?
His body lay atop a hill
in Kashmir for two days...
on ice.
No one ever knew
Ram, there will be no friendship
with Pakistan. I won't let it happen!
You should think real hard
before you hate Raghavan...
because one day you will become
exactly that what you detest the most
Shut up, Ram
Now you are going to kill
these innocent kids...
and become what you once
hated the most. A filthy murderer!
Silence!
He has the blood of innocent people,
kids, on his hands
I say shut up, Ram.
- Project Milaap won't stop.
Project Milaap won't stop.
You've lost, Raghavan
Silence!
Go on, kill these kids
and avenge your son
It won't stop Project Milaap.
You have lost, Raghavan
Khan!
No Khan. No, don't Khan
Khan, don't
Khan don't shoot. Damn it!
Not now, Khan.
Put your gun down
My war is still for my country.
- Khan...
Fulfill the promise you made
to your mother
We may not meet again.
I wish you peace, Major
You too, Khan
Until Project Milaap
is cancelled we will stay here
And what if it doesn't stop...?
We'll have to kill the kids, Khan
Shoot them
Major Ram... Major Ram!
Hey shut up. Major Ram is dead!
They killed Major Ram!
Murderers!
You are a very bad man.
- Shut up and sit there!
Captain Roy, go check outside
There's no one outside
Sit quietly
Captain Mahesh,
there's no one there
Let go!
Calling all stations.
Come in. Rai... Rai...
Mahesh
What the hell!
What about you?
- Please, please... go away please go
Move it! Go
I have to do something for father.
Please go!
Go
Go. Find him now.
Quick
Why did you do this Khan?
Why did you deceive me?
No, it was you who
deceived us, Raghavan
I supported you for our country...
not to avenge your son.
- Khan!
It's not a personal war, Raghavan.
It's not a personal war damn it!
It always is, Khan. It always is
Ram... Ram
What happen?
- I saw them escape, Commander
I was fixing explosives on the roof.
- Major Ram can't escape!
Go find him damn it!
You won't come out
like this, Ram
Lucky! What are you doing?
Sanju, I can't leave my brother
alone in there
Lucky, don't go... please don't go
Sanju, he's my brother
Don't go... please.
- He's my brother
Ram... Ram
Why scream? If you call from
your heart, you will even find God
The sun is rising. No one can stop
Project Milaap now. Not even you
In five minutes the army will be here
to arrest you, Raghavan
You have truly lost
I'm the one with the gun, Ram.
How can I lose?
I can finish you off in a second and
parcel you to your father if I wish
But, I'm sure he can wait
another five minutes
Five minutes, Ram
Hurry up, Captain!
General Mohammad Ibrahim.
Congratulations on Project Milaap
You too
Your five minutes are up, Ram.
Wish we could play a bit longer
I was enjoying myself
Alas, I must leave now
Major Ram, your father beckons you
The count down has begun!
Three...
Two...
One
Sorry, Major
Where are you running now, Major?
Turn around, Major
Turn around damn it!
I want you to face your death
Ram, get away from that God damn roof
How will you face
your father otherwise?
He took his bullet
right on the chest. Turn around
What a pity! This story
has a sad ending, Major. Death
What a pity, Raghavan!
Have you forgotten?
It's always the bad guy
who dies in the end
Two...
One
Don't let go, Ram.
Don't be scared. I'm here now
That's what I'm afraid of, idiot.
Now shut up and pull me up
Welcome parents, teachers and students.
And welcome to Prom night!
What are you saying? Not Prom Night,
it's Congratulations Day
Welcome to Convocation Day.
And this year finally
Lakshman Prasad Sharma is graduating
Along with a very, very, special
student Major Ram Prasad Sharma
"Can you hear the air,
and the songs it's singing..."
"about how life is youthful
and charming"
"Every moment is liberal"
"Every second is a thrill"
"Looks like this caravan did find,
The oasis of true love"
"If the days are bright..."
"the hearts will delight"
"If the days are bright,
the hearts will delight"
"Can you hear the air,
and the songs it's singing"
"It's a musical season,
and dreamy is the mood"
"How can one ever stay subdued"
"In life's chase,
you'll stay in my eyes..."
"I'll always feel you
in my embrace"
"Every heart is crazy
and now I know why..."
"this evening feels so hazy"
"Every moment is liberal"
"Every second is a thrill"
"Looks like this caravan did find,
the oasis of true love"
"If the days are bright..."
"the hearts will delight"
"The hearts will delight"