This is here's ulitimate
river front
here millions of yachts docks
this yort belongs to Armaan Malik
on last saturday of every month,
there is a game of cards
so much money is gambled here by
which armaan can buy an island
his life talks with air
armaan never opened his secrets thats
why his property is worth billions
he started his criminal career as
a underground street fighter
he loves his money and other's money
he hates 2 things, other's cheat
and own loyalty
its not about 5000 euros,
its about cheating
you promised me if I will say truth
you will leave me
and I never break my promise
one side armaan's power is
getting stronger
on the other side he has 1
weakness
her mother died when she
was born
so they met like this
since then omisha is with armaan
she is armaan's step sister
she is armaan's 50'/, partner
in 3 years we will make this
place into this
I cannot give permission to make
casinos in my state
dont be so fast to take decision
you can see sister love
all cards have micro sensors
Ilena phone has micro processors
when Ilena gets this image,
she changes armaan's cards
there life goes on if this storm
did not come in their life
he is good for good ones
if someone do bad with him then
he will be baddest man on earth
just now a man has bought 5 million chips
if he wins then we have to
pay 180 million
who can say just 2 minutes before
you have lost 5 million euros
I have used 5 million to meet you
I dont want you have to wait
to meet me
what can I do for you?
I want to do something for us
I have so many currency papers
that I can print as much as notes I want
why you are telling me this?
You need a company to go to jail?
You all have atleast 5 casinos each
in return you will give me 500 million euros
you will earn 100 million euros
but why we?
Casinos have the best currency
checker machine
casino is the most safe place
for fake money
change the system of your casino
I have used 5 million euros here
who can use 5 million euros to
meet someone?
Can you give me 24 hours?
I give you time or money,
its same thing
its written if you will not return my money in
15 days then your 5 casinos will be mine
I have to think for whom
I have to pray?
You can see it blank paper
I can see you in it
if you will shout in this condition
then your brain will damage
the money which I lost in your casino
those were real
why you have done this?
I dont know you
if you knew me than you would
not done that
I never thought you can do this
do you know why they call mangoes
to mangoes?
What kind of man you are?
You never goes anywhere
you think I'm flirt?
Your previous assisstant told me
you are very colorful
I use it when I want
where you have gone?
I was fine until now,
now you have come I cannot say anything
she has gone,
she ran away with arab
we are not together now
I have some work with you
I have a great deal by which we
can earn alot of money
this deal is impossible
without 1 person
whom you know from years
this cant be happen without him
deal is of billions and I will
give you 10'/,
tomorrow there is a big race here,
armaan will come here
once few fruits were talking to each other,
orange said I'm like ball
why banana said this?
I have to make answer for it
he is armaan malik
she is armaan's sister Ilena
I told you ranvir has a big
deal for you
lets talk in stands
we should put money on number 4
I have put 2 millions on it
he has never won any race
I think you have come to
race 1st time
I have come here before
I dont understand 1 thing,
how you won this race?
I gave money to all jockeys
I have heard you are interested in
Vikram Thapar's casinos
his casinos cost 1500 million euros
I will take 10'/, of it
vikram's 5 casinos are mine now
your share is in your car
it means I have to win again,
you have to lose when you play with me
dont worry my car has all
the safety systems
by the way if we will die then
what about his reputation?
You will not ask how I know this?
I knew his game is fixed,
I can see more than you
you are magnetic, you have taken
back your money
there is a party on this weekend
who will stop me?
I like men like you
I will come at 1 am
you dont waste time
what you notice 1st in girl?
But the girl is same
god has given you assets but he
did not give you brain
I could say this but this
is not enough
in last 48 hours I remember
time which I spent with you
still arrow is not on target
until now nobody has touched me
without my permission
when did I say I feel bad?
Do you know each other?
We just played archery and
he won
there are 2 reasons for this party
recently we have acquired 5 casinos
its looking more beautiful but it will look
more beautiful when someone will wear it
when you will give me ring?
I think you are angry because I won
yesterday
today if I lost then your hot costume
will be reason for it
if this would not be a game then
I would have killed you 3 times
now I will not turn back on you
is there any fruit which you
never eaten?
Since how long you know ranveer?
First he helped me to buy
thapar's casinos
whether he is very nice or
he wants to win my trust
because I have a plan for which
we have to trust each other
there is deal in which there
is 15 billion euro investment
it will take some more days
to complete deal
I told you me and sonia are not
together
we were very happy that day
because it was our last day in cyprus
we were moving to bangkok where
sonia's sister was waiting for us
but its awkward. I'm meeting my sister
after 11 years
I transfer money from bank
so vikram thapar killed sonia
vikram just completed contract,
armaan malik killed sonia
I have already give punishment
to thapar
after so much hard work I left police job
and running this club
nothing is more important
for armaan malik than money
sonia's body is still in morgue
I have taken swear until I kill armaan
I will not bury sonia
you never thought that you
will find me here
I was also shocked when I saw
you in armaan's weekend party
I thought you have also come to
take revenge from armaan
but you started to flirt with me
and Ilena
my sister loved you alot and you
are flirting with armaan's sister and girlfriend
I'm waiting for 1 chance to kill him
you love your sister and you
just want to kill him
I loved her the most and armaan
love money the most
he has taken sonia from me and I
will take his money from him
I know what I'm doing
if you are with me then my
work will be more easy
you were waiting for someone else?
You were meeting me in 10 minutes
where did you plan to kill me?
I wanted to kill you but ranveer
want to ruin you
you have made me sonia's sister
I told you he asked me for
my address
he believed that I'm sonia's sister
by looking at fake passport and photo
he said I know what I'm doing
how do you know ranveer
has come here?
You also dont trust me?
I love money the most and its a matter
of money I dont trust anyone
I knew ranveer has come to ruin me
I just want to confirm it
what will happen in future?
After finish line I will make his
win into my win
there are 2 reasons for too
much drinking
he wants to say something which
he cannot say
tell me how do you like me?
Your heart can cheat
if there were no fruits in this world
then what would you eat?
What is that?
Its a copy, its original is in
italy's church
why you called us here?
Its a way to take out 15 billion euros
from Armaan
he is armaan,
he is not a fool
until you will not steal shrout,
armaan will not give money
you will help me in it
I have made a mistake
I have introduced a wrong guy
ranveer singh is cheating you
he dont want to give profit,
he wants to take sonia's death revenge
after thapar he wants to ruin you
you cannot imagine his plan
ranveer singh gonna steal
shrout of turine
I will give 5 billion euros and
armaan will take 15 billion
after that I will take shrout
and money too
why you are telling this
to me?
Ranveer is giving me 10'/, and you can
also give me this
help ranveer,
I'm with you
first and last time I'm telling you
dont interupt me infront of others
because half of money is mine
what do you think?
I came to know now RD information?
Killer shooted sonia's murder
when RD introduced me to
ranveer I knew he come here for something
infact I will get 35 billion euros
remember 1 thing, he will never know
we know everything about him
you are making plan of making
a rich person into poor person
how did you guess? I have seen this
expression many times on armaan's face
I want that look which you showed me
on hotel
what are you saying? What kind of bomb?
Ilena and ranveer both are in car?
There is a bomb in the car,
dont stop or slow down car
there is a bomb in the car,
how do you know there is a bomb
in car?
My guy informed me vikram thapar
placed a bomb in your car
may be he wants to take his
casino's revenge
you have confidence that he will steal
shrout of turen
I trust him like I'm stealing it
he is saying deal will be happen
in ruins of antalia without weapons
when this robbery will happen?
Who did not heard his name?
You have said thanks for coming then
what you will say later?
I will also introduced you to someone
you have always won against my fighter,
there is my new fighter in saturday's fight
like you never lost same like
typhoon never lost
I'm sorry my last fight
was my last fight
its good otherwise typhoon would
force you to leave it
even hollywood movie did not steal it,
its gonna happen in real
if someone other said this I would
have killed him
if your hands have power than
I will give you money
this saturday you have to fight with typhoon,
if you win I will be in
you were listening to my brother?
You want to take sonia's
death revenge?
Whatever you plan armaan
always knows about it
I made a mistake, I have introduced
you to a wrong guy
you best friend is cheating on you
why you are telling this to me?
On that day armaan put that bomb in car,
not vikram thaapar
did you place bomb in Ilena?
Yes but ranveer is also in that car
what are you saying?
What kind of bomb is it?
Armaan forgot his talk also
record in this villa
he called you to save you,
because you have more benefit for him
we both have started this business empire,
now he wants to be single owner
this time I'm saved because of you,
next time I wont happen
you want your revenge and I want
my money
shrout is here
this is church's main hall
these panels have sensors
security guards and cameras
also watching it
if someone crosses shrout then it will
automatically go in a compartment
then steal shrout from here
these walls are of steel
expect this door which opens
with a security code
we can go in from here
and steal it
how we will reach there?
I'm christian but I never
got time to go church
1 Kg RDX
when this box to be delivered
here armaan's fight will start and
there this box will reach church
real bomb squad has reached here
now what we do?
By tomorrow you will get your money
ok you will get money in bonds
in you make any mistake then
I will kill you
its not safe that we all go
together from here
you go,
we will come from evening flight
lets go to some resort
I'm going out from room,
you meet me at automen fort at 12:30 PM
I will say to you
you have become so fruity
by eating so many fruits
now you will make me liquid
dont say sir in this position
i got you after a long time
last time I was waiting for fruit
to complete
you eat so much
thank god you are fine
I saw it on news
this is not real,
its duplicate
real shrout is in airport's locker
and I have its key
tomorrow deal with armaan is in
ruins of antalia
you give him this shrout
this guy will become theif
and give it to armaan
and give him shrout and give it to him,
until deal is finished you stay in his car
after that you both go from there,
after half KM eric will give you car and money
then you come at airport and wait for me
my omisha will do as you want
and I will do as I want
I trust you
deal is completed and armaan
has mixed poison in drinks
we will die and armaan will
take all money
you trust everyone so easily
you trusted me so easily
you dont know blood relation is the
biggest relation in this world
atleast bigger than 1 night stand
Ilena put poison in your glass
cheap glass is more expensive
for ranveer
what do you think?
You can run race
I can run race
since 1st day I know everything
I also know this shrout is fake
because of me you will lose
your good habit
this is your 10'/,
it was pleasure loving you
according to our plan we got
shrout and money
after you I will handle
everything
we should not leave good habits
nothing is more good habit than
to be alive
you are thinking how I'm alive?
Ilena did not put poison
in my glass
when I came to know you have
placed bomb in my glass
then I decided on which side I'm
you were saying you run this race?
Race was always mine and
it will be mine
I sent RD to you to tell
my plan
so that you will feel you are
far than me
I'm sonia's sister and I have
come to kill armaan
do you think I have never seen
sonia's sister
and even I did not see her photo
why did you kill her?
She had to die
before you she was with me,
I loved her
thats why I killed her.
If you were at my place, you also did this
dont trust him
I dont trust him and I
trust myself
you think I killed sonia for love?
I killed her for money
today I will give you a
precious gift
you meet me here,
dont meet me down
who gave you this?
This is fake
its a normal cloth which is printed
we are working together since
10 years
I know you will never cheat me
I dont care
you also print calender, account books
turn on speaker
until now you have known you
have become poor
dont try to think how shrout
and money become fake?
You always called me hero
what I call you now?
Either I kill you and take
everything from you
or you give me everything and
I will let you go
from now your everything is mine
and your girlfriend is mine too
you forget race starts again where
it ends
when shrout is stolen then
where it gone?
We cannot steal that
religious thing
i just took a little help from god.
I have informed church, its a breaking news now
ranveer trust you but
I dont
I dont understand 1 thing
when bags got replaced
you give me 10'/, and armaan too
now I want peace in my life
not suicide
take swear you will not
meet me again
we take swear to break it