Hey you kids, how're you all?
No greetings raees?
Begin working..
Who bring the more stuff today?
Bring the all market for you!
Put some chemical In It..
Gujrat Is the state of
free india where everyday Is dryday.
Means, buying selling liqour Is forbidden.
If you got busted selling liqour,
you're will be impriosoned for 10 years.
But abondonned Is the
begining of rebelness.
Still gujrat Is declared drystate,
but annually It's consuption Is 25 crore
It'd be impossible of raees
would not be born.
Take a bath
the biggest seashore Is here
In our gujrat.
Learn..
I don't like to hit,
but you make me do It.
Now learn.
Now go there.
Nothing to worry, his eye sight Is
weak, he needs the specs..
Is that necessary today? If you don't
give me specs I won't go to school
his eye sight Is weak but
brain Is strong..
I can't see the blackboard,.
How much money do you
need for specs, don't worry about It.
Give me some other time.
I don't want to give him
the indebt sight..
I'll order It In few days.
I'll give you signal when danger.
You spec theif..
Brother..
From where did you find
this frame without glass.?
It won't work.
You come tomorrow,
I'll buy you a specs..
But I don't have money...
you've to pay me 2 rupees fee.
Take this frame back.
And give It to gandhi...
It's looking good ..
Look there.
Gandhi Is smiling.
Look, they're heading
to dealers den..
Our business Is In danger..
Lets go.
Remove everything.
The bottles and all.
Hurry up, don't let go anyone.
Find the liqour..
You here?
Are you fond of whistling?
Why did you slapped?
Ask him.
It's my work stuff..
Work stuff or violence.?
You do bad works..
As you do police job,
I do scrap job..
Mind one thing, no business
Is small for us..
And no religion Is bigger
than business.
Is really no business Is small
and no religion Is bigger than work.
Till It not hurts someone.
What'll do with money?
We'll sell the liqour,
ilyas Is gone, do you want too?
Police nabs the people who
sells desi liqour, not english
so we'll work for jegra seth,
he sells the english.
It's impossible..
I'll try.
Everywhere Is checkposts,
can't deliver today, If we do so?
Who are they?
They both used to work for ilyas.
It's 6 bottle..
I'll take 3 rupees for 1 bottle.
Are you asking for work or ransom,
don't call me battery.
You're wearing the specs,
so what do I call you
don't call me battery.
1.5 rupees on 1 bottle.
Give me bottle.
Never call me battery.
Do you understand now?
Run away..
Give him a job..
He has hindu's brain,
and muslim's daring both..
Salaam boss.
The police Is gone crazy on check post.
Tell raees to get the stuff released.
Sit..down.
Take the money,
release the stuff.
Let them go..
Your pocket was empty,
I fulfilled,
you flated, now inflat It..
How do I inflat It?
Blow now.
Blow It now..
Do business politely,
you'll save your honor and time.
We buy the goods, and lookafter,
and he takes the benefits.
Till when will we work
for gerag seth?
Lets start our own business,
It's not our line..
Take your salary, and enjoy
for our business,
we need daring.
You forgot what jayraj seth
told you..?
Miyan bhai's daring.
And banya's brain..
We have both.
You've come and my lucky ace.
I'm the slave of king.
Your mood Is not good.
I'm working for you for many years,
now I want to start my own business.
I'll increase your pay,
why to business.
Convince him..
He's stuborn..
My boy Is grown up,
he'll do his own business.
You must have think that
from where will you buy goods?
How can I buy goods from
anyone else except you
do you know, In our business,
you've to spend money like water.
Do you have enough money?
He must have It.
How much worth goods do you want?
I'll buy for 1 lac..
Give me cash and take the goods.
I don't have money,
I just need some time.
He has no money,
just need the time.
You worked for me for many years,
so I'm giving you 3 days.
Give me money In 3 days,
and take your goods.
72 hours.
Or you'll get nothing.
Keep It..
The time will run In your brain.
You know jayraj,
If you'll not pay him In 3 days..
You about to sacrifice It.
Who'll pay for It.
It's worth 500 rupees.
I bought It In 300 rupees.
Cut the crap.
Where are you going?
You've come so early..
I took u turn..
I just see your queen.
Give me keys,
come fast from corner.
I give you king and
taking the queen.
Becarefull
It's eid, people give you
1000 for a goat..
Who will give It In fatehpur.
Not fatehpur,
but In bombay..are we going?
Do you have any other plan
for paying jayraj..
You take your shop there..
Who's goods Is It?
It's my own..
Do you have permission?
No..
From where did you come?
From gujrat
take your goats and go back.
We'll do some business here..
It's eid, let us earn some money,
we'll pray for you.
If I sacrifice you with your
goat so It'd be better.
Hey battery, can't you hear?
Get outta here.
You messed with mosa bhai, If you find
danger, why didn't you give me signal
you didn't give me time.
It's my mistake okay,
he got unconcious In a slap
anger Is the talent of devil,
therefore anger Is forbidden.
Your boys started the fight.
Your goat has became biryani
goat Is the prey of lion
not the business.
No business Is small
and no religion Is bigger then work.
Mother says.
My lose Is big and time Is less for pay.
If you pray for me
so I'll leave now.
Come here.
Keep It...
for future.
Can I have a biryani for both.?
Everybody will celebrate eid,
and we'll do fasting.
Leave the jayraj,
think about mechenic.
What?
Do you see girl dancing on my head.
It's 1 lac worth biryani..
You have It too
my ace has 3 thousand rupees.
What do I do with It,
do I give It to jayraj or mechanic.
You've come till here,
the haji bro sent me for business.
Let him come.
Have to kill the moosa.
I don't have any mess with
moosa, and It's not our line.
If I'd like to shake tail taking order,
I'd never do my own business.
Take your money back.
Moosa sent this for you,
now you were saying to kill moosa,
and now saying I'm his man..
Who are you?
My name Is nawaab.
I'm moosa's sadiq..
He can give me In train.
But moosa measures first.
Don't take this money,
It's of your goats..
Brother likes your business saying.
And when brother likes someone,
so nobody dare to touch him
If we'd agree with your first deal so?
My left hand never misses the aim.
Jayraj seth asked for you,
your time Is over.
Tell your jayraj seth,
raees give up following ordres.
Now my time Is started
mother, we'lre going to start
our own business..
By the will of god,
we'll earn ..
We'll not harm anyone.
Pray for me.
Who call you here?
Whose guest are you?
Don't show me finger.
We're hasmuk's guest,
whose guest are you
so you're giving desi liqour
to people?
It's not desi, but scotch.
We've to shut this party,
but we'll do party In police staion
for your convinience, we've
arranged for transportation
give me In writing,
I'll release them.
If my father'd say to release
them so I'll take It In writing.
You'll get your transfer
order In writting.
Send him to fatehpur.
Get the ball.
Again.?
I told sadiq not to hit upthere,
he always hits the sixer,
and sends me to get ball
will you do me a favour?
Get me some soda and ice..
How can you arrange It,
I understand I can arrange.
What's the speced boy..
Raees
what do I write,
your resignation..
Or the address of liqours den.
Nothing happens with
one bottle, I want the truck.
Whose car Is It?
It's jayraj seth's goods.
Take the car aside.
You got the truck.
Now?
Call the media people.
I'm feeding all the cops for many years.
And they're crushing my goods.
Go and find who did It.
Majmodar screwed jayraj.
Don't take him easy,
we're going to have a big order.
Majbodar sir, called you
whose goods was It?
Do you know.?
It was jayraj's goods.
You used to work for him?
Yes used to work
what do you do now?
I do business.
To which you're calling business,
It's a crime..
Raees truck Is coming..
It's police station tea,
get used to It.
Or stop your business,
the speed you're running,
you'll put yourself In danger.
Give this pill to father
who are they?
Minor criminals..
From where did you
get this groom..
He's the man of raees.
Send them all,
and you come with me.
Do you know raees,
how do you do business.
I just know that
today Is my wedding.
What you gonna do outside
when you don't know anything.
Cancel his parole,
don't send me back to jail.
Do you want to complete your nikkah?
Find out where raees keep
his stuff...
do you agree...?
Yes.
Go now..
To saving the business
from majbodar,
groom speaking,
have to give you info about raees.
Tomorrow raees Is getting
big consigment.
If you catch him this time
so his business Is over.
The police Is everywhere
on the checkpost of gujrat.
Till we don't find his truck,
nobody will move.
This time his the end
majbodar has surrounded the gujrat.
Even a bottle can't pass
do you know any shooter
named saleem.
Yes..
He got killed.
Do I ask you something.
What you used to
call your father.
Aunty..
Obviously father.
What?
If someone call you father so.
Who'll call me father?
It's the begining of orginzed
crime, If we don't stop raees.
The incident happened In your
area and your lecturing me?
Now you give me In writing
why I don't transfer you
you can transfer me anywhere,
but I won't spare raees.
And you can take this In writting.
As I got transfer from fatehpur,
raees played openly
raees every month gives the
liqour truck to cops
say my salaam to raees bhai.
Now bulldozer weren't working
but camera's flash.
All the officers comes
In the front page.
Press police government,
everybody Is happy
raees has sent the shirt for you.,
see the color
he has new idea,
he's starting home delivery of liqour
why're you stucking me..
I'm speaking truth.
When you'll get married,
then you'll know the fear of wife.
Why're you yelling at him.
Faizaan.
You like It..
You're seving me.
Do you want the leave.
I got the son..
Congrates.
What you named him?
Faizaan.
Father Is ramlal,
and son Is faizaan.
You're quiet secular
raees became the father.
He sent this invitation to you
so send him answer.
He became the father
of kid, not gujrat
labours worked for you for many years.
Give them money..
File the case In court.
The indebt labour are
commiting suicide..
Did I say to die.
Think about It once again seth
I won't give them money
now you take something
for not becoming hurdle.
C.m on raees's party.
How're you..
He's rasookh bhai,
he has construction business..
He do our government work.
He drinks the liqour here,
and gives lecture on not drinking It.
I don't talk lie..
I do politics.
I understand your politics.
The election Is near,
stop this drama of oposition.
C.m sir has buy the new property.
Gave the work to construct the building.
The problem Is that,
people are living there.
People occupied the land.
Sir want you to vacat that land..
If he wants so, I'll do It.
I'll take 30% ..
I give you..
Raees mistakely called me near him,
so I could hear his heart throbe.
From here to here.
Nominated this 200 acre land.
You've did big investment.
The dream of building
housing colony.
It's the correct time
to start the construction.
So start It now.
The news Is hot, tell this to
press before It gets cold.
Raees thretened..
If
you bombed them while sitting,
go now.
Now It will be war.
Are you gone mad?
You're challenging In media.?
I didn't talk to press.
Told you not to shout.
You sell your liqour..
I'm doing my politics.
I told you not to go
through my area..
The business gets damage.
Now you understand?
Who's the daring.
Raees did what he challenged for.
Now what will you do?
Raees Is your friend,
parasha Is your enemy
police Is doing Is work.
Majmodar's transfer Is the
cause of your friendship with raees.
Raees will be In jail
In next 24 hours.
Why do I go to jal..
What about my business..
I'll give you all the arrengments.
Do your business
while sitting inside
I'll get you out
when will you say.
I'm standing with you
so late night,
Is everything allright?
I just was reminding of you
I need to win the election
for coming out
Is that so easy to win
the election
we'll need money and vote,
you arrange for money I'll get votes.
Raees did so much for people,
he won the election.
Here both sides.
Seeing the highest flats.
On the roof kids are flaying kites.
The whole sky Is covered
by the kites..
Salaam..
After many days..
Have you come to meet me
or raid on me?
In our world,
everything Is legal.
You're making colony
after selling the bottles,
your days are good.
People may have day and night.
Lions has era..
Have some tea of my world.
May your perception change.
You're the same what you
were yesterday.
Little change has occuried.
Now you can't hear the
phone call of m.l.a
I don't need to hear your phone.
Believe me, I'm not behind
your transfer.
I know.
Don't mind..
Stop your business for few days.
We can't do It.
Hindu will say stop langer..
The buden will loosen.
Did we think about hindu muslim
while doing business.
Nobody should die..
Neither anybody's langar will
stop nor our business.
I'll get the money
you controlled the violence,
now control that raees.
His own world
Is becoming everybody's world.
Tell the truth to everyone.
Or make them believe.
That everything will be fine.
Leave me alone.
I need some money,
you need alot of money.
Believe me.
I'll pay you back double interest
I can't do It on credit.
But I've a work for you..
What about that duha work?
It's final,
eijaz Is doing....stop It.
Listent to me once.
I'm receiving call from
duha, It has to send bombay
today the serial bomb blast
occured In the city..
When It blasted, people
were injured.
I know nothing sir,
I'm just an driver.
My duty was to deliver the goods.
From where did you picked up goods?
Porbander.
Whose goods was It?
Whose saying It was unloaded..
On raees.
It's big messed up, the goods of moosa,
wasn't a plastic..
It was rdx bomb.
How come It possible.
If It'd be bomb, so your
officer should know that.
It's rdx.
Moosa betrayed us.
This time police will not nab but kill.
You've to live alive to proove
that you're innocent.
If you run away so they'll kill you
sadiq Is saying right,
run away..
If I run away so police
will not let you rest.
You betrayed with me.
You said gold and bought the bomb.
You did a big virtue,
you'll go to heaven.
To killing innocents,
you can't get heaven.
I'm going to duha, come with me.
We both will be safe.
I'm not going anywhere.
Neither will let go anyone.
Kill him
sadiq speaking,
I fix up eveything.
Are you allright?
Yes..
The van Is heading toward
the house of doctor.
How many man are In van
Is raees In It..
Can't see In
target the van door,
If you're In doubt so shoot.
It can be new trick of raees.
When you knew what Is gonna
happen with you, so why you come back?
If I'd not come,
so wll you leave my men.
Has to come to save my people.
Whatever you're going to do..
Why?
What happened?
Don't you believe on system now?
Or on yourself?
If anyone call you father so?
Here's every day will be eid.
Every night will be diwali
while saving the alley,
burnt down the city
I didn't know weather I was
right or wrong that day.
But hence the question of
raees surrounds me..
Can you live with the alas
of my blood whole life?