Chest - 54.
Chest - 19 C.
Grow up.
Chest - 19.
Chest - 48.
- Chest - 51
- Chest - 52
Sing a song starting with 'M'.
Let's sing "My Girl".
- Hey, Insia has got her guitar out.
- Quiet, everyone.
- Quiet...
- quiet.
"Secretly, quietly and with care,"
"patiently I picked a twig here,
and a straw there,"
"and built myself a dream."
"With a stitch here and a knit there,
collecting little patches,"
"I quilted myself a dream."
"O dream, my dream,"
"come alive, my dream."
Insia, is this a new song?
It's really nice. Have you written it?
What are you doing here?
I have an announcement.
These are pamphlets of an inter school contest.
There's solo dancing,
group dancing, beauty contest,
and singing, too.
In every category, the winner gets a laptop
and one year of free internet!
Show me!
And one more thing,
all the best for the 1 0th grade.
Same to you.
I missed you so much.
Give it to me.
You know, on the show Singing Idol,
a little boy was auditioning.
Shakti Kumaarr was so hard on him...
it was terrible!
What happened to your eye?
It's nothing.
I opened the kitchen cabinet,
and the door hit my eye.
You're right.
I'm really stupid.
So, I was saying,
Shakti Kumaarr was so mean
that the poor kid broke down.
I am right.
You really are stupid.
Insu!
Get away!
Be quiet.
Did you get me a gift?
Are you nuts?
Two chocolates?
No.
One chocolate?
Shut up.
Not even one?
- No!
- Insia!
Have you no manners?
Haven't greeted me?
May peace be on you, grand-aunt.
May peace be on you, too.
Why didn't you get me a gift?
Get out of here!
Gift... gift. Go!
Why are you screaming at my Guddu?
- Guddu...
- Up to no good, this mother and daughter!
This one... no this one...
Good job.
So, judges, what's your verdict?
Monali-ji?
Aw, you're so cute.
- 1 0 points just for cuteness.
- Wow, 1 0 points!
What?
Cuteness?
Are we judging cuteness?
This is a singing show, Monali.
Singing.
I know my job. I'm a judge, too.
You're a rubbish judge.
He can't sing to save his life.
Kiddo, you're an insult to talent!
You're an insult to talent!
How dare you!
What do you know about talent?
Don't interrupt.
What are you looking at?
Now, get out!
Get out!
"Friends, Shakti-ji is well known
for his anger."
"And now it is rumored
that his wife left him last month."
"Obviously he's under stress and frustrated."
"Well, his marriage seems to be over,"
"after the break our astrologer will predict,"
"whether this year
Salman will finally get married."
Oh, I completely forgot,
Glamour Awards is on TV tonight.
I remembered.
Who do you think will win Best Singer?
I don't know. It's a tough one.
Best Music Composer?
Anyone... but Shakti Kumaarr.
He has never won an award in any case.
Earlier, he made such good songs.
But nowadays, when I listen to his songs,
it feels like he has remixed
some really nice song,
and that nice song never got made.
Mom... potty.
Wait for sometime.
Come.
"Let's move to the next award,
which is the 'Best Female Playback Singer'."
"And the nominees for this award are:"
"Monali Thakur..."
Sudha Venkat will definitely win.
No, Monali Thakur.
- Bet?
- Bet!
Done.
If I win, I can ask for anything.
Okay.
Mom, I'm done.
He's done.
I am coming. Push some more.
There maybe some left.
"Friends!"
"I'm tired of receiving awards."
"I'm tired."
He'll blabber on now.
"So, this time
I called Glamour Awards and said,"
"Glamour Award,
this year Shakti won't receive the award,
"he'll give it."
Mom!
- Yes?
- I'm done.
"So, here I am to give the award
for the Best Singer..."
"female."
"And the award goes to..."
"Oh!"
"To my protégé, whom I launched."
"Monali Thakur."
"Come, Mona. Come."
"Come, babes."
Wow!
What can I say!
This award means a lot to me.
Actually, it means the world to me.
Thank you so much to the jury,
to all my fans...
and to Glamour Magazine!
Keep loving me this way
and I'll keep singing such lovely songs.
Thank you so much.
Babes, you're singing quite well nowadays.
"Keep it up. I like it."
"Thank you."
"But, you've been only screaming
at little children nowadays."
"Why don't you write some songs?"
"Who are you to tell me what to do?"
"I've won the award, haven't I?"
"I think I've earned the right to speak."
"Why are you giving a speech?"
"Have you won an award?"
"You used to sing jingles for toothpaste ads,
"that's where I picked you up from.
Don't forget!"
They behave so badly. No shame.
By the way, I won the bet.
Yes.
So, what do you want?
There's an inter-school singing competition.
Can I participate?
Okay. But, don't tell your father.
But, if I get selected for the finals
I will have to go to Mumbai.
No, Insu. Then let it go.
Your father threatens
to break the guitar at every instance!
He'll never allow it.
You said I could ask for anything.
Insu, I said you could ask anything of me.
Not from life.
Listen.
I have an idea.
- What?
- Come here.
Straighten your face.
Tell me.
- Your father will return late tonight.
- So?
He'll be tired and hungry.
Ask him this question when he's eating.
He may agree.
Good idea, mom.
Which song should I sing?
Song...
Do you know what the first prize is?
A laptop and a year of free internet.
So, think of a good song.
Sing any song.
You'll win for sure.
You're my favourite singer.
Even better than Monali Thakur.
Really.
Go to sleep.
Salam, father.
Can I expect to get some water in this house?
Yes, father.
How was your trip?
It was good, father.
Did you learn anything
or did you just waste your time?
No, father. It was good.
How are you?
Salam.
Father, there's this...
Father, there is a...
There's less salt.
What?
Come here.
Just coming.
Sorry!
Should I fill my stomach with your apology?
Can a man not expect a decent meal
after working 1 7 hours?
Father...
Najma... have you packed my bag?
Bag?
Are you Najma?
Sorry, father.
You are leaving day after, right?
What did I say? When was I leaving?
On the 3rd. What's the date today?
Today is the 2nd.
What does that make tomorrow?
Sorry.
You forget the salt. You forget to pack.
Is there anything you remember?
I'm fed up of you.
Sorry, I...
Say sorry once more,
and it won't be the plate, it'll be you.
You go inside.
Mom, I think you should leave father.
He's not the right husband for you.
Then who is?
Shah Rukh Khan?
Mom, why don't you get it?
I'm not joking.
Insu, I've told you a million times.
Who will take care of us?
There's your school fees...
We can't be dependent on your grandfather.
Why grandfather?
Mom, trust me. I'll take care of us.
Really?
What's your plan, madam?
Just say yes, mom.
Tell me, isn't the destination decided first
and then the route later?
Did the chicken come first or the egg?
What?
It depends on the situation.
Meaning?
Meaning, if you want to eat chicken,
the egg comes first,
it hatches into a chicken, which you cook.
But, if you want to eat an omelette,
the chicken comes first,
it lays the egg,
which you make into an omelette.
Oh God, Insu!
You have the answer to every question.
No, mom.
But, we'll find it, won't we?
Insu, it's impossible to argue with you.
Then, don't.
Promise me.
What?
If I make a good plan, you'll leave father.
Insu...
Don't Insu me. Promise me.
Mom, promise me.
Okay... fine...
Go to sleep now... I promise.
Like a definite promise?
Alright, I promise.
A real promise?
Yes!
Bye.
Come on... quick.
Insia.
Insia!
Give me one example of irony.
Did this witch have to ask me
a question right now?
I've just got a tune.
If I answer it'll be lost.
Are you deaf?
Give me one example of irony.
Should I answer or stay with the tune?
Give me your hand.
I said, give me your hand!
Go on, hit me.
Hi!
Chocolate?
Thank you.
You are most welcome.
Guddu, open the door.
How long do you take to open the door?
Sorry... sorry.
Give it to me!
What's this?!
Mom, what's this?!
What?
I have no idea.
Where did it come from, Guddu?
Drama queen!
Mom, how much did it cost?
1 000 rupees per kilo.
Your laptop is even
more expensive than mangoes.
Tell me, where did you get so much money?
It doesn't matter.
Last night if I had put salt in the dinner,
then perhaps you would've won this
in the competition.
But, I forgot.
Tell me honestly.
Did you borrow the money?
I can't accept it. Let's return it.
Are you crazy, Insu?
There are so many things in life,
I have not been able to give you,
and nor will I be able to.
Don't rob me of the joy of seeing you smile.
It comes rarely.
Mom!
Yes?
Look, the world is so big,
and our Baroda is so small.
Is this Baroda?!
"Suddenly my eyes have learnt to dance."
"Suddenly my teeth have learnt to sparkle."
"It feels like this heart of mine
has just learnt to laugh."
"Laugh from the depths of my soul."
"Suddenly my hair has learnt to bounce."
"Suddenly my stains have learnt to vanish."
"It feels like this heart of mine
has just learnt to laugh."
"Laugh from the depths of my soul."
"Suddenly the windows have begun to tickle me."
"Suddenly the chairs have begun to tickle me."
"Suddenly every little thing
is bringing me joy."
"Suddenly the curries have begun to tickle me."
"Suddenly the flatbreads
have begun to tickle me."
"Suddenly every little thing
is bringing me joy."
- Who is this?
- No idea, mom!
Really?
What's with these dramatics
in the middle of the night?
Mom, I too want to upload my videos on YouTube.
How wonderful.
Upload your videos on YouTube,
and send it to your father in Riyadh.
You know what will happen next.
I know, mom.
Insu, it's 3 am.
Stop dreaming and go to sleep.
How is that possible, mom?
First you tell me to sleep,
then you ask me not to dream?
When I sleep won't I end up dreaming.
You tell me, why do we wake up every morning?
So that we can realize our dreams.
Otherwise, what's the point
of waking up everyday?
Mom, there is no point
to anything without dreams.
Neither to sleep, nor to wake up.
Neither to live, nor to die.
Mom, to dream is a basic right!
Everyone should be allowed this much.
Insu, how much you talk!
Tell me in one line, what do you want?
Tell me, what is your dream?
What do I want?
Mom, I want the whole world to hear my voice.
Not just school, or Baroda, or India.
The whole world should know me
as the best singer.
Not just you.
That's my dream, too.
And I'm sure it'll come true. Go to sleep now.
Let it be, mom. It's useless talking to you.
Insu.
I have an idea.
What?
What are you doing?
Wait.
Here.
What's this?
An idea.
- It's not an idea, it's a burqa.
- Exactly!
What do you mean?
- I should wear this and make videos?
- Yes.
You want the entire world to hear you, right?
Why do they have to see your face?
They should hear you.
It does matter, mom. How absurd?
It's a horrible idea.
I want to be famous
and you tell me to hide my face?
No. You don't understand.
Listen to me.
I'm not telling you to change your destination.
Just change your route.
You should allow that much.
No, mom.
It's a stupid idea. It'll never work.
To all those watching,
this is my first YouTube video.
My name is...
I can't tell you all my name.
But if you like this video please click 'like'.
"Can someone tell me, where am I?"
"Can someone tell me, where I stand?"
"Have I chosen the correct path?"
"Should I embark on this journey?"
"I fear my dreams, will they destroy me?"
"I fear those close to me,
will they betray me?"
"Am I the moon? Or the shadows in it?"
"Am I the ashes? Or the raging fire?"
"Am I the drop? Or the mighty wave?"
"Do I bring tranquility?
Or do I unleash a storm?"
"Can someone tell me, who am I?"
"Do I have a purpose?
A reason to be? Who am I?"
"Do I believe in myself?"
"Does my existence even matter?"
"Whose shoulder do I cry on, should I falter?"
"Who will guide me, should I lose my way?"
"Am I the moon? Or the shadows in it?"
"Am I the ashes? Or the raging fire?"
"Am I the drop? Or the mighty wave?"
"Do I bring tranquility?
Or do I unleash a storm?"
"Should I live my truth? Or remain silent?"
"Should I bear my soul? Or break my heart?"
"Should I cross all boundaries?
Or rein myself in?"
"Should I keep fighting? Or just give up?"
"Am I the moon? Or the shadows in it?"
"Am I the ashes? Or the raging fire?"
"Am I the drop? Or the mighty wave?"
"Do I bring tranquility?
Or do I unleash a storm?"
"Who am I?"
I knew it was a stupid idea.
What's the time, Insia?
Sorry, Miss.
Your mother put me in a fix.
I already have so many children.
I shouldn't have taken you in.
Everyone knows that
I don't take more than 45 children.
Sorry, Miss. It won't happen again.
Come, now.
Find a place.
This is broader. This is narrower.
You know why? I explained that.
1 1 73K.
And 1 973K.
Okay.
Miss, there's no other place to sit.
What is it?
You came late to class.
So, if you want any notes,
I can share them with you.
Okay.
Hey, Insia.
I added you on Facebook. You didn't respond.
- Are we friends?
- Aren't we?
Chintan.
Tell me.
Do you have the trigonometry sums solved?
Yes, I do.
You copy them. I'll wait outside your house.
Are you a doorman?
No.
You can come inside too.
Okay.
Insu.
Lay the table.
Mom!
Mom.
- Insu.
- Come here.
Calm down.
Look, mom.
This is your video!
Yes, and guess how many people have watched it?
1 1,470 people!
Seriously?
I have never even met
so many people in my life.
All thanks to this laptop.
Your idea worked, mom.
I told you, didn't I?
Now I'll be a superstar, too!
Insu, listen...
everyone knows a superstar.
You'll have to remain a secret.
Or your father will throw us
out of the house along with this laptop.
Nothing will happen, mom.
Insu.
I mean it. Your father shouldn't get to know.
How will father know?
Father doesn't watch YouTube.
Promise. Nothing will happen.
Alright.
Before your grand-aunt yells,
I'll serve dinner.
Listen.
What is it now, mom?
Father will be back tomorrow.
He's going to be home all day.
Please keep this thing shut.
Mom, when will father get that job in Riyadh?
Once he does he's out of our lives
for 1 1 months, right?
Yes, and during Ramadan
he'll be in the house 24-hours.
Only one month, right? We'll bear with it.
It's not a bad deal.
Hey, what's your name?
You are so talented.
Your videos are damn good.
Do you have a Twitter account
or a Facebook page?
So sad! You can't show your face?
How does it matter
if she shows her face or not?
What an amazing voice this child has!
Otherwise videos nowadays are
short on both talent and clothes.
You have such an amazing voice.
When do we get to see your next video?
Thank you.
You are not sleepy either?
It's 3 am.
I'm in New York. It's 5.30 in the evening here.
Mom.
Mom, people in New York are
watching my video, too.
Mom.
Salam.
- All well?
- Yes.
- How's Guddu?
- He's fine.
What's this? Where did it come from?
Brother sent it.
No one was using it at his house.
Has your brother ever sent anything new?
He likes dumping his trash here.
Aunt.
Shah Rukh Khan's film is showing.
Do you want to see it?
Since your uncle passed away,
I haven't gone to the theatre.
Shall we go, then?
That's a great idea.
Insu too, has been wanting to watch a film.
Doesn't Insia have assignments to do?
Aren't the 1 0th grade exams important?
Films, TV, guitar... stop everything this year.
And now this laptop... what use is it?
Come here.
It is very difficult to find a match
for an illiterate, uneducated girl.
I got stuck. Not everyone will.
Sorry.
Be careful.
Hello, everyone.
Thank you for your likes and comments.
Here's my second video.
This song is for my mom.
"She's a little cute, and a little stern too."
"She's a little cool,
and a little old school too."
"She's like a sweet, chilled juice,
on a hot summer day."
"She's like a warm blanket,
on a freezing winter night."
"My dearest mom."
"She's my dearest... my mom."
"When I'm troubled,"
"she's all tears."
"In my joy, too,"
"her tears wet her scarf."
"With every tear drop,"
"she weaves blessings."
"Will someone tell me, are all moms like this?"
"Sometimes she's practical,
and sometimes she's emotional."
"Her one smile, dispels all my worries."
"She's like a master key,
which opens all the locks to my fortunes."
"I've placed in her care,
all my trunks, full of dreams."
"My dearest mom."
"She's my dearest... my mom."
"My dearest, my mom."
"My dearest mom."
"She's my dearest... my mom."
"My dearest, my mom."
Chintan, does ma'am yell at you?
Yes.
She yells at me more.
Hey... shush...
Miss, I'm done.
- So fast?
- Yes.
Show it to me.
Wait a minute, Insia.
What's this?
Miss, I'll study better tomorrow,
and take the test again.
Get your mom to sign this.
Your mom pleaded with me
to take you in this class.
Taking you in was a waste of my time.
It wasn't the pleading,
it was double the fees that worked on you!
Oh, really?
Your father is the one paying me 'double fees'.
My fees come from his hard earned money.
So, get his signature too.
I'm so sorry, Miss. I didn't mean...
Go, get the signatures.
I'm sorry, ma'am. Please...
Go or I will call your home.
Get the signatures.
Miss, I'm done, too.
Insia, what happened?
Sorry.
Hey, this is you, isn't it?
What?
What rubbish?
And what are you doing here?
I've seen all your videos.
I had a feeling it's you.
Because I recognize your voice.
Everyone at school watches your videos.
Who else knows?
I don't think anyone else knows. Only me.
Hey, just a minute!
You don't want anyone to know,
that's why you wear a burqa, right?
Insu?
Chintan, please take this paper and run.
And don't tell anyone, please.
Okay. Don't worry.
I keep everyone's secrets. I never tell.
Thanks, Chintan.
By the way, can I tell you one of my secrets?
Sure.
I love you.
What?
Look... not because you are a superstar.
God promise. From much earlier. Honestly!
You must have felt it too?
You leave. I have to go home.
Should I go?
Go.
- Najma.
- Yes?
Have you taken the newspaper?
Newspaper?
The newspaper hasn't come today.
Be sure to deduct his money.
Today's not a holiday.
Yes.
"Secret Superstar."
"Anonymous, yet famous."
"Who is this mysterious girl
who won't show us her face?"
"ls this a marketing strategy?"
"If not, who is this person,"
"who has taken the Internet by storm
in barely four months?"
"Friends... you must've heard..."
Father, look at this dinosaur...
Sorry, father.
"Coco Money Singh's song
has got one million views."
"But our Secret Superstar
has got thirty million views!"
"Not just that,"
"her song 'Who am I?'
is trending number one on YouTube."
"- And Superstar Mr. Amitabh Bachchan himself
has tweeted about this song."
"This afternoon the All India committee
of the Singers' Association,"
"has boycotted music composer
Mr. Shakti Kumaarr."
"The committee is deeply upset in the way
he yelled at a small child,
"on the Singing Idol show."
"The situation now is that no singer will sing
for Shakti Kumaarr's new film."
- By the way,
- "Now, the producer will have no choice
"but to replace him."
it's Zahir's daughter's wedding tomorrow.
You have to come, too.
And there's no need to wear a burqa there.
They are very modern. They won't like it.
Guddu, you come, too.
Hi, ma'am.
I'm in love with you.
I haven't seen your face,
but I love your voice.
Bye!
Babes, I saw your video.
Hiding your face, eh?
Naughty... naughty!
You have a pretty good voice.
Not bad. You have potential.
If you want to make your future,
then call Shakti.
- Yuck!
- My number is 98200...
Couldn't AR Rahman have emailed instead?
Go on.
What happened?
Father, we had a science test.
The same? 50 percent again?
No father, this was just a test
at the extra classes.
I will study harder for the school exams.
How much did you score?
Out of?
1 00
Failed?
Yes, father.
But, this was a surprise test.
I was totally unprepared.
Had I known earlier, I would've gone prepared.
I need your signature on this.
Father, look how strictly she has assessed it.
Get me your guitar.
What?
Father, I'm sorry.
I'll study well for the school exams.
I will score 70 percent.
70 percent? You can't even pass!
I said, bring me your guitar.
Sorry, father.
Don't make me ask you again.
Don't restring it till I tell you to.
How is this connected to my exams?
Even if I don't play I could still fail!
Insu! ls this any way to talk to your father?
- Apologise.
- What did you say?
Sorry.
She's just a child. Let her go.
Are you doing me a favour by apologizing?
Sorry.
Insu.
Why are you irritating me, Chintan? Go away.
Sorry.
Knock, knock.
Say 'Who's there'.
I have a great 'knock, knock' joke.
Why are you bugging me, Chintan?
"Hi, Insia!"
"I see you're in a bad mood."
"I'm a lollipop. Why don't you eat me?"
Are you a pet dog?
Why do you keep following me?
Why are you stuck to me? What's your problem?
I've told you off four times since morning.
But, you don't understand.
Because you have no self-respect, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Extremely sorry.
You're looking like a star.
Come on... hurry up.
How much longer?
I'm coming. Just a minute longer.
Insu.
Eat your food.
And serve grand-aunt, too.
We'll be late.
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
Will you come like this?
What is it?
Your neck is looking bare.
Wear that gold necklace
your father gave you, the cheap one.
Otherwise, what will people think?
That this engineer husband
can't even buy his wife a necklace?
I don't know where I've kept it.
If I start looking for it now,
it'll get very late.
Let's go.
It's not like we live in a palace!
It's a small house.
Look for it. I'll wait.
I remember now.
It's in the bank locker.
Have you taken sleeping pills?
We gave up the locker four months ago.
Don't waste time.
Go... find it.
Actually, I forgot to tell you.
I left it at my brother's house.
You had worn it on Eid.
We haven't met your brother since.
Don't bullshit me!
Go inside.
I said find it. That's it!
Nonsense!
Come, I'll help you find it.
I'm waiting here.
Mom, you sold the necklace to buy the laptop?
What else could I do?
There was nothing else to sell.
Why did you sell the gold necklace?
What will we tell father now?
I don't know, Insu.
What should we do?
I'll say that I've kept it somewhere.
I can't find it.
Will father believe you?
I don't know, Insu.
I don't know what to say.
I'll have to say something.
There's no other way out.
I'll say I've misplaced it.
Let's try that.
I'm looking for it.
I'll find it.
Insu, look there in that box.
I must've kept it there.
Look in that box below.
Can't find it.
Sell the house next without asking me.
- Father, listen...
- Did I speak to you?
- Father, but...
I was going to tell you.
Father... listen...
Father, I had insisted...
Stand here.
Father, listen to me.
I'll definitely sell the laptop tomorrow.
And we'll buy a similar necklace.
Father, it's my fault, not hers.
Insia, take Guddu and go inside.
I'm telling you the truth.
Mom had nothing to do with this.
Didn't you hear me? Take Guddu and go inside.
Father, it's not her fault.
I'm responsible for this.
Do you want your brother to see this?
Do you?
You should definitely be seeing this
because it's all your fault.
She really had nothing to do with this.
Father...
Insu, take Guddu and go inside.
Go. Go inside.
Tell me, what else you've sold.
Don't tell me later, you sold this
and that and you forgot to tell me.
What are you looking down for?
Look at me. I'm asking you something.
Yes? I'm asking you.
Answer me.
Tell me.
Who am I? Am I a dog?
Am I your servant?
Put a leash around my neck and tie me outside.
Is this what I'm worth?
Who do you think I am?
Will you say something? Or have you gone mute?
Mistake? How? Did it happen on its own?
You must've planned it.
So you didn't plan it?
Was it involuntary?
Father, stop it, please.
I don't want the laptop. You can sell it.
I'm admitting that it's my fault.
Ah. The laptop. Where's it?
Najma.
Go, get the laptop.
Laptop.
Quickly.
Throw it out.
Why are you looking at her?
And you are the one who wanted it.
So, you should throw it out.
You are angry, right?
Because you insulted me in front of everyone?
You are the one who should be angry.
I'm sorry.
Actually that was my trick.
Trick?
Yes, I do the same thing with my mummy.
When she's in a bad mood,
I try to cheer her up.
Instead, she yells at me.
And when she does that, she releases her anger.
Then she's back to normal.
So, I thought I should use
the same trick on you.
Still... I'm sorry.
No problem.
It's okay.
Flatbread?
No, thanks.
It's the best flatbread in the universe.
Then I'll have to eat it.
How's Mr. Bachchan?
You both are now friends, right?
You read his tweet?
I read all your tweets.
And the ones by your fans, too.
That music composer,
Shakti Kumaarr has also sent you a tweet.
Call him.
You can be a playback singer in his film.
I won't call him.
Why?
He's not a nice man.
Do you know him?
No!
Then how do you know that
he's not a nice person?
I've seen it on the news.
And his wife left him, too.
So, he must not be a nice man.
My mummy left my daddy, too.
But, he's not a bad man.
My mummy told me that herself.
I'm sorry, Chintan... I didn't know.
It's okay.
It's not your fault.
Mummy tells me it's nobody's fault.
- Will you do me a favour?
- Sure, tell me.
My laptop broke.
Will you check my email?
And post on Facebook and Twitter that
I won't be uploading videos for sometime.
Some personal problem.
Okay.
And, do you want to say anything
to Shakti Kumaarr?
Insia, what's your password?
Give me a pen.
Go... sit!
Okay, students. Settle down.
For the final examinations,
25 marks will be given for the science project.
You can choose from volcano, blast furnace...
Chintan.
- Chintan!
- Yes?
Your stop.
Oh... I see.
I'll get off at the next stop.
Next stop... for sure.
What's your mom like?
Mom is like a child.
What do you mean?
You know how children are cute but so naive.
Always scared.
And very stupid.
You have to always explain
what's right for them, and what's not.
Yet they never get it.
Mom is exactly like that.
Absolutely stupid.
How do you know?
Know what?
About children.
Do you have any?
Sorry!
Sorry. I'm just joking.
Take it easy.
There are two boys. This one beats the other.
Then he sees...
Salam, father.
Salam.
How are you, child?
I'm fine.
Guddu, open your mouth quickly.
What are we celebrating?
Aunt, I've got that job in Riyadh.
In one of the Sheikh's oil rigs, there.
As a senior engineer.
Very good.
- Did you hear?
- Yes.
Here, have some.
That's such good news.
I'll make a thanks-giving prayer tomorrow
at the mausoleum.
Why not? And tonight, we'll all eat out.
You come too.
Okay, father.
Here, take.
You've grown up so much.
In these last few months, enjoy your freedom.
Then you'll have to start a new life
in a new country. Isn't it?
Did you know, Zahir's friend lives there.
He's the vice president of the company
I'll be working for.
He has a son. Razzaq.
He has a travel agency.
He also has a license for Hajj tours.
He's a good boy. You will like him.
Look. He has also sent some photographs.
You knew all along, didn't you?
That if father got this job,
we'll all have to move with him
to Saudi Arabia.
I didn't think he'd get the job, Insu.
Forget it, mom. I don't want to talk to you.
- At least listen to me...
- Mom, please.
Insu, everything will be okay.
What'll be okay?
How?
Mom, I'm telling you let's run away.
Where will we go, Insu?
How does it matter?
Anyway, in this house, no one cares about us.
He just cares about Guddu, doesn't he?
We'll leave Guddu behind.
What rubbish, Insu!
If we leave Guddu here,
he will grow up to be exactly like his father.
So what's the point of our lives?
That we make Guddu two percent better than him
What about our lives?
Insu, some things are beyond our control.
Wrong, mom. Wrong!
Everything is in our control.
There's nothing that we can't do.
I'm telling you, mom,
I'm not going to Saudi Arabia.
I'll run away.
And you shouldn't go either.
Mom, I'll plan something.
- Insu...
- Insu... Insu... Insu!
It's useless talking to you.
"Shakti Kumaarr's life has taken a new twist."
"The Mumbai Family Court
has ruled against him."
"And his wife has won the case."
"His wife's lawyer, Sheena Sabavala,
has proved in court,"
"that he has not one, not two,
but three affairs!"
"And that too, simultaneously!
Here's what Shakti Kumaarr had to say."
"Sir, you lost the case. How do you feel?"
"Bullshit. It's all rubbish."
"My wife's lawyer, that b****,
Sheena Sabavala has lied in court."
"I will appeal to the Supreme court."
"But are the rumours about your affairs true?"
- "Shut up, you B****!"
- "Sir, please, sir."
"Now, let's meet the enemy of such men,
Sheena Sabavala."
"Madam, tell us about Shakti Kumaarr's case."
"Shakti Kumaarr is an ill-mannered
and disgusting man."
"I'm very happy with the court's decision."
"It's important to teach a lesson
to men like Shakti."
"If I'm not mistaken,
this is Advocate Sheena
Sabavala's 1 1th victory this year."
"Which means, she has ruined the lives
of 1 1 men in this one year alone."
"Sheena Sabavala has a perfect track
record in matrimonial matters."
"Whether she's up against a music composer
or a mafia don,"
"Sheena Sabavala is going to win!"
Chintan.
Come.
I have some work. You carry on.
Okay.
Number?
I've saved it. It's in 'contacts'.
- But... there's a problem.
- What's the problem?
I recharge the phone with my allowance.
There's no money left on the phone,
and I'm broke.
So, I can't call?
- No. You can give him a missed call.
- A missed call?
Why will he call me back?
He will. Give it a try.
How do you know he will call back?
I have my fingers crossed!
Try once more, please.
I'm sorry.
Tomorrow I'll take an advance on my allowance.
It's okay. Forget it.
Chintan, go home.
Don't irritate me. I want to be alone.
I'm headed to your building.
My friend stays there.
Which friend?
Er... Jignesh.
There's no Jignesh in my building.
Oh, sorry.
I thought every building in Baroda
would have at least one Jignesh.
Chintan, please don't try
your tricks on me again.
Go home.
Sorry.
Insia... Insu...
the call has come. Come quick!
Hello. Shakti sir.
Sir, this is Insia.
Insia Mallik...
My videos are on the internet
- Secret Superstar.
Yes sir, the girl in the burqa.
Sorry, it's my friend's phone.
There's no money left on his phone, so...
Sir, Baroda.
Today?
Not today, sir.
Tomorrow?
Yes, sir. Tomorrow.
But sir, I have one condition.
If the recording goes well,
then you have to help me.
That, I'll tell you tomorrow.
Promise, sir?
A real promise?
Thank you, sir.
Sir, can I... can you call me
back in two minutes, please?
Thank you, sir.
He wants me to go to Mumbai tomorrow,
to record a song.
Chintan, how will I go?
- By aeroplane.
- Yes, I know.
He said he'll book the flight
and send an airport pickup.
You'll have to skip school tomorrow.
I'll give you the class notes.
And anyway you don't do your assignments.
By the time school finishes, you get back.
What if someone sees me?
You are the 'Secret Superstar'. 'Secret!'
There's one more problem.
I've never flown in a plane.
Don't worry.
I'll make a plan by tomorrow.
- Mom, come quickly.
- Wait...
- Bye, Insu.
- Wait for two minutes.
Hang on.
Your lunch box.
Your mom drops you to the bus.
So, you have to get on it.
Don't stress about the ticket,
I'll get a printout.
The bus drops us inside the school.
So, you'll have to
make your escape from school.
As soon as you reach school,
go to the girls toilet.
And, jump out from there.
- Good morning, Miss.
- Good morning.
I know an escape route.
I figured in case of a terrorist attack,
I must have an escape plan.
- Chintan, there's a lock on this!
- Lock?
Now what?
I'll think of something.
I'll be late for the flight.
It won't break!
- What are you doing?
- Wait.
You'll have to jump the wall.
Have you lost it?
Do you have a better idea?
How will I get back inside?
I have eight hours to figure that out.
I'll think of something.
Come on, give me your bag.
Put one foot here.
And one foot there.
Yes.
Land on your feet or you'll hurt yourself.
Are you okay?
Yes, and you?
I'm fine.
Listen...
Yes?
I also love you.
Thank you.
The airport, please.
Please drive faster.
At the airport, show your school ID and ticket.
If questioned,
say that your grandfather is unwell.
You travelling alone?
My grandfather is unwell.
Okay.
At the airline counter, ask for a window seat.
- Can I have a window seat, please?
- Yes, sure.
Uncle, you are on my seat.
It's a short flight. Sit anywhere.
But the window seat is mine.
How does it matter?
I'm already sitting here. You sit here.
Uncle, that's my seat. Get up!
Come!
Don't forget to wear your seat belt.
When the plane takes off, then you'll see...
how big the world is, and how small Baroda.
Your bad mood, your father, Miss Sheetal,
leaving everyone below, you will fly away.
I'll wave to you from down,
but you won't see me.
Do you need an auto rickshaw? A taxi?
A hotel? Where do you want to go?
Secret Superstar?
No.
I'm the airport pickup.
I'm Ranjeet.
Come.
Has Shakti Kumaarr sent you?
Yes, ma'am. Shakti Kumaarr has sent me.
Now, shall we? Or we'll be late.
Come on.
Unions don't operate on relationships,
but money.
Give as much as you want.
I'll call you back.
What a voice!
Wow.
My pleasure to meet you, kiddo.
You okay?
Tea? Coffee? Coke?
Coke?
What an interesting journey!
What a story!
Baroda... Burqa... YouTube...
Shakti Kumaarr... and then...
Superstar!
I'll host a launch event for you.
At a five star hotel.
Big time!
Industry, media, trade.
I'll buy the front page
of Mumbai Times for you.
Shakti Kumaarr launches
YouTube sensation, Insia!
Babes, don't mind,
but your name is low on glamour.
What does it mean? Your name? Insia?
It means 'woman'.
Oh! Woman...
Woman.
It sounds awful and it's meaning is worse.
What about Shabnam?
Too old fashioned.
Sunny?
- It's taken.
- Ah, it's taken.
Natashha!
Natashha with a double H.
N-A-T-A-S-H-H-A
That's the one!
Sir, I'm sorry
but my identity needs to remain a secret.
If my father finds out, I'll be dead meat.
Look kiddo, sooner or later the media
will find out.
Whether I tell them or not.
Anyway, we are short on time.
The song shoot is in two days.
The album releases in two weeks.
And the film, in two months.
And you have to get back to school
in six hours.
So, let's not waste time. Okay.
Ali, play the song.
"I'll speak your words."
"I'll sing your praise."
"I'll adorn myself
with the colours of your love."
"Oh, I dance wild and free,
"for you, my sexy lover!"
"O, my sexy lover!"
Ali, cut... cut.
Superhit.
It's a superhit, kiddo.
It's a gift from God... through me.
On the mic, kiddo.
Ranjeet, take her to the mic.
Come on.
- Ali, is everything ready?
- Yes, sir.
Well done.
It's a sure hit, kiddo. Superhit!
Just sing it.
Come on. Go for it.
Sir, two minutes.
Yeah, okay.
Take your time.
Let's start.
Ready. Come on.
Let's go.
Go for it, kiddo.
Not like this, kiddo.
Don't you get it?
Okay?
Cut it... cut it!
Do one thing. Start from the verse.
- We'll patch the moaning later.
- Yes, sir.
"I'll speak your words."
"I'll sing your praise."
"I'll adorn myself with the colours..."
This is not a hymn, kiddo.
Sing it with feeling.
Get the feeling of the song.
"I'll speak your words."
"I'll sing your praise."
Cut it... cut it...
Look at me, babes. Look at me.
You are making a mistake.
You are singing from your head.
Do you know where you should be singing from?
Heart, sir. From the heart.
Doomed!
She wants to sing from the heart.
You don't have to sing from the heart, kiddo.
You have to sing with your body.
- Meaning?
- Body language.
Body language. Okay?
You know what, you need to loosen up.
Open up a little.
Try jogging.
- Jogging?
- Yes.
- Where?
- Right there. Spot jogging.
Come on, I'll show you.
Yeah... come on... one... two.
Yes, go for it. Knees up...
One, two. Bounce... bounce.
One, two, one, two...
Yeah, well done. Very good.
Yeah... yeah.
Feeling better? Eh?
Come on. Very good, kiddo.
Buck up, India... buck up, India.
"I'll praise your speak. I'll words your sing."
Kiddo, give me something.
Something... anything!
Come on. Go for it.
"I'll..."
Listen, you won't be able to do it.
Ranjeet will drop you to the airport.
There's a huge difference between
singing at home, and singing in front of a mic.
Not everyone's cup of tea.
You... go back to school.
Sir.
What?
Sir, I need to use the toilet.
You know Insu, earlier,
he made such good songs.
But nowadays, when I listen to his songs,
it feels like
he has remixed some really nice song,
and that nice song never got made.
I told you she's not good enough.
But you won't listen.
As it is, no one wants to work with you.
Why are you destroying my film?
I'll find someone.
Who will you find? Should I sing the song?
Please leave this film. Spare me.
Sir...
- Sir, can you step out for a minute, please.
- What is it?
I want to talk to you in private.
What's up? What's the problem?
Sir, I feel the problem is not with me,
it's with your song.
Oh. You mean there's no problem with you.
The problem is with my song.
Wow... wow! Amazing! I like it!
That's a new one. Amazing!
Sir, I'm not a professional singer.
I can see that.
Sir, actually I'm a listener.
Ever since I was born... my mom played to me
Bollywood songs... new, old, all!
So? What am I supposed to do?
I need the song, babes.
I've no interest in your nonsense.
But you should be interested in my nonsense!
What!
I read in the news,
that the Singer's Association
has boycotted you.
Who are they to boycott me?
I boycott them. Scram! Boycott!
Sir, let me finish.
Yours is a romantic song,
but the tune is disco.
Such good lyrics,
and you've ruined them with innuendo.
It feels like a remixed version of
a great song... which never got made!
My mom says that, too.
This song should be one from the heart...
Huh?
2007. I made this song 1 0 years ago.
This is the remix version...
Party song... party song!
The producer kept asking for a party song.
I spun it around.
But, you're right.
This isn't the original.
"Your words and thoughts will flow from me."
"In your praise and devotion,
will I always sing."
"In robes weaved of your love,
I'll dress myself,"
"and merge into your colours."
"With ornaments bejeweled with your love,
I'll decorate myself,"
"and merge into your radiance."
"I dance wild and free,
adorned in you, my love."
Sir, this is what I will sing.
Exactly this way.
- You like it?
- Love it!
It's a flop.
Too slow.
Nowadays, everyone wants a fast song.
Sir, that's not true.
Have you heard the songs of Aashique 2?
Not a single fast song.
Yet they were superhits.
Ha! They just got lucky.
But...
You're smart.
So sir, let me try it once.
I'll sing it just the way you did.
The producer won't agree.
Sir, let me try once.
Not with 'body language', but from the heart.
Just once. For me?
For you?
Please.
Sir, it's a lovely song.
But can I remove the word 'sexy', please?
Shakti had put in that word. Remove it.
Ali, cancel this session.
Load the one from 2007. The old one.
I'm trying a new version. Check it out.
Sir, the slow one?
Why? Do you have a problem?
Just do what I'm saying!
"Your words and thoughts will flow from me."
"In your praise and devotion,
will I always sing."
"In robes weaved of your love,
I'll dress myself,"
"and merge into your colours."
"With ornaments bejeweled with your love,
I'll decorate myself,"
"and merge into your radiance."
"I dance wild and free,
adorned in you, my love."
resonating with you, my love."
"I've lost my bearings, the world taunts."
"I'm beyond consciousness, beyond reason,
I've lost myself, they say."
"I've lost my identity to you, they scorn me."
"But what do they know,
the mysteries of this heart."
"By losing myself, and realizing you,"
"I've found myself. I'm complete.
I'm one with myself."
"I'll abandon all ties, and come to you."
"All evil aimed at you, let it befall me."
"In robes weaved of your love,
I'll dress myself,"
"and merge into your colours."
"With ornaments bejeweled with your love,
I'll decorate myself,"
"and merge into your radiance."
"I dance wild and free,
adorned in you, my love."
resonating with you, my love."
"I dance wild and free,
adorned in you, my love."
resonating with you, my love."
Superhit... superhit!
Babes.
You've no idea how I'm feeling right now.
I feel as though this
was the first recording of my life.
You won't understand.
Sir, actually this really
was the first recording of my life.
"With ornaments bejeweled with your love,
I'll decorate myself..."
Wow.
Sir, I want to discuss something with you.
Yes, tell me. What is it?
Sir, I want your help.
Help?
I'm so sorry!
Your fees, yes. Sorry... sorry!
Your friend... Chintan?
Should I send him your cheque?
No sir, I don't want money.
I just need your help.
Kiddo, once this song releases,
you won't need anyone's help.
Producers and music composers
will line up outside your house.
Sir, aren't you divorced?
What do you mean?
Your wife has left you.
She's taken your kids, too.
Yes, so?
I want to meet your wife's lawyer.
I want to get my parents divorced.
What? Why?
Oh... I understand.
I'm sorry. I can understand.
Don't worry. I'll help you.
I'll call my lawyer right away.
Kamlesh, he's a fantastic lawyer.
No, sir. Not your lawyer.
But your wife's lawyer.
Who? Sheena Sabavala?
She's crazy.
Bad idea... bad idea.
Sir, you promised.
Yes, and I'm not refusing you.
I'm helping you. Don't worry.
He's a fantastic lawyer. Hi, Kamlesh...
Sir, your 'fantastic' lawyer
lost your own case.
Kamlesh... listen... I'll... I'll call you back.
Okay?
Bye.
Hello Sheena, it's me.
What do you mean 'Who?'
Don't pretend you don't know. Hello!
I know you're busy. I'm not free either.
I haven't called for small talk.
I have important work. Need to meet.
We'll talk when we meet.
No, this isn't about my divorce.
It's another matter.
It's about a girl...
Age...
- What's your age?
- 1 5
1 5 years.
What! How dare you, Sheena?
How can you even think like that?
You've gone crazy. You're mad!
You shut up! You shut up!
You shut up and you go to hell!
I will take you to the Supreme Court.
Yes. Bye!
I told you. She's bad news.
I tried... you saw me.
You saw what happened.
Hello, Sheena. I'm so sorry... I'm so sorry.
Listen to me. You're right.
You're absolutely right.
I am a totally ill-mannered person.
You're right.
Listen, babes, my mother! I'm begging you.
Not for me. It's for this little girl.
This innocent child.
Please.
She just needs half an hour. That's all.
Can we come now?
Next month?
No, babes, that's too late.
Next week? It's an emergency.
Next week?
Next week, good. Done.
Thank you, babes.
You're a sweetheart... sweetheart.
Witch!
Thank you, sir.
So, see you next week.
I'll send your ticket to your boyfriend.
What's his name? Yeah, Chintan.
Sir, he's not my boyfriend.
What? He's not your boyfriend?
Then, why are you blushing?
Bye.
Chintan!
Mom, all the material
I need for my project is missing.
Oh Insu! We bought it just a few days ago.
Where can it go? Did you leave it in school?
Mom, how will I complete my school project now?
Guddu, get ready for bed.
Guddu...
have you seen my glue bottle?
And my brown tape?
No?
Should I slap you?
Mom, tell him not to touch my stuff.
Guddu, how many times
have I told you not to touch her things?
I was making a gift for Insu.
There's no need to make me a gift.
Okay.
Airport, please.
Come, kiddo.
Babes, tell Sheena that Shakti is here.
She's busy.
Please wait.
Oh. Busy?
"Please wait."
Come, kiddo.
Sit.
Oh my... I'm heart broken.
No, thanks.
I'm better off "thirsty".
Come.
I'll see you now on Monday.
Come in.
Not you.
You go.
Insia, come.
Come.
So, tell me. What can I do for you?
Ma'am... um...
my father...
he beats my mother... for every little thing.
Once, mom forgot to turn on the water heater.
He broke her hand.
Babes, have you heard my new song?
Which one? Which one, 'Soft and Tender'?
No... that's old.
The new one is...
Rough and Ready'.
Look, Insia. This is a difficult case.
Firstly, Guddu and you are children.
You are minors.
You understand?
Furthermore, your mother's
financial situation isn't strong.
Anyway, I will prepare a file for you.
Take it home.
Read it to your mother
and tell her what's written in it.
Explain it to her. Okay?
And then get her to sign on it.
She has to sign all the papers.
Alright, ma'am.
The lines on your palm tell me,
there's a new love in your life.
Here.
- Thank you so much, ma'am.
- You're welcome.
Ma'am, I can't afford your fees...
Don't worry. She's a very cheap lawyer.
I'll handle it. Come.
- Bye, ma'am.
- Bye.
Listen.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you, ma'am.
No, dear. I was telling him.
Perhaps you are not as bad as you seem.
- Sweetheart... sweetheart...
- Don't push it.
Cheers.
Sir, may I ask you something?
Yeah?
Why are you helping me?
Kiddo, actually...
our stories are very similar.
How's that?
You know, in the past 1 0 years,
I've been divorced twice.
My brother sued me.
Effectively, I pretty much have no family.
This film industry
is my all... mother, sister, family.
And, this film industry too,
has never given me an ounce of love.
They nominate me every year,
but have never given me an award.
How does this make our stories similar?
Anyways...
how did you learn to play the guitar?
I was six... mom got me a guitar.
Sir, I want to shift to Mumbai. With mom.
I want to learn to sing... properly.
Then, maybe I can be
a part of Singing Idol, too.
Kids like you don't need Singing Idol.
Then how will I become a superstar?
You will become one anyway.
Talented kids like you are...
Er... how do I explain?
Are like bubbles in a soda.
See these bubbles? Rising one by one?
So?
Talented kids are like that.
They rise up like this. On their own.
Nothing can stop them.
Thank you so much, sir.
No problem, kiddo.
Any problem... call me. Okay?
And once you've reached home safely,
tell Chintan to give me a missed call.
- Bye.
Take care, kiddo.
God bless.
Bye, sir.
Mom, get down, I want to talk to you.
Not now, Insu.
Hurry up and start cutting the vegetables.
Mom, get down.
Not now. Later...
Mom, it's very important... get down.
What is it?
Sit.
Mom, I... I had gone to Mumbai.
Shakti Kumaarr, the composer,
he sent me an email.
He called me to Mumbai to record a song.
The recording went very well.
After that, Shakti sir got me to meet a lawyer.
She's a famous lawyer in Mumbai.
She has given these divorce papers.
Take a look.
Mom, please leave father.
Then we won't need to go to Saudi Arabia.
I'll become a famous singer.
And Shakti sir said that he would help.
You went to Mumbai?
When?
Last week. And today.
Mom, the plan is ready.
In a plane?
Alone?
And school?
Mom, I was going to tell you but...
Have you grown up so much,
that you'll go to Mumbai alone?
You'll get your parents divorced?
But, mom, I told you that I had a plan.
What were you thinking when you went to Mumbai?
If something had happened to you,
how would I know?
You met a lawyer, too!
What were you thinking? Meeting a lawyer?
That you'll get your parents divorced?
Did you ask me whether I want a divorce?
And what is this nonsense about divorce?
What has your father done?
Don't you know what he has done?
He beats you up all the time.
He has a bad temper.
He doesn't have control. Which man does...?
Please, mom!
What sort of life are we living?
We aren't even allowed to breathe.
Now, he will take us to Saudi.
Marry me off to someone like him.
Without even asking me.
My life will become like yours.
Look Insu, everyone has their limitations.
But I don't, mom.
Mom, trust me. I'll make everything okay.
What'll you do?
My father didn't ask me
before getting me married.
My daughter didn't ask me if I want a divorce.
No one cares about what I want.
Whatever, mom.
I won't go to Saudi.
That's it, Insu.
This is my world.
And this is your world, too!
And in our reality,
I've given you as much freedom as I could.
But, don't dream of flying beyond this. Don't!
We are going to Saudi with your father.
I won't let your education stop, I promise.
But, my dream of becoming a singer
will never come true.
Don't argue with me.
We are going to Saudi with your father.
I won't go to Saudi.
I can't believe how you can be so stupid.
Doesn't it make any difference to you?
My life will be wasted, mom.
You're such a coward that
you can't do anything for your daughter!
The gift?
It wasn't ready yet.
I'm sorry, Guddu.
It's okay.
Give it to me.
It's not done yet.
Insia, now apologise to your mother.
I won't apologise to mom.
It's her fault. Not mine.
Her biggest mistake is
that she gave birth to you.
Your father had said,
"What will you do with a girl?"
"Abort her."
Najma was adamant.
Everyone beat her up.
They dragged her to the doctor.
Then?
The doctor said, "It's late today.
We will operate on her tomorrow."
They kept her in the hospital all night.
Didn't you say anything?
I constantly wonder
why my mother didn't abort me?
What good has my life been?
And mom? The operation?
Next day, when we went to the hospital,
your mother had escaped.
1 0 months later, when she returned, with you,
she said, "Next time if it's a girl,
we could abort."
"Let's keep her. This is my Insia."
Where was I born?
And where was mom?
How does it matter?
It's your mother's fault, not yours.
Why should you apologise?
Listen.
Najma never wanted you to know all this.
Don't tell her you know.
Understand?
But...
The joy I'm getting in telling you this,
is nothing compared to the joy
your mother gets in keeping this from you.
"This great big world suddenly seems so small."
"I took flight only to crash
into a glass ceiling."
"O my heart, stop insisting."
"Lock your cage from within,
along with your dreams."
"O my heart, stop insisting."
"Lock your cage from within,
along with your dreams."
Kiddo, I've spoken to Sheena.
There are many ways.
You can lodge a complaint with the police.
There's a children's organization here
which can help you.
There's Sheena. There's me.
You don't need to waste your life.
Sir, my mom didn't give up on me.
She fought for me.
It's my turn now.
How can I desert her?
But...
what about you, Insia?
Why are you wasting your talent?
"O my heart, stop insisting."
"Lock your cage from within,
along with your dreams."
"Secret Superstar!"
"Friends, a few months ago,
a mystery girl wearing a burqa,"
"uploaded her songs on her YouTube channel."
"These videos became so popular that
"even celebrities and politicians appreciated
and shared them."
"But a few weeks ago,
"this YouTube channel went dormant.
No more songs!"
"There was silence
on her YouTube, Facebook, Twitter pages."
"Come Back Secret Superstar'
pages began trending,"
"and all her fans were upset."
"But today, there is reason to rejoice."
"Because our Secret Superstar has
set foot into the world of Bollywood."
"Let's talk to Shakti Kumaarr about her."
"Sir, tell us something
about the Secret Superstar."
"There's a pain in her voice that
stems from her heart."
"Her eyes have a passion that
transcends into her voice."
"She's blessed by Jesus.
She's a gifted child... gifted!"
"What's her real name?"
How does it matter?
Her voice is real!
"Will she sing more songs for you?"
"God willing!"
'I dance!'
"Your words and thoughts will flow from me."
"In your praise and devotion,
will I always sing."
"In robes weaved of your love,
I'll dress myself,"
"and merge into your colours."
Insu...
Mom, no more dreams for me.
Isn't school over?
No, father.
Today is the last day.
When are your exams starting?
From the 5th of the next month.
- And when do they end?
- On the 20th.
Alright. I'll book the tickets
for the 20th itself.
Start packing.
Don't leave anything for the last minute. Yes?
Bye.
Hi.
Shall I write something?
Are your tickets booked?
Insu.
Shall we go?
Bye.
Auntie, just a minute.
I'm Chintan. Insia's friend.
The 'pav bhaji' lunch that
you sent that day was amazing.
I never let Insia eat. I finished everything.
Will you have ice cream?
No.
Auntie, today is the last day of school.
So, if you don't mind,
can Insia and I go for ice cream?
We'll be back in 1 0 minutes.
Promise. Please?
Please?
Go.
- Thank you, auntie.
- Huh?
Go.
Come.
Go!
Listen.
Father has gone to Ahmedabad.
He'll return late at night.
You can stay out longer, come back by evening.
Come.
Babes, your song has become a superhit.
Yes, sir. I've seen it.
It keeps coming on TV.
And mom has bought the CD.
- There's more good news.
- What?
Glamour Awards has nominated you.
- Best Singer.
- What? Really?
And me, too.
Wow, sir.
I can't believe it.
When is it?
On the 20th. In Mumbai. You should come.
No, sir.
I won't be able to come. You know that.
But, you will surely win the award.
Ha! Fat chance.
No, sir. Don't say that.
You'll surely win.
Listen.
Don't forget about me when you go to Saudi.
Keep in touch.
How can I forget you?
You've done so much for me.
- Thank you.
- God bless, kiddo.
God bless.
Don't be sad.
You are anyway the best singer.
And you, best friend.
Thank you.
Let's celebrate today?
What?
I read on twitter...
"Don't cry it's over, smile it's happened."
- You read this on twitter?
- Yes.
Who tweeted it?
Break up Quotations.
"At 7.30 in the morning..."
"At 4.45 in the evening..."
"When the first rains fall..."
"When the summer holidays come to an end..."
"Sometimes in joy... sometimes in sorrow..."
"and sometimes for no reason at all..."
"I'll miss you. I love you."
"Whenever I pass by your house..."
"I'll wait a little for you."
"I know, I won't see you there."
"I know, I'll end up getting delayed."
"When I have tea and cookies in the morning..."
"When I have cold coffee in the evening..."
"When your birthday comes by..."
"When my birthday comes by..."
"31 st December, 14th February,
Festival of Nine Nights..."
"I'll miss you. I love you."
How was the exam?
Good.
I'm going to Mumbai.
For the Glamour Awards.
Shakti sir has kept a pass for me.
I'll miss you, Chintan.
I'll miss you, too.
"I'll miss you. I love you."
"I'll miss you."
Sir, load this too.
Careful.
I need to use the toilet. Hold this.
Watch the luggage.
Ma'am, please come.
I...
Please come, ma'am.
Madam, my husband has gone to the toilet.
He'll be back in two minutes.
No problem. Please step out of the queue.
No... please check these.
Mom, don't worry. I'll take care of it.
From here to Mumbai, then Mumbai to Riyadh.
You'll get the boarding passes to Riyadh
at the Mumbai International airport.
You'll have to check in your bags again
at Mumbai airport.
Okay.
I have another request.
These three seats together.
And these two seats behind them.
Okay, ma'am.
Done?
Come on, then.
It happens every time.
Someone takes my window seat.
Excuse me.
- Hello.
- Yes.
That's my seat.
So sorry.
Come, take the window seat.
"Monali Thakur, Sudha Venkat, Geet Singhal,
have been joined this time,"
"by our first time nominee, Secret Superstar."
"For the beautiful song..."
- Secret Superstar sings really well.
- Yes.
She'll definitely win the award.
Yes, she should win the award.
Where are the rest of the passengers?
Hello!
Why don't you dive into the television?
Come on.
Guddu, move to the side.
Stand here or you'll get hurt.
- Sir, this needs a fragile tag.
- Okay.
- These two, too.
- I'll do it. Don't worry.
Sir, you have extra baggage.
You'll have to pay for it.
What rubbish?
Every bag is under 25kgs.
I weighed them myself.
Sir, it is not about the weight.
You have an extra bag.
You are allowed 1 0 bags
and you've checked in 1 1.
How much will I have to pay?
Sir, 4,500.
What's this?
Where has this come from?
It's Insu's guitar.
So? Are we taking her there to play the guitar?
When will you both stop obsessing
over the guitar?
Insia... pick up the guitar...
yes... and dump it in the dustbin over there.
There is no need for a guitar there.
You think I'll pay 5,000 rupees to carry junk?
Listen...
Insu has nothing but her guitar.
We are carrying so much anyways, please,
let's take her guitar too.
It's not a guitar, it's junk.
The same junk that's in both your heads.
It's not junk. It's Insu's guitar.
If you say the word 'guitar' once more,
you have no idea,
how hard I'll slap you right here.
Get it?
In fact, it's not even a guitar.
It's Insia's dream.
And without dreams
there's no point to anything.
Neither to sleep, nor to wake up.
Neither to live, nor to die.
To dream is a basic right.
Everyone should be allowed this much.
Have you lost it?
I've told you once that
the guitar will stay here. That's it!
Alright.
The guitar will stay here.
Along with Insu...
Guddu...
and me.
We are not coming to Riyadh with you.
Sorry.
Hold it!
There are cameras everywhere.
If you hit me,
we'll take the footage from security
and upload it on YouTube.
Insu has a channel on it.
Haven't you seen it on TV? The burqa clad girl.
Who sings, plays the guitar.
She has millions of fans.
They'll all see you.
Before any of this happens,
it's best that you go to Riyadh.
Enough is enough! Stop this nonsense.
I'm your husband.
You can't move from here without my permission.
Hold this, Insu.
What's happening? Can't you hear?
Can't you hear or have you gone deaf?
Why are you opening this bag?
What's this?
What file is this?
Can't you hear me? I'm talking to you.
Look...
What are you doing?
What file is this? What are you signing on?
What are you signing on?
What's this?
I can't read. You can.
It's written here that
if I complain to the police...
you'll be arrested.
You'll definitely lose the children.
I might get your house, too.
If you get arrested,
you'll lose your job in Riyadh.
And your life will be ruined.
Why take the risk?
It's best you go and leave us alone.
Come on, Insu.
Sir, are you checking in?
Shall I prepare your boarding pass?
You are blocking the queue.
Are you going or not?
Excuse me, sir. I'm talking to you.
I can hear you!
I'm not deaf!
Najma!
Where are you going?
Listen to me.
The passports and luggage are lying there.
Insia, explain to your mother.
It's all about the guitar, right?
We'll take the guitar along.
Listen, I'm ready to take the guitar.
Madam, once you step out,
you won't be allowed back in.
What could be better?
Najma!
Listen to me!
But, mom...
what will we do now?
Where will we go?
Madam, may I use your phone to make a call?
It's very urgent, please.
One call.
Thank you so much.
Insu.
Call Shakti Kumaarr.
It's the night of the awards, right?
Let's just go there for now.
We'll figure the rest later.
When will they be here?
Any minute.
How are you?
Ms. Mom, I'm very happy to meet you.
Fantastic!
Shakti's entry.
Hold it.
Where are your passes?
Don't you recognise her?
No.
Wait.
Oh! She's the YouTube singer.
Ma'am, I love your songs!
- One selfie, please?
- Yes.
Yes, of course.
Let's get on with what we've been paid for.
Let's move on to the awards.
And to present the next award
for Best Singer - Female,
please welcome on stage,
the dashing, the melodious - Shaan.
Can't wait to open this envelope.
So, ladies and gentlemen,
the award for
the Best Singer - Female goes to...
Monali Thakur.
What?
- What rubbish!
- Congratulations, Monali.
It's all rubbish.
It's... all rigged.
Nonsense!
- Congratulations, Monali!
- Thank you so much.
Ever since I was a little girl,
and used to sing on stage,
I had just one dream.
To win these awards.
And every time I'm in the audience
and the nominations are announced,
I always wish that I win, not anyone else.
But, this time...
something didn't feel right.
Today, amongst us,
there's a new star.
And compared to her voice,
my voice seems to pale.
Secret Superstar...
if you're here amongst us today,
please come up, and collect your award.
Because I...
I can't accept this award.
Go on.
Go.
Go. They're calling you.
- Come on.
- Insu, go.
Secret Superstar, are you here?
Is the Secret Superstar there?
Secret Superstar...
Go.
Are you here?
She's here.
The Secret Superstar is here.
Put a spotlight on her.
Give her a big hand.
Move the jib! Cameras on her!
- Insu, go.
They're calling you.
Go.
Claim your window seat.
You all think that I'm the 'Secret Superstar'.
But, I'm not.
I was six years old...
mom got me a guitar.
How?
She stole money from father's wallet.
She had a necklace.
Her last one.
She sold that and bought me a laptop.
Father wanted to end my story in my mom's womb.
But she didn't let it happen.
My mother has written my story.
As she does today, too.
Singing songs, winning awards,
has always been my dream.
But, some people aren't allowed to dream.
The freedom to dream...
my mom gave me that, too.
So, who's the superstar here?
Me?
Or my mom?
Mom...
You are not stupid.
You're a genius.
You are not a coward.
You're a fighter.
You aren't childish at all, mom.
You are the world's best mom.
"She's my dearest... my mom."
"My dearest mom."
Friends,
this is Shakti Kumaarr's first YouTube video.
And I dedicate it to the Secret Superstar,
whom I launched!
So, presenting my new song...
fresh off the block... recorded yesterday.
Brand new.
Enjoy!
"Hit it!"
"I'll speak your words."
"I'll sing your praise."
"I'll adorn myself
with the colours of your love."
"I'll dance like you."
"I'll sway like you."
"I'll adorn myself
with the jewels of your love."
"I dance wild and free..."
"I dance wild and free, for you,"
"my sexy lover."
"O, my sexy lover."
"Go for it!"
"Let's go."
"Everybody in the house,"
"shake, shake, shake."
"Shake your booty... come on."
"Very hot, whiskey shot,
got me high without a sip."
"I'm doomed now, left to lay in the fields."
"I've got cash, you've got lips,
let's meet and party hard."
"Tandoori... Manchurian...
I'll have a go at them both."
"I search for you."
"I search for you, everywhere, my sexy lover."
"O, my sexy lover."
"Give it to me!"
Superhit! It's a superhit!
If you enjoyed the video, click on 'like'.
And if you didn't, then change your taste!
Love you.