The website of Bollywood Won
Bollywood1.Xyz / Info / Org / Net
The Best Indian Cinemas with Persian Subtitles in Bollywood Van
Intagram Bollywood Van
Instagram.Com/Bolly1official
India
East India came here for business
But now it is ruling
Many areas dominate
People are getting theirs
But Ronak Poor soil is still free
We need to look after our home
Who's this?
guess
... The most beautiful and the most evil girl of Ronak Poor
Ok ...
what are you doing?
I'm dandoned
Two of my two tears broke out in the ceremony
Do not come yet
Who's this?
Khodabakhsh
what about me?
You and your mother rest
... Slam is on his own
I and God protect the territory
Let's go to the protector's house now?
.Not
Let's go to your mother
Your dungeon breaks down
Do not be so scared of your wife
come here
Bad to me
Do not break my sex
- Get out of here, old man
you're welcome
- I do not care
Are you looking
Sir
See all my stuff I'm killing
Say from the government
They have the right to do anything
The company's ruling is not worth it here
And will not
Get lost to Gorton from here
And do not go again
Get away
What did you say
.Not
If it was so dangerous
Why did you send your slam with khadabakhsh?
It was important
Khodabakhsh is a fighter
The name is just a kid
My son is
What was needed?
... If you do not spend your time now
I'm coming to the end ...
Khodabakhsh and Aslam with twenty people
To help go to Diegapur
But still do not go
... There is no use for now
!Friends
We need to turn to the company as soon as possible
And overcome them
... if we do not do anything now
Like all other cities
We will also become their bearer
Tomorrow is the flag in the company's area
Raise up
Sir
See you sooner
... Treat them like a guest
... But if I mention, understand it
They are not guests
They are enemies
Hello dear Mirza
I'm ashamed of you at this time of the night
Your dear friend, Mr Clive
how can I help you?
Thinking about your friend?
You have a friend name
Slave sells
We are the merchant, Mr. Mirza
Sales are ours
... But Nitta is governed
...in the future
The main rulers will be businessmen
Are you a futuristic one?
I'm not an opportunist
Opportunity and truth
I recognize
Really?
You like the words of the lyrics
You hide something
Just like your cup of tea
That's a good smell
.... We also have that and that
There is a bar
And the great truth is hidden in this poem
... in the two-day dinner
.... In the evening without the moon
"Riding on a horse, a person to punish sinners"
... This poem is more than poetry
It's like a deception
The last poem of this book is my son
Slam wrote
And this poem is written against you
This book was pre-slam
When your hand is
It just means one thing
That my son was martyred
... Dice is yours, Mr. Mirza
I'm so well ...
So I want to get something done
Slam
.Father
Friendship with us, Mr. Mirza
It's not good with us
... got what you wanted
Now let's release my son ...
.Sure
.the freedom
Khodabakhsh
! Yeah
!Father
Intagram Bollywood Van
Instagram.Com/Bolly1official
"Indian killers"
Translator: Yassin
Eleven years later
Ram Clavan, putting it down
Until I said I would not be above
This is how it belongs to the company
To pass each person should
Pay taxes
For each person one
How many are you
Forty? Forty people should do this
! Hey West!
! Vesta!
Do not see any problems?
You have to pay a bad tax
Tax?
The company is on the ground
Everyone wants to cross, you have to pay taxes
. For each person one
Lady or master?
What
.... When both the master and the bearer are going to die
What does it cost?
Lord lord
Well, you gotta get my money from my lord
Who are you?
Great diamonds, all the best
Navab Fardeddin, Hakim al-Din
Great lord
Give it to her somebody
I'm sorry
What's so rude?
Get the money from the donkey
Take me to the canyon to count your hands
Mr. Inspector
Sometimes it's not something you can imagine
And that's not what you see
See, this is our master
And we are her boyfriend
You do not see, but this is the master
And since the company has come
It's a lot of lords
They are all donkeys
But it will not be known
Mr, ah, a wonderful word
"Your letter is correct"
"But my servant is right"
... they are cunning
Where is this master
Master Champoor is a gentleman
... He trusted the company now
It should be a move away from its own region,
What do they say to her, tax
You need to pay taxes
Come on, sir
We are late
I'll give her a share
!Excellency
. I do not accept charity
I'll pay for it
I'll be with you
I delight you
The path is so short
That you do not know
There is a bad guy
what is your name?
Flying sailor
Village of Gopalpur
Kanpur district, Awad
I like that kind of food
Eat your finger too
Evil Fiery
Do not you have a better thing?
Listening to these angels is always between
But if you have a chance
Fairy comes along with her
Do not throw it, loathe it
Then go to the card
This thief is very new
Forget the ring
Dying for yourself
Otherwise, take a serious shot
To be seven passengers
Five rupees per rupee are 35 rupees
35 I will show you a beautiful silver coin
. And one way to tax the route
Are you kidding you?
The procedure is the same
I had to get along with them
Keep it up
32 to
We're going to pay the price
Be ridiculous
28 I will not see more a century
I'll get 30 and the other two bags of rice
See you are everyone
Yes
Finger on her words
I said twenty to give you a thief
One was not enough
The card has good numbers
For each killer I will get 10
For this twenty to 200 coins
We had 100 coins
Mr., see you all this bug
I've compromised myself
Maybe you have to say: Come on, this is your 100th
And this is 100 coins
all right
Keep waiting for the boss
...Excellency
I do not expect death
... the sooner I have to go to Rasoulpur
Where's that gonna be?
No news, sir
My grandmother died
I promised you
So I did the job first
But doing it is with me
!OK
come and get it
!Grand mother
Grandmother, where did you go
... dear master, remember
For grandma, a little charity
Always coming to us
let's go
No way
look there
what has happened?
We do not allow them to come
Have a receipt? Yes
I did not write anything about it
What are the gadgets
Mirror
!that's beautiful
Singh's verdict
Captain
We must move now
Orum Dadash
Take you to the ship
Come on fast
Intagram Bollywood Van
Instagram.Com/Bolly1official
What is this coat?
Is Hindu
Is our enemy
His name is Freedom
Freedom, Freedom, Freedom
I'm tired of hearing this name
He throws a thunder to him
Threatens you in our territory?
Sir, do not worry
I end up doing this free
For you, freedom is just an outlaw
There is a killer for us
I do not know why people are so respected
how about you ?
We heard that it was free from the biggapour
Much help?
These are rumors, sir
The great lord knows that
We are so loyal to them
You must help us in this war
We will respond with fire
Forget about freedom
... if someone calls him a bad name
Directly goes to jail
Thankful
Thank you, for this fight
We need guns and guns
You just give us this
Sure
Thank you very much
It can be a gun and gunpowder
Let's go ahead
I doubt my sermon
I doubt everyone
... but to hunt milk
We have to bite the sheep
The people of Freedom are the Messiah of Messiah
And the hunting of Christ with sheep is not feasible
No other animal in your mind?
His figure is like human beings
But their work is like wicked animals
And his behavior is different
There is nobody but friv
Get out of it
apology
Soon, Soraya Jan
Soraya Jan
What are you doing soraya
The white men are waiting to wait
What do you think of me today?
hit
Bounce again
But if I tell the truth
It wakes up
My grandmother died
What would I do?
Oh my God! Grand mother?
I loved her very much
.Sure
For the one that has the fourth one
Miskhish, Hermit
Have you already killed the grandmothers?
Your mother was in bad condition too
You just changed the name of Haro
What are you doing sorry
I'm coming now, aunt
Where are you going to rush
... the company has requested
That's good today
... just dance for foreigners
...Only
...what about me
The command is captain
... that if it's a mistake too
... Take a Hindustan there
If I say this is Indian Hindi
Just what's your reason for you?
Do not say that heart, dear sir
Do you really love real dai
For a lover in your closet
... Everyday, I'm going to be here
And the silent, interrupted and gone
... Such people are crazy
... I'm not open
Lover that without fear of the whole world
She expresses love, she is in front of everyone
You do not have hope
!Sir
Bring me liquor
A presentation of Bollywood Wave
Translation and Scheduling: Yassin
"... you are the mistress of the English"
"... you are educated for love"
"Do you have a trial like me?"
"... you are the mistress of the English"
"... you are educated for love"
"Do you have a trial like me?"
"In the pacemaker of my heart, you are a deadly bit"
"You are the beginning and end of my beautiful song"
"Soraya Javan takes me"
"Soraya is up to daddy"
"Threesome you take my life"
"Soraya Javan takes me"
"You arrive at Soraya's house with a crooked look"
"Look at you, what more do you want?"
"I've been singing the traditional song, Jigertoo I've Been"
"Do not you want to have a kid too"
"Do you want to give Soraya your hand too?"
"Soraya is up to daddy"
"Threesome you take my life"
"Soraya Javan takes me"
"Do you want to give Soraya your hand too?"
"... from my point of view, they are all equal"
"What is the general who is the soldier?"
"All the tricky guys"
"Soon I love my love"
"Make any mistake in life"
"Soraya Usuve With A Smile"
"You're going to go up there"
"Show yourselves to God"
"Change yourself a little Soraya"
"Be All Beyond Soraya, Fear God"
"Is it your heart of Senge, Soraya?"
"All of you got your name in your name"
"Do you want to kill these guys from India now?"
Thierry and Hutchinson
My work is gone
"Soraya takes her, be sure"
You are singing between 200 English singers
And you do not get arrested
How did you think that?
The name is Furangi
I am from the inside
Outside, it's a little Indian
Have a picnic?
Did you think I'm having a drink right now?
I'm downhill
Is allowed?
... free
Did you hear his name
Sir, I am your messenger
... Getting the killers is not a problem for us
But it's free
It's not up to us to fall into it
Fringe, you've gotten a very aggressive two-year-old
How long are you looking for these ten twenty coins?
Think big, think carefully
One predictor said that
I'm going to be a stranger
I have to see England once, sir
One, two, did something
Three and four tenths, happy night
I wanna go to english
This is my dream
Let me know
Ten thousand gold coins
There is a house next to the pond
And forty acres of agricultural land
I see you started the program
When you gamble
You must also take a big risk
.Chapter
Say hello, I want some help
When
Land, wind, water
And monsters, they all have their own language
We do not understand their language
But I know such a person
That's the language of this thing
Where is ?
Where more people get stuck
There is bad news in the way
Good news?
Treacherous
I do not want to flutter
Shut up
Dirty Hindi
Hello sir sanicher
Fiery
A friend of a childhood
I hope you do not explode
... I have not seen you for years
The end of our visit was the same time
You got me in this prison
Your face is in front of me
Forget Harry's Comrade Past
why not?
Let's forget all the past
What do you want to forget about now?
How did you throw me in jail?
Or have you escaped with your fiancé?
We did not escape. Comrade
We just changed the weather
He wanted to give him a little distance
I swear to my grandmother
The treachery of my friend was in my horoscope
So when thirteen years old
I fast at night
I prayed so much to get rid of this curse and doom
... Sannicher
... I've been your friend for many years
I know a little cheater
.. I do not do it
But I value my friendship
The value is low
But it is
Come join us for the last time
You want to give me a headache
I dreamed for you
I live it
... land, capital, bride
The coin and the coin are ...
That's the way
What's the job
Finding free
Evil Baba
Live live alive I'm going to grave
I think so big, Mr. Santicher
With my wisdom and your thoughts
We will love and live for the rest of our lives
Eul Baba
Fiery, this time we are not deceiving
Okay, Dad, I'll swear to my grandmother
Bring wine
Happy
Shed
Drink gods
In the old days, the gods are shabby
Britons are now eating
Gods today they are
Yeah
We have come to find freedom
Do not drink wine
Sounds sad in the north
Goes south of the penguin
... according to my signs
Our goal will be in the south
By crossing the waterway
This is the saying of the stars
The ship goes to the Viking
We'll get there
And free with hot tea
Welcomes us
He says, say, eat tea
We will arrest you if you do not
My job is to find it, so do it
Your work and white skin too
Arresting him
Give it a little bit to the baby, please
Very feverish
Do not stop it
!drink
Please forgive me
what are you doing?
Tell your captain
It's coming
You cursed
Then straight into hell
!leave me
We're done
Fire
Go
Hide somewhere
Hide
Attack
!Fire
!Attack
You wanted freedom, I found it
Where are you going?
Your thinking and my cleverness
!you alive
I told you
You were sleeping well
Now that you wake up is better
Jaythin Bey, Doctor Degree here
He has any pain
As well as the whole wine
The last night is still in my head
... Draw today too
You're all set yourself apart
Did you find a new friend?
We are free in the hide
This is the only way to save
What was your anesthesia for four days?
I had to be friends
And tell them the courage of my supporter
Bring it here
Take it there
What is your name?
We got the spy
What information did the UK follow?
Do you know what the spy punishment is?
I'm wrong, sir
I got a baby
excuse me
Your job
Kelim
Akbar and Gopal
All martyrdom
Everyone was for you
The knight for Clive blinded you
That you are after selling your brothers too
You're not ashamed again
Your soul is captured by this man
I must give it up today
Liberty
Free
We are now responsible for protecting our family
You've done a lot of courage
Jan Maro saved you
Well, take care of him
The first bartech
Otherwise you kill people
But you will not save them
I liked it
It's too late for another one
Find a good day
This is my mistress
Believers have saved you
what is your name?
where are you from?
Fingerprint
Village of dwarara
Fateh Pour Sikri, Agra region
But now everywhere I can live
... let's lead you
Find your route as far as you can
Thankful
Do not
Thank you, you gave me a new life
From today's new life and my dignity
Everyone is at your disposal
I'm tired of being a nurse
I want to be free
To stay free
Do you know who to make a deal with?
... I chose from your ship on your behalf
It's when they have the English
They were drowning in water
It is true that the name is foreign (foreign)
But I will not play the game
Are you scared?
Honestly, we're afraid of anything
But be with you
We also learn courage
I'll learn you very quickly, sir
From the rest of the time, you are also liberating
take this
!Excellency
I do not see the girl I saved
You still wake up?
I told you to sleep
I wanted to sleep
... but that's it
... this is not going to sleep
... when you were born
Mr. Mirza gave me this
... and told me
"Protecting Dafai from today is your duty."
.I know
Do you feel I still need to protect?
No, no, no
But this show did not spoil me for sleep
Do you want to be awake for the rest of your life?
... One day I close my eyes
And I sleep in full comfort
I fall so deep into sleep
I do not wake up with no sound
Even if i give you my voice?
... with your voice
I'll be back in hell
Baba
I'll give you this very day
... in the courtyard of the house
Pine tree ...
My little girl ...
A good place to hide somewhere
But a road should be here
The sea is here
.. I knew from the beginning
You want to grab me
What did you look for
A way out of here?
I was doing with you
I would be outrageous
I'm also awesome
how are you ?
I do not trust you
Two reasons
One, that I'm so sweet
It tells me all
The second is Khodabakhsh
Also known as Freedom
what do you mean?
I feel there is a problem between you
Maybe you want to be a leader of the group
Khodabakhsh also trusted me
But you are
I feel like you betray me
The truth is that you do not trust me
I put the weapon on my shoulder and put it
It's free
Why do not you trust me?
Foolish girl
Next time, such a thing goes to the mind
I'm rolling my neck
Ok, I do not mind
I close my mouth
The discussion is over
what did you say?
I heard that bypassing the seven seas
If you save the lives of someone
Eternal friendship arises
The day you die for liberation
The friendship itself arises
I do not think so for my father
Why do you want energy?
Nothing grows on this land
- if so what?
Two years old has not grown, how is it now?
I put it right there
Eat hungry
Thirsty Drink
Is this free too?
Farming is all of us
I lost my land
Instead of plowing the soil, I got a sword
It's as if someone does not trust your agricultural power
I can help?
-Not
This is my job
I just do it myself
What did you plant now?
Royaam
Free dream
Freedom that I believe
I want people to have a good power
I say that there is no need to be dare to get involved
We should be happy a little
What happiness is higher than freedom?
How do you want to change your loneliness?
Change one
Everyone changes
Of course, if the human is so close
In every human's life
... At least one opportunity to get that
Which will cross its weakness
And toward luck
And bless the best
Change his personality
Get better off of yourself
I believe in that
I do not know how to handle you
Or are you scared?
This is my fear of you
Why?
Because i trusted you
Are you garb
You are an enemy
... But when I look at you, I feel
I see a worrying man
Looking for something
It will follow its path
Find a free one
Maybe I'll be your free bridge
And it only tells you the time
That you are my greatest discovery
. Or my biggest mistake
Think it
.I thought
Translator: Yassin
A presentation of the Bollywood Web site
"Before midnight, it's torn"
"A Night Made of Arabic Stories"
"The melody is just like a fingernail"
"Devil's Night"
"Look at the glow of the mountain of light"
"It's also fantastic ... Evil my friend"
"Gone with wine"
"Now is the best chance to go missing"
"Everywhere the enthusiasm has grown"
"Do not have the pleasure until the morning."
"Give the drum a shot"
"Rejoice Comrade, Rejoice"
"Everywhere the enthusiasm has grown"
"Do not have the pleasure until the morning."
"Give the drum a shot"
"Rejoice Comrade, Rejoice"
"Judge says drinking forgiveness"
"But drinking for me, after all,"
"No one here is my friend and friend"
"Your drink is a twenty-odd friend"
"When we drink, we feel a king."
"What sound is it that we are not calling again?"
"Even if there's no sound, we'll make it rhythm"
"Mistakes in drinking are forgivable"
"Hello to the sun before sunset"
"For Drunk, the Sunset is Likewise"
"We make so mistakes that stupidity"
"Now you know me, I'm all about it."
"Everywhere the enthusiasm has grown"
"Do not have the pleasure until the morning."
"Give the drum a shot"
"Rejoice Comrade, Rejoice"
"Everywhere the enthusiasm has grown"
"Do not have the pleasure until the morning."
"Give the drum a shot"
"Rejoice Comrade, Rejoice"
Where are we going
A realm of this close proximity
Helps us secretly
King of the Circumpolar, Sir Samangar Singh
Our help is ours
For the English speaking, it breeds opium
... our troops
Have a lot of courage
But they have little weapons
Today we compensate for it a little
All the paths end there
Get scattered
No one should understand
Which is free in Garagaur
Somebody gave him a gift
Do you remember what you mean?
How can i forget, honey
But what do you do among people?
I do not trust the syndrome
So I'm worried
I see! Ok go me
Finger!
Did not you get any news?
... the news I do not have
But I found a free man
I just have a request
Blood and bleeding
Get your business and office
And make sure I can escape
After pointing me
You run away
I am the only one who
I know you are working for us
Unreasonable martyr Nashi open
I am not ready to be martyred by my father
Where is freedom
Sangram
My brother Khodabakhsh
I finally met with you
How are you guys
I got a gun and a gun
Now let's make you cool
Destruction disappears
Your friends are yours
Liberates himself
The sooner you have to fight
And eliminate Clive
Sick, we're miserable
Soldiers Understanding us here
What are you doing sangram
You listen
For my friend, I'll give you that
Do not go out
... but the sigram
This is the safest place for you
I'm coming back to them
Intagram Bollywood Van
Instagram.Com/Bolly1official
We got into trouble
Saw, we were surrounded by four sides
I would not be like that
I was surprised
How much did you sell me
Do you miss your time?
I'm deceived in my blood
And your trust is my blood
From here, one survives
What did you think
God?
Do you think you can change the fate of someone?
Or herself?
There is nothing in this world
I can not make myself a better guy
I do not need it
I'm working
I'm happy
Do not look that way
Nothing, nothing changes
No, I'm not you and not my destiny
Some people can not stop the company
I do not accept slavery
surrender
Stay alive
!look there
You thought you came
Who will capture Maro alive?
!Fire
Khodabakhsh
! Yeah
Come back to me, my doll
Come on ahead of me
Come on in the silver or silver apron
Good for a few days
... but you will not be injured in your wound
It will not be good forever
We should not leave now
Have a calm for a moment
Sleep, pride and smile
We take it all out
... I swear to God
... I do not rest from now
So when Clive is in black soil
. She wants to enslave her soul
We release her from life
Liberty
Free
How are you doing it
Ram Clavan, okay?
Hello sir
What are you up to here, Fyrgy?
I came to win my prize
I do not see you coming
So you are your avatar
!my Lord
I'm your sweetheart, sir
Between flattery and respect
There is a lot of difference
I'll make Hero Taro, sir
Honestly, our main goal
See you here
You will receive a prize
do not worry
I have to go now
I know, sir, you made a great celebration
But I have some news
You are astonished at hearing
what's up?
If you say, my belly is empty
Have something to eat
The news comes out
You've done the cartoon
... I did
After giving a prize
I'm on your way, you go to your own way
To say this
Did you keep all this?
get lost
You go there
Sacrifice, do not freeze
Impossible
I saw myself
Right?
Purpose?
Dead
But it's free
Keep my head in my head
Freedom is not human
Freedom is a mindset
One goal
Think of a disease
Anyone can get it
One will kill 100 people
Freedom is in the hearts of the people, as God is hanging
So your concern should not be ruined yet
You're still in danger
Perhaps more than before
I told you to come and tell him
Where is this free army?
Sorry sir
... but
I heard the company have a land of 200 hectares in Kissing
And you know who this is
There are fifty thousand gold coins, much respect for him
is not it?
The price is not high?
I'm selling my name, sir
Please do not leave it
... fingers
.I accept
Free Army Map
My fool's partner is in your prison
You have given him so much food right now
How do I get there?
Try to escape this time
Otherwise both of you were killed
...Sir
Very good
You were with us
We do not forget
Q: What do you mean by bitch in English?
Hromosadeh
"I am happy to meet you."
We have two or three rounds
Move your dear master
These are very beneficial
And their wine does not speak
Are you fine or bad?
I'm good and bad
I love you
He is the most important
Or you are so big or too bitchy
I am a great observer
He was his signal
All people go to the sign
!turn around
Come on!
Be brave
Color
The card was not correct
Do you deceive us
The boiler tells the pot that it's black
I was scolded by many because of you
I gave you a bit of food tonight
Go to Clive, tell the faith of a Hindu
It's not a shame that we'll break apart after eating
.. ours takes the enemy's neck
And as long as his last breath fails
His neck does not go away
Thank you, bye
Two missing three
Free
Fiery
Finger!
Sinichar
We saved hell
Now this is my life
... even if I miss me too, I have no problem
Now that I understand the meaning of self-esteem
I will never let her go
.Thank you very match
I'm yours
You made me lose the wrong path in life
What is your self esteem now, when do you think?
You're gonna kill me
So Figuer showed us the wrong map
I thought you would trust her
I trusted me most
So I got a new snake
!very good
I was wrong, sir
False mistake
And you will be punished by the felony
We do not know where to hide it
Where to arrest him?
Where do you get me?
let me go
How are you mad
Still, you're a friend of mine
Do you think of fiction?
Call me?
I thought about you wrong
That I did not trust you
It was my mistake
Succeeding in your courage
.that was my fault
I'm angry now
I've come to the extreme
If I can not, I can not be kind
So I grew up, what would I do?
Clive, Revenge and the House
Except for this, I did not think anything
It's not blood in the bloodstream, it's poison
And this is the poison of my power
But maybe that's not all violence
The sword is free
Today you are one of my people
... This is a sign of trust and belief
And there is a friendship between us
... Today it is your duty to do this
And it's the duty of our friend
You do not need to be so angry
What I was supposed to do
Done?
Clive cried out
What do you want now
... Frankly speaking
My goodies are coming to an end
That's why I have to go from here
Be it, i'm talking about you
Do not trust people
What if we go back to our hometown?
come here
Goodbye I'm short
I'm afraid that a bitch would come out of me again
"Walk Anywhere"
"It's a misfortune for the rest"
"No one believes that something grows here"
"Make a silver change, everyone changes it"
! Yeah
! Do not
what has happened?
The ships of the company attack us
They are attacking us
hurry up
We can arrest most of them, sir
What
Surrender to themselves
Who said this?
Hit them all
! All out!
Take the baby out
Hurry up go
hurry up
Be fast, we have to go soon
You saved me
If you did not, everybody would not be aware of it
My master savior is not
One more time
Translator: Yassin
A presentation of the Bollywood Web site
New misery
Go ahead and solve it
Why are you all alive?
Eat daddy
Come on, Jaythin B.
That is Soraya
Sorry, we are unaware
Wedding caravan Edward
Soraya John is very humorous
Come here, see what I've come up with
First, bring down the voice
What did you think about yourself?
Do you like to eat food?
Poor you are in trouble
When you lie
First of all, I notice it
When did I lie?
You are in a hurry to be a passenger
- We came for help
But you must know
Who you help
.. I'll explain them
We are a free army
To give us a bonus
Sustenance is equal to death with us
This is not the case
Say a word
Thank you for your greatness
But why should I help you?
Because Clive is in the rush
Set up a great celebration
Because this celebration will not be done without you
And this is the last place for us
To reach Clive
True or False
It is your decision
Slavery is not good for anyone
Not for the insiders, nor for the aliens
But what are you doing?
Heart and dance
I love drooling with dreams
...Anyway
There is a rush
... We must blow the raven (devil)
She also gets warm
... Mr and Mr Clive
We came to you
Show our performance
... The difference is that
Seeing this, maybe your eyes
Swinging does not have any other beauty
Let him know
... because sometimes, by seeing our tribute, people give them their lives
Today's celebration is very magnificent
Tomorrow is a great success
When it overcomes badly
... Rawani, who until this day did not care
Death will end
But who is this devil?
In Ronapur today, one
Devil is Ravan
Free!
... before the execution of Soraya Jan
... I'll give you
... the leader of the murderers of India
I'll give you a quote
It is also known as the Sailor of God
There was a martyrdom
survived
To justice now
... at this funeral
Together with the head of the rave
The head of this killer will be shaken
.. Ravan is your own soil
And we know him from childhood
But in recognizing your mutilated person
We were very negligent
... in this circle
You are the main clown
You can not escape your punishment, Khodabakhsh
Listening translation: Yassin
Bollywood Web site
"Freedom if I accept my guilt"
"Now whatever, God's will will be"
"... daddy"
"Drop my doll ..."
"Turn the yard upside down"
"Girl holding the tree branch"
"And the silver was upside down"
"I'm burning in one hand"
"In the other hand I have instruments"
"I used to just laugh"
"Even if it was a sadness, let's do it"
"Today, despite the sadness of the whole congregation, I sacrifice myself."
"Until I reach my goal, the soul will not be separated from my body."
"What God wants is"
"Our destiny is what God's will is."
"The stars are shattered with the light of God"
"This slavery is a few days."
"My body gives him hello"
"But my soul is free forever."
"... we are not here."
"We belong to where"
"That's where it's always around"
"When we grow up, we are fading"
"This is our story"
"We must pass through the sea with a drowning ditch."
"This is our life"
"I give my religion to life every way"
"Until I reach my goal, the soul will not be separated from my body."
"What God wants is"
"Our destiny is what God's will is."
"The stars are shattered with the light of God"
"... daddy"
"Drop my doll ..."
"Turn the yard upside down"
"Girl holding the tree branch"
"And the silver was upside down"
. Another concern was added to us
He wanted
Blow up your head
But at the right time
The cheater gun came off the water
But sir, I am the professor of deception
Saffron, Rasoulpur Village
Fateh Abad area
Awad
Finger!
The whole army is free
Capture them all
See you there
Take it
What are you doing
I'm doing my own
Protecting my lord is my duty
Meanwhile, my name is foreign (foreign)
Look carefully, my look is like it
Sacred, looks like in our previous world
We had a relationship with each other
You were our father
And we have your basket
...Sir
I am the whole army
This is not just an award
What are you telling her in English?
Medal ! Dude
This is the time to give me a medal
Keep it safe
It is very dangerous
Finger!
Have you been chatting
... Say something, Duffy
Man must always have hope for deception
Two things left
Death and deceit
For everyone in this life
Once upon a time there is going to be
Thank you, you do not know
... where you are sitting
This is the realm you are dealing with
I do not have a heir, he's Duffy
The only daughter of Mirza Sikendar
He's dead
!very good
All the killers are under one roof
Why did you deceive him?
Sir, I said
I bring you the whole army of freedom
Just do not forget your Maro Award
Mr. Mirza is right, fingers
The greatest enemy of a Hindus
Is a Hindu man
Mr. Mirza was right
But you are wrong
Sir
Sorry, my little mouth moves a lot
You sit down
The name of Mr. Clive should be
Was gracious
... they have to say that
The life of Zafira is now in your hands
You have to do a little work
Anyone who has done anything for free now
... or in her heart, she is crazy about working with her
Give us your voice
Only save Zanara and Zafira
That's just that
If not, that is free from your eyes
Tomorrow will not exist at all
! Now cut off!
Bride delicious delicious Clive Prison
Take another
What are you made of?
Even hell is not the way for you
Shut up two, bitch
! Yeah
That's all because of Dfieura
I do not really understand Hindu Hindi
... capture them all
And duffy
... morning
Let him be executed
who are you?
I'm brave, open it
Come to eat all the sweets
We celebrated
We went for all the sweets
Give everyone a go
Yeah
They are glad
Eat and take it
Comrade is not a good game
I wanted to give you one too
But why do I wear it
So take a look
Hello, sir
Do you eat sweets
It's nice
Everyone is eating
You look like that
It's as if you want to eat instead of sweets
Come on, go on, take it
Let us talk
Uncle, the point is that
I know you're angry at me
There is a lot of difference between talking and acting
I say something
But I do something else
You have asked me to be careful about Zafira and my disciples
... God, so far, I have not done so hard
It's unlike the essence
May God have mercy
Whatever I had done
But I was fooling myself
But I saw him later
I'm sure I'm back
Otherwise, I would have gone the right way
I had forgotten my destiny
I saw you myself
To give a story of sweets to
Do you have that big?
Give me somebody
Do you eat
I told you
I miss the poison
!help yourself
!no no no
Wow!
I will take a sweet
And you attack me
The warrior within you is still alive
Even with the bracelet, you'll find a way
You are not afraid of death
So death does not come close to you
And I am so, that I even fear life
And I have to deceive
But today is not our life
But it's about your death
Just wanna do me with zobont?
Or another weapon?
I have time weapons
We do not have a bigger weapon
.. I told you that
At 10:05 your card will expire
I kidnapped Mr. Clive's clock
But I can not read it
You will take the time
The rest of me with me, I'll take a minute
At least I die with my own sword
You look at the clock
It was time to act
Jayton's magic syrup worked badly
We came to kill Clive
But when I saw you
My mind was working
... and thought to me
All your people are in prison
You also said, "When we are together, we are free"
But i am not
What
I'm not free
Do not do this, I know your name is God-loving
I say, my hand is closing
I am not free now
... and if you speak a second word
I'm crazy
I'm annoying you, uncle
What's are you waiting for?
Want to invite you to embrace?
!Sir
! Yeah
What are you doing crazy?
Hear my story
Every time I tell you the truth
You miss me
Flip, do not talk a word
We do not have time to talk
You are back
The goal is so bad
I needed to go back to hell
Which fool you taught you?
Do not forget this
And I'm bunny
I reminded you
You understand yourself
There is a tunnel here
... that goes straight to
All people are here
We are all and everyone
You will move as fast as possible
And give Clive a lesson
veto?
I've got a lot of pain on the stomach
you do not worry
I'll rest right here
It's one hundred percent
There is no reason for your chest
Until I martyred
You do not get two
I knew that your wickedness was fleeting
Are you drunk
I ate one of your sweets
Fool, how are you going to fight now?
Freedom has its own way
I know how we go
We all die
People say when you go to war
Forget about everything
But today must be the whole past
Remember
Clive we've loved so much
It's our turn now to compensate
Before the fight
!be ready
Ahead!
Liberty
Fire
Get my ship out
You go up
! Yeah
Do not shoot me, sir
I have little kids
You know how much I hate fighting
Now I'm lost in front of your eyes
-it's enough
Fooling us and yourself is enough
No sir
In your life for the first time in the right direction
You stepped
On the same track, stay tuned
Thank you, Indian, from the water
Inside you are like Hindi
But outside, a little outside is a model
Finger!
You really can not trust you
You are not the right guy, really
You got the Hindi with a closed cognitive hand
Now enjoy the power of their hands
Do not miss the ship
Mr. Clive
Translator: Yassin
A presentation of the Bollywood Web site
India's Best Indian Bollywood
Bollywood1.xyz
Liberty
!the freedom
... fingers
also
What did you get there
It's dawning
New beautiful
.Full
More videos and subtitles order
Bollywood Van
Intagram Bollywood Van
Instagram.Com/Bolly1official
Long live it!
Stay alive
Dfiera asked: where is Firogy?
No, he is now a leader
New people are new people
He does the job well
If I stay, I'll make it weak
Liberty
Follow you
Not
Yeah
Even after figuring out
You stole it
Come on, follow you on the door
It seems to be following you
I brought him a victory
I saved my life
Anyway, I took it from myself
-that's a lie
I swear to my grandmother
What do you swear
I swear to live or swear to die
How long have you been honest?
She liked
You could be king
I would be your minister
But no, you're my destiny
It's time to spend time with you
Look, comrade, marriage is the death of love
And the relationship between the two sides must be equal
Between me cum
See where is Zofira
That's not the case
Do not think yourself
I'm so big
I'm telling you that
Color
Again, we again became friends with Fab
I'm so glad to hear that
No one should be friends with us
What are you thinking about?
Cum says
He hurts you
Let me take it into account
Soraya, are you here?
I'm glad to see you
When you stole all my jewelry
I had no other choice
Hello
I did not hurt
I just borrowed you
Anyway, the beauty of a woman
It's a shame
What do you know about shame and hilarity?
Shame on your language
She is shameless
When you beat you
I'm happy to be happy
I do not hear that, dear sir
If you say your love is over
To sail
Where to go
Let's go Kolkata
What He said we were going to school
We're not going to have a colloquette
Why Calcutta, is it there?
I want to buy from my site
Fiery, where are we going?
... where they say hello to him
And just no Thuraya
But other dancers dance
Let's get two, you work
Take the bell, let's go
Loose shirt and tight pants
Friends, our ship goes straight to
England
They say they are British too
These white wreckage loot
... it's our turn now
I swear to the grandmother that if in a few months
I do not kidnap my country, I do not mention it
Long live the gods!