Will you marry me?
Kabir... please.
Okay.
Will you marry me, please?
Why are you doing this?
Because sooner or later we will.
We love each other.
Our families seem to tolerate each other.
I'm an architect and
you're an interior designer.
We're perfect.
What do you say?
Are you sure?
Natasha, please make it quick...
my knee is hurting.
Yes!
It seems like only yesterday
that Natasha came into this world.
And today she's getting engaged.
Kabir, I'm not losing a daughter.
I'm gaining a son.
You're so filmy, dad.
Harryji
Two years ago you commissioned me
to build your hotel.
Who would've imagined that
one day we'll be a big family.
On behalf of my family,
I welcome you all.
Thank you so much.
Did you ever know that you're my hero
You're everything I wish I could be
I can fly like an eagle
Cause you're the wind beneath my wings
You're the wind beneath my wings
- That was lovely.
Hello everyone.
I am lmran.
Kabir and I have been friends
since school.
The three Musketeers!
That's right, it was the name
uncle had given the three of us.
The three Musketeers.
Unfortunately, the third musketeer...
Arjun is not with us anymore.
Don't worry, he's alive.
He just isn't here right now.
Anyway, Natasha...
Kabir is one of the nicest guys ever.
So, if you ever smash his BMW,
don't worry.
Good excuse to get a new car.
He's also very intelligent.
So leave the kid's homework to him.
You're a true friend, thanks.
You're welcome, bro.
He's very large hearted.
So, don't think twice...
just buy those diamonds.
Basically Natasha...
Kabir is a solid guy.
Put your hand in his and
walk with him.
Because no matter what...
he will never let you down.
- So sweet.
- Hear, hear!
Thank you.
You can send the cheque now.
Tanya...
thank you.
Let me warn you...
Nikhil is planning a
full power bachelor party.
Too late.
His school friends have planned
a bachelor holiday.
A road trip...
through Spain.
- A road trip?
- Don't ask.
They had made some pact
in college that...
each one would choose
an adventure sport...
Are you serious?
Like Fear Factor?
Exactly!
And the other two would have to do it.
So, what have you picked?
That I can't say.
Not in front of me, at least.
You see...
the sport we pick
is a surprise for the other two.
Shut up!
- Seriously.
- Are you kidding me?
No.
That ensures none of us back out.
Whose idea was this?
Mine.
Three weeks.
You know how these boys are.
Not Kabir.
Oh please!
All guys go crazy at bachelor parties.
In fact...
Nikhil still hasn't told me
what happened at his.
I don't know.
I heard something about
your bachelor party.
Who told you?
So it is true.
Does Natasha know?
No man, why would I tell her?
Please... don't tell her.
She was from Ukraine.
- Bloody hot!
- Nice.
I was sloshed.
Okay, listen...
If Sameera finds out about this,
she'll kill me.
I know, don't worry.
It was my last night as a bachelor.
You know I'd never do it otherwise.
I understand, don't worry about it.
- Please.
- It happens.
Sameera!
Sorry, I couldn't resist.
- Take care, man.
- See you.
Trust me, this trick never fails.
What do you mean?
Well, you tell people you know
something about them...
and before you know it,
they tell you their secrets.
Shut up!
You didn't know about the Ukrainian?
No, he just told me.
Mind blowing!
- Yeah, well time equals money, Simon.
You want money, stop wasting my time.
Sell 50,000 June contracts!
50,000 and don't screw up
my stop losses this time!
How much?
Damn! That's horrendous!
Sell it. Sell everything.
Listen Joe, if you continue to give me
bullshit fills like that...
I'm going to have to trade
my Ferrari in for a Ford Fiesta!
We have white and gold and...
tonnes of champagne.
And...
- the centre peice.
- This is nice.
Finally!
Kabira!
Sorry man.
You have no idea what's happening here.
And you have no idea
what a nice party you missed.
I'm sure, man.
Listen...
I've a problem.
I can't make it to Spain.
- What?!
Arjun, you promised!
I know but...
I thought this deal I'm working on
would come through...
- but I'm stuck.
I can't believe you're ditching me
on my bachelor trip.
It's not that...
- Then what is it?
We had decided to do this together.
If you can't make it,
I'm calling it off.
Don't get sentimental.
It's my work!
I'm not.
It's been cancelled once before,
so let's do it again.
It's fine.
It's either the three of us going
or none at all.
Hey...
Hi.
How are you?
Good.
Looking good,
you've been working out?
Yes.
I usually come in the morning.
I was going to call you.
Then why didn't you?
I'm getting married.
- That was quick.
- Arjun, please!
All the best, Rohini.
- Arjun, it's me again.
- Don't ditch me.
- I know why you're making excuses.
- But it's been four years
for that incident.
- I'm getting married now.
- Even today, I only have two friends.
- We're the three Musketeers.
All for one, one for all.
Have you thought about...
what we spoke?
About what?
Are you moving back to Bombay?
Ammi...
I like Delhi and living on my own.
And this trip to Spain...
is it a coincidence or
did you plan it?
Why don't you just say
what you're really thinking?
Fine.
Do you intend to meet Salman?
I don't know.
Imran, why don't you trust me?
It's not about you Ammi.
- He is my father.
- He's your father?
Has he ever called you
or tried to find out how you are?
Maybe he did and
you kept it from me.
Until recently I wasrt even aware
that he is my father.
Alright.
Do what you want.
But please remember this.
Faisal was your only father.
- Hello there.
- Hello.
I can see you.
I miss you, baby.
Now we can see each other everyday.
I'm only going for
three weeks, Natasha.
What will I do in London all alone?
You'll shop.
And in three weeks I'll come to London
to carry your shopping bags.
- Very funny.
- I know.
- I don't see Madrid in this plan.
- Because it's not there.
- We travel to Spain but
we're not going to see the capital?
- We don't have enough time.
- We can't change it now.
- I think we should.
Look who's here!
- Welcome! How was your flight?
- Hello.
Well...
it flew.
Funny!
- Good to see you.
- You too.
I'm sorry about Abu.
I got your email.
- How's Ammi?
- She's fine.
It's not easy to get over these things.
How've you been?
I'm good.
Pretty good actually.
I've a new apartment.
Three bedrooms, big space.
Nice.
I can't believe we're together again.
- Yeah.
- Finally!
Should we sit?
So, here is the plan.
First...
we go to Costa Brava,
which is my choice.
Then Arjun wants to go to Seville.
And then we'll head to...
Pampalona which you've chosen.
Tomorrow morning we leave for
Costa Brava.
What are you doing with the laptop?
I'm looking for an address.
Hola Kabira.
Kabira...
Your treasure.
Brilliant. Thanks a ton.
What have you done to this?
Dude!
First of all, be thankful that
I bought this 12,000 Euro bag for you!
What?
Here... show, show...
12,000 Euro for this purse?
Way more than your salary.
What?
Natasha loves these bags.
And I love cars, Kabir.
Always remember.
If you ever want to gift
me an expensive car...
don't hesitate.
I won't.
Good.
Let's go.
I can't.
I need to make some calls.
I'll see you guys later.
Adios amigos.
- I thought this was a holiday.
- Me too.
Let's go.
We take the next right.
- Looks quite old.
- There it is.
There is the cathedral.
- Do you know where this place is?
- Yes, straight ahead.
How far is this gallery?
Shut up!
It's just here.
This is the street.
Catonia... whatever.
And that's the place.
I guess.
Hey!
Salman Habib.
It's a desi name.
He must be Pakistani or Indian.
Thanks.
I wish you'd come with us.
We walked all over
looking for his gallery.
Man, this city is beautiful.
Well, today I made
a 2,000 Pound commission, so...
excuse me if I don't complain.
Cheers.
- 2,000 Pounds?
- Yup!
Cheers.
Dude...
I heard something about you.
What?
You know what it is.
Mom told you?
Yes.
But did she tell you I was forced?
- Okay?
- Okay.
God man!
She can't keep anything to herself.
She's driving me crazy, man.
Yeah.
She came to London a few days ago.
And dragged me to
some friend's relative's place.
To see a girl.
Neelu aunty and
Gogi uncle's daughter Cookie.
I'd decided that I'd go,
have some tea...
exchange pleasantries and
decline the match.
As I took the first sip...
Cookie said 'no'!
So... you know...
What?!
I mean, so what!
What is there?
What?
Come on, man!
You were set up for
an arranged marriage...
and you got rejected?
But I didn't even try
to create an impression.
- Now you're just saying it.
- I didn't want to impress her!
You've ruined our reputation.
Shut up, please stop it!
Why did she have to tell you?
What's wrong with her?
Actually, your mom said nothing.
It's his latest trick.
And you're his latest victim.
- Cheers!
2,000 Pounds!
Grow up, man!
How old are you?
You know what...
we have to have some shots.
- One for Cookie.
- We'll raise a toast to Cookie.
Okay.
Not for me.
I have a conference call
in an hour.
Same old plan?
Mint money and retire at 40?
Yup!
That's the plan.
Listen...
thank you.
For what?
For coming on this trip.
It means a lot to me.
I'm sure it does.
Literacy is the key.
It's not that simple.
Oh - my - God!
Kabira, amazing choice.
She's gorgeous but she isn't ours.
What?
An SUV will be a lot comfortable.
To hell with the comfort.
Just look at her!
Guys?
- Hola, good morning.
Your name?
- Kabir Dewan.
- Guys!
Kabir... Arjun...
She's beautiful.
I've booked an SUV and
they've charged me, sorry.
Sell Natasha's purse.
Funny.
Please!
What are you doing?
Behave yourself!
Oh, don't even
think about it, dude.
All my life I sat in your car.
Now it's my turn.
What are you doing?
12,000 Euro. She rides first class.
Hey Sarah, what's up?
Mr. Yamamoto called?
Well, he'll have
the docket in two days.
No, no don't say I'm on a holiday.
Just get Joe to call me back. Bye.
Hey Joe, what's up?
Like... 'now' now?
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, I'll do it, bye.
Sorry guys.
Guys... ten minutes tops!
Moshi moshi, Arjun-san.
Moshi moshi, Yamamoto-san.
How are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
Moshi, moshi?
It's Japanese for hello.
- I assure you,
I will always be here for you.
Kabira...
Look at this amazing view.
And, now look at our friend.
My team is going to
put together all the information.
And you will have
the docket with you in three days.
What happened to him, dude?
If you ask me...
he has become mantally sick.
And he needs the psychaitrixt.
Isn't this from school?
Not school.
- Eschool!
- Eschool.
Eschool!
Because only the Mr. The Dubey
can the talk like this.
The Mr. The Dubey.
Are you mantally challanged my buy?
Not buy.
Bwoy.
- Bwoy.
Mantally challangedmy bwoy...
Mantal bwoy.
Thank you, Mr. Yamamoto.
Let's go. I'm done.
Arjun, my bwoy...
you look the mantalin this the uniform!
Let's go.
Okay, the very the well the saids.
Guys...
just do as I say.
It's been ten years since college.
Please grow up.
- Don't do this, please.
- Trust me.
You'll kiss me later.
When I shout...
point to the urinal and
scream loudly.
Bye!
Dude, you're the mantallythe sick!
People are the same everywhere.
It's just human nature.
What are you doing?
Poor thing's feeling hot.
Poor thing?
Kabira...
meet Bagwati.
What's happened to your jokes?
Are they sick?
Well, they've taken after you.
Hey Joe, yes I spoke to
Mr. Yamamoto and...
Somebody please
throw his phone out.
What the...
- Are you mad?
Did you just...
You think we'll get it?
Sorry, I didn't think he would do it.
Of course you didn't know, Kabir.
Now go find my phone.
- Where?
- I don't know.
I want my phone, that's all.
It could've broken.
Arjun, don't be silly...
we won't find it.
Silly?
You threw my phone out
of a moving car, you moron!
He said it, I threw it.
Didrt you?
Kabir...
please tell me to slap him.
Don't be silly.
Just tell me to slap him.
Slap him.
- What's wrong with you?
- Guys!
I'll get you a new phone.
I was just joking.
Well, it's not funny.
That call was important.
You think being 'cool and funny'
gives you the license to do anything?
It's always like,
'lmran said this. He's so funny.'
Lmran did that, he is so cool'.
Grow up!
Throwing my phone
out the window is not funny!
Hooking up with my girlfriend
was not funny!
Listen...
it's been four years.
And I've apologised for it.
Now let it go.
Or what? Huh, what?
Stop it. Stop it, you two.
You're behaving like kids.
If there's a problem,
deal with it.
Like adults.
Who made you the judge?
Do you see anyone else here?
Listen.
Let's get this straight.
I don't have any problem with him.
Why would you have a problem?
Sonali was my girlfriend.
Come on, Sonali and me
fell in love.
It happens. Shit happens.
Yeah.
It was shit.
For me.
And I'm sure you didn't
give it a second thought.
Imran man...
I would never do that to you.
Arjun...
I screwed up.
Now what do you want me to do?
What do I do?
Should I wear a 'Sorry, Arjur t-shirt
and walk around?
What should I do?
Just look at him.
Listen to me, okay.
You two, please!
Sonali was a bitch.
Understand?
I'm sorry, really.
She used you.
Then gave you a BPL
and used him.
And she dumped you as well.
She was a waste of time then
and she is a waste of time now.
Four years ago we cancelled
this trip because of her.
Today we're here for me.
Don't let her ruin this.
Please!
How many times
do I have to apologise?
How many times?
Let's just make it clear.
Till it doesn't come from here.
What's BPL?
Bum Pe Laat.
[Kick in the arse.]
You're crazy.
Speak with him.
He slapped me.
I can't believe this.
Hi baby...
Good.
We've left Barcelona.
On the road.
Yes, it's beautiful.
Of course, they're with me.
Where will they go?
Everything is cool.
Yeah.
All ready.
Come on.
Yes!
Now this is a house.
- I like.
- Cool.
It's lovely.
You haven't seen the half of it yet.
Can we slide?
No, you can't.
- Captain.
- Amazing.
Wow, man!
This is nicer than the pictures.
Amazing.
What a view!
Someday.
How was it?
Refreshing.
Who is she?
How should I know, dude?
She's nice.
Really nice.
What's happening?
She's got me.
She's pulling me towards her.
She's pulling me.
I saw her first.
So true.
But has she seen you?
What?
- Hola.
Can I try that?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Where are you from?
Brazil?
Half US, half India.
India?
What a coincidence!
Which part?
My dad's from Delhi but
I live in London.
Hindi? Not bad!
You too... wow!
If you're free,
want to join me for a drink?
I have an early morning.
Sorry.
Thanks.
Bye.
What's your name?
Laila.
Imran.
But my friends call me 'Romeo'.
Romeo?
Seriously man... Romeo?
I mean, chee!
Arjun...
It's a mars duty to try.
Success and failure are in His hands.
Great, professor.
Seriously?
You got me this time!
What the hell is this?
What?
This! What the hell is this?
You said I had to
get you a new phone.
You didn't specify which one.
I'm a trader.
Not a Japanese school girl.
Moshi moshi.
Shut up, just shut up!
- Just don't talk to me.
- Guys that's enough!
Look at this.
What's wrong with him?
What's wrong with you?
It's funny.
Anyway, now listen.
Why we are here in Costa Brava.
Ready for this?
Yeah.
Deep... sea...
diving.
What?
Yes, our training begins
first thing tomorrow.
I'm sorry but...
why is this turning into a
let's torture Arjun holiday?
I just don't understand.
Relax, I know.
I spoke with the people
at the diving school.
You don't need to know how to swim.
At least you know how to drown.
Listen, just keep quiet. Just...
keep quiet.
Kabir...
I don't understand how you thought
I'll do this.
What's wrong with you?
Bathroom... to the left.
Okay, listen.
I know you're scared of water.
Okay.
But then that's the challenge.
And it's completely safe.
Think about it.
Blue waters... okay?
Fish swimming close to you.
Corals...
It'll be amazing.
Look, if you're not comfortable,
no one's going to force you.
No, I'm serious, it's okay.
Okay. Fine.
Kabir Dewan?
Laila?
Hey.
Hi, what are you doing here?
Following you, I guess.
Really?
No.
I'm here to train you.
I'm an instructor here.
Wow!
- Hi, I'm Kabir.
- Laila.
- This is Arjun.
- Hi.
Laila.
Romeo?
You remember?
Arjun...
If you don't want to dive,
it's totally fine.
He can't swim.
It's okay, doesn't matter.
You'll be fine.
Thank you.
Shall we start?
Let's go.
It's a little difficult to
talk under water.
For obvious reasons.
So these signs are very important.
Up.
Down.
Okay.
Not okay.
Air guage.
Okay?
Alright!
You have to wear a wet suit.
The water is pretty cold.
Next is the BCD.
Your buoyancy control device.
All okay?
These weights will help you
remain underwater.
Finally, your fins.
Cheers. Salut.
Good job, boys.
So, when is the wedding?
In two months.
- That's like now, man.
- Yeah, I know.
We only started dating
about six months ago.
Well, you know what they say...
when it's right, it's right.
That's what I said.
Actually, she said it.
What does she do?
Interior design.
And she's bloody good.
Okay.
And of course,
her father has a hotel business...
that's evaluated at...
Ten billion?
Ten billion.
I'm not marrying her for her money.
Kabir, of course not.
But you've got to admit,
it's a plus point.
Plus point?
Are you serious?
Would you marry for money?
Depends.
How much?
Ten billion!
Definitely.
And what if she's a bore?
When you have ten billion in your bank
who needs the wife for entertainment?
- Romantic.
- I agree, it's true.
- Cheers!
Are you seeing someone?
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
Hey... what about Rohini?
What happened there?
- She was nice.
- Well...
I guess she wanted
different things out of life.
Laila...
apart from my body
what else do you want out of life?
I don't know.
I haven't really made a list.
Still...
there must be something.
I guess, I want that...
life should continue to surprise me.
Inspire me.
Make me meet new people.
Hola.
Hola?
Sorry.
Give me new experiences.
And...
I want...
you to get me a drink.
Your wish is my command.
- One for me, please.
- Arjun?
I'm okay.
- Keep it down.
- Guys we're gonna get arrested.
He's here. Quiet.
I was just telling...
that's the problem you see.
Sorry.
Your life is about to change.
That's if I survive!
We'll see.
Yup, we'll see.
The moment flows by like molten sapphire
Deep blue silences
No earth below, no sky above
The rustling branches and leaves
Are saying only you are here
Only me
My breath and my heartbeat
Such depth, such solitude
And me
Only me
I now believe I esist
Baby, it was amazing.
You should definitely do it.
I have no interest.
Hey!
Hey...
Sorry. Can I use your loo?
Lmran is taking a shower.
Sure.
Who is that?
Wait. First say hi to Natasha.
Okay.
Hey... I'm Laila.
Hi.
Kabir has told me a lot about you.
Congratulations in advance.
Thanks.
Well, it's really nice to meet you.
- Bye.
Who is that?
That's Laila, our instructor.
She's studying fashion in London but...
three months a year she works
at dive sites around the world.
Isn't that cool?
Very cool.
What is she doing in your room?
She's using the bathroom.
Imran invited her over for dinner.
To celebrate our first dive.
D'you think I'm stupid?
What? It's the truth.
Arjun is cooking.
Yeah, you must be very busy.
I'll speak to you later.
Natasha, why are you getting upset?
I'm not upset.
I've a flight to catch.
You're being really silly.
Yeah, I know. Bye.
Bye.
- All okay?
- Yeah, fine.
- See you downstairs.
- See you.
Need some help?
Nope. Almost done.
Paella.
- Yup.
- Very nice.
Thanks.
So...
you didn't tell me how it was.
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
You did it.
So, how was it?
It was magical.
It felt like the
most peaceful place on earth.
It was beautiful.
I was 16 when I did my first dive.
And then stopping myself
was impossible.
Yeah, it could be addictive.
Addictive?
No.
Addiction is such a negative word.
Diving is...
something else for me.
It's like meditation.
You're conscious of
every breath, every moment.
Just imagine...
living your whole life like that.
Be fully alive to each and every moment.
Delicious.
- Seriously.
- Thank you.
You should cook more often.
I know man but...
where's the time!
So, the fear of water still there?
Now there's no fear.
Not even of life.
Wow! In one dunk
you've unravelled the mystery of life!
Well done, my lad.
Actually, it's quite simple.
What is it?
Just...
keep breathing.
Laila!
Finally, our old friend has surfaced.
And to avoid a relapse...
why don't you join us on the trip?
I'd love to.
But I'm off to Buñol tomorrow.
It's the Tomatina festival.
- Too bad!
- Is it?
Toma-tina, what's that?
Arjun!
How can you not know that...
it is world s largest tomato fight?!
It's like our festival of colours.
But played with tomatoes instead.
Really?
Actually, you guys should come.
It'll be a blast.
I'm in.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah, I'm in.
What? No!
We're leaving for Seville tomorrow.
That's perfect.
Buñol is en-route.
- Come on.
Look, Seville is Arjurs choice.
He made the reservations.
To mess with Arjurs reservations is...
like inviting Death!
Come on.
Alright, let me see what I can do.
Is that your phone?
It's a long story.
Let's not go there.
No, it's nice.
He's very much in touch
with his feminine side.
Eat your food.
Don't worry, even I like pink.
Great, I feel much better.
Thank you.
How could you do this?
Rohini, I'm really sorry but...
can't you see that
this deal could help me.
Can't you see that maybe I don't care!
You don't care.
- You don't care about my life?
- Stop it, Arjun.
Don't confuse your work with your life.
Your work isn't your life.
It's just a part of it.
Just like this relationship
is a part of your life.
- What about this?
I bought this apartment so that
we could live together.
What? Please!
You bought this apartment to impress people
with your up market address.
I can't believe you just said that.
- I'm planning a future with you.
- Our future will come tomorrow, Arjun.
- Don't scream!
- Where is our today?
Don't scream.
Then listen to me.
What do you want?
I want to spend time with you.
I want a relationship.
Not a retirement plan.
Please, Rohini.
The chairman of Nakatomi Corporation
wants a meeting with me.
What do I do?
I have to go.
If the presentation does it,
he'll give us the entire account.
That will boost my career.
Can't you see that?
What about our deal?
We can go next month.
It's my birthday, Arjun.
- I know.
- It won't come next month.
You had promised that we would
go to Italy no matter what.
And you cancelled the tickets
without even talking to me.
Rohini, I really am sorry.
Please understand. Just a second.
It's an important call.
Just one second.
Rohini, one second.
Hello...
Yes, Alex...
I'll be there in ten minutes.
Hey babe, I guess you're on the plane.
I called to say that we're going to
Buñol tomorrow, for the Tomatina festiva
Laila is taking us.
Please don't be upset.
Please call when you get this message.
I love you.
Where the hell is he?
Oh - my - God!
- I love it.
- Unbelievable!
- Okay.
- Yes?
- Can I drive?
- No.
Kabira...
if four days of diving
can do this to you.
Trust me, you should stay under water.
Who knows if I'll be with you guys again...
I decided, it's all or bust!
- Right?
- Correct.
Dude, you're getting married.
You're not going to prison.
Thanks.
All set?
- Arjun...
can you help me?
- It's to the right.
- It's jammed, what did you do?
Dude!
You have to apply some force.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Child!
Relax in the front seat.
Driver... Buñol.
So Lailaji, hale and hearty
both packed in the bag?
No, thanks.
What are you doing?
Laila, meet Bagwati.
Hi Bagwati.
Bagwatithinks you are very beautiful.
Thank you, Bagwati.
The evening was hazy...
The mood was sad...
A thousand memories vanished as they came...
That's really nice.
You wrote it?
I wish...
It's by Raghupati Sahai Firaq.
Even our man writes quite well.
- Really?
- Thanks man.
- What say, Kabir?
- Of course.
Diamond biscuit Diamond biscuit...
Whenever in a mood just have it...
For a healthy life just taste it...
Whenever mummy daddy bring it out...
All the happy kids squeal and shout...
Diamond biscuit Diamond biscuit...
For a healthy life just taste it...
Now available in a new coconut flavour.
- So beautiful.
- One has to do it, assholes!
Inspired writing.
- It's kind of nice.
- Isn't it?
Brought a smile to your face, didn't it?
Hello.
Hi, it's me.
- Where are you?
- Just landed in London.
Look...
I'm sorry I hung up yesterday.
It's okay.
You know what, just forget about it.
Thank you.
So, you're going Buñol?
Chee!
- What happened?
- What are you doing?
Sorry.
Yes.
- Laila, where are we staying?
- Hotel Venta Pilar.
Some Venta Pilar...
Venta Pilar.
Okay, fine.
Well you have fun, okay.
Okay, of course.
Arjun...
what are you doing man?
- Again?
- What are you doing?
I'm sorry, it's the wind.
I'm really sorry.
Really?
By the way, Bagwatiis feeling kinda hot.
I'll let her get some wind by the window.
- Turn left here.
- Yeah?
- I know I'll see her somewhere.
There she is.
- Hola!
Everybody this is Nuria.
- Hola.
- Arjun.
- That's Kabir.
- Hello.
And that's lmran in the corner.
- Hola!
She's saying it's already started.
We have to go.
We're going to miss it.
Imran.
- The bags?
- These guys will take care of them.
- But my laptop.
- Arjun, let's go. Come on!
- Okay.
- Imran.
We're leaving you.
Laila...
your friend is very cute.
Is that so?
You've already forgotten me?!
You're pathetic!
Laila...
You will go down in history
as my first love.
Okay listen guys,
there are two rules.
You have to make way for the trucks.
And squash the tomatoes
before throwing them.
Otherwise it hurts.
Alright? Let's go!
- Kabira, squash it.
- Did it hurt?
- Of course.
- Shit man!
What are you guys doing?
There are rules.
Have you ever followed a rule in your life?
You bastard, now you want rules!
Come here!
Come here I'll tell you the rules.
Come on!
Ooh aah... take the world and paint it red
Ooh aah... paint it red
There's a passion, a madness
All around
A carefree gladness
Somewhere lightly, the colours fall
Stories of yesterday, you can't recall
Someone softly tells my heart
Give yourself away, let the magic start
This moment that's so whole
Seems high on its own
This moment unveils its intosication on you
Now you're in the mood
You hold hands with the groove
As voices blend in with the hues
And it's stinking too.
You're going to get this.
- She's going to get it.
- Put me down!
Kabir?
Natasha?
What are you doing?
Hi...
I came here to surprise you.
I thought you'd be
happy to see me.
I am happy.
Yeah, you look it.
Natasha...
this is my bachelor trip.
And you know, I want to
spend this time with my friends.
Really? Laila is your friend?
She's our diving instructor.
I told you on the phone.
And the other one... Nancy?
Nuria.
Whatever!
Oh God, Natasha!
I just met her this morning!
She was kind enough to give us her room.
We'll probably never see each other again!
That's just perfect!
No one will ever know what happened.
Is that why you are here?
The apology on the phone was
just an excuse to get the address.
How dare you, Kabir?
- That's really mature...
- Shut up!
Who is it?
Lmran.
Come in.
- Hi.
- Hey.
I'm sorry, I just need my bag.
Don't apologise, it's totally cool.
Thanks.
We've made dinner plans,
would you like to join us?
- Actually...
- Yes.
Definitely, sounds like fun.
Okay, I'll call when we're heading out.
We don't have to go.
I don't want your friends to
think I'm a witch!
Witch alert!
Our holiday is in danger.
Who is next?
Mind if I go first?
Even I love you very much.
Dude, I can't believe Natasha's here.
I'm shocked!
Why?
What's the big deal?
Laila...
your fiancée can't crash your bachelor party.
That's the only rule!
Rule?
- You guys are so stupid.
- What?
Stupid?
You're stupid.
Natasha hates you.
What?
Yes, she said...
Is Laila your friend?
She asked you that?
No, she asked Kabir.
I was eavesdropping outside the door.
Of course.
How do you say,
'can I come ir, in Spanish?
Dude, what're you doing?
Don't be stupid!
Yes?
See you in the lobby.
I want to learn Flamenco.
It looks like so much fun.
Laila, you live in Spain?
No, in London.
So does Arjun.
Yeah.
Kabir and I will be there
after this holiday.
We should definitely get together.
Yeah, we should.
I'd love to but I'm off to
Morocco from here.
For a month.
Wow!
I think all of you
should come to Seville with us.
I'm going back to London tomorrow.
You only came here for a day?
Yeah.
Kabir wants to hang with the two of you.
I don't want to disturb your plans.
Don't be silly, Natasha.
You're hardly a disturbance.
- That's really sweet, lmran.
Thank you.
But, Kabir said it's a miracle to
get you two together.
And you have to attend the wedding.
No excuses.
100 percent!
Of course!
Excuses...
Could we get the more
the red the wines?
Arjun, the translation into the Españols?
Lmran, please!
It's because of such behaviour
that Indians have a bad reputation.
Will you please tell him?
Lmran, don't do it.
Chee!
What chee? He is right!
I agree with you.
Imran, it's wrong.
No.
I'm the very the sorry
No, I'm sorry.
Not funny!
- Been to Morocco?
- Morocco? No!
- Good night, guys.
- Good night.
Let's go?
In a bit.
Moshi moshi.
- Will you do me a favour?
- No way!
Why don't you both take a long walk?
Dude, it's late, we're tired.
You must be tired.
- You must be tired.
- No, not really.
That's the spirit.
The night is young.
You two aren't that old either!
I'm sure you'll come up
with some plan.
- You sure?
- Come on.
Shit! I forgot my phone.
Arert you on a holiday?
And, you are absolutely right.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
Really?
Why not?
You see, the guys I liked...
wanted different things out of life.
What kind of guys do you like?
What's your type?
I don't have a type.
Come on, everyone has a type.
Really?
Like I know, a guy who gets
only three weeks off in a year...
isn't your type.
He can't be anyone's type.
He has no time.
He is a slave.
And one who only thinks of his career,
isn't your type either.
If he only thinks about his career,
then he is a bore.
Or someone who thinks money is
the most important thing in life.
Like you!
You don't know anything about me.
So?
So, don't judge me.
I wasrt judging you.
I'm merely asking...
does money really make you happy?
I was eight when my dad passed away.
Leaving behind a huge debt
for my mother.
Very early I understood that...
only money makes the world go round.
Simple as that.
- I understand, Arjun.
But you still haven't
answered my question.
Yes, money makes me happy.
Then why did you cry,
the other day...
after the dive?
Has a paycheque ever brought
tears to your eyes?
- No,
Think about it.
When you've done so well in life...
are you really happy?
Even today if you feel
something is missing...
what is it?
Take time out for things that...
give you genuine joy.
Like cooking.
Well, that's the plan, I mean...
I'll retire at 40 and...
Dude!
How do you know
if you'll be alive till then?
Seize the day, my friend.
First, live this day to the fullest.
Then think about 40.
Come on.
My friends don't know
why I made them come here.
Your skin is beautiful.
I love your colour.
I want to meet Salman Habib.
I've never met him.
I have never met my father.
What if he
doesn't want to meet me?
- You're welcome.
Why are we lying here?
I mean, it's ridiculous.
No.
It's ridiculous that
you've never done this before.
What to do?
I'm stuck with
a beautiful home in London.
Only someone who has
never slept under the stars...
can say something so stupid.
Wow man.
I should learn from you.
I feel like I've spent my life in a box.
But you...
you are free.
You're free, Laila.
Arjun...
The only time a man
should be in a box...
is when he's dead.
Natasha, stay for a few more days.
You don't mean that.
No, I do.
I don't like it that you're so sad.
What do you expect?
How would you feel if I just left you
and took off with my friends?
You have your own life.
And if you and Sameera
ever decide to go on a trip...
why would I stop you?
And if I told you
that we've met some guys...
and made dinner plans
with them, then?
Then what?
I trust you.
Of course I'd want
you both to be safe...
but besides that,
I won't suspect you.
I'm sorry, but it's easier said than done.
Babe...
you're welcome to stay
if you want to.
But if you don't,
I'll drive you to the airport tomorrow.
Good night.
- I'll miss you.
- Take care.
- Stay in touch. See at the wedding.
- Imran, can you help me?
- Of course.
For sure. Okay?
- Email me.
- I will.
Good luck.
Hey...
Yesterday was...
I had the best time yesterday.
Me too.
And good luck...
for your upcoming adventures.
Thanks.
I'll see you.
Bye.
Ciao.
A thought came alive, but away it hid
It stole a glance, from under the eyelids
Sometimes from you, sometimes from me
it asked for words to set it free
Words to wear, so from the lips it can flee
A voice it can embrace and sway with glee
But this thought
Is a feeling... just a feeling
Like a fragrance floating in the breeze
A fragrance that is unspeaking
You live with it
I'm aware of it
Out in the open for the world to see
What is this unknown mystery?
Laila?
You'll forgot something?
I hate regrets.
Then you shouldn't have any.
Bye.
Flying away in the open sky...
Are the birds of my dreams
Flying away...
To the land of my heart
are the birds of my dreams
Don't know where they'll go nest
Wings have taken flight and
now says my sight you've flnally awoken
What was on your mind is left behind
You've moved far ahead in time
Life is floating on a breeze
Life is telling you and me
Now whatever will be will be
A touch from someone
and I've been wandering without a thought
Somewhere new words were spoken
and since then I've been lost
Something made the heart melt
In a blink, I was someone else
Now whatever will be will be
A light shone down
Now there's a beauty being showered on the streets
Happiness came down
Now there's a zest being showered upon me
Now I flnally know who I was meant to be
Do you remember that moment yesterday
The one with the magic force?
It transformed us into something new
I wonder which moment it was?
The heart says just blindly go to
Any place that desire takes you
Now whatever will be will be
What do you mean,
you've quit your job?
Meaning?
We're getting married in two months.
So? You can resume after the wedding.
How?
First, we'll go on the honeymoon...
then I want to redo the house.
That will take about a year.
And if you're going
to Singapore for your new project...
I'll be coming with you.
But...
that hotel is your dream project, Natasha.
Dreams change baby.
Then, I didn't know I'd be getting married.
Married?
What does marriage have to do with it?
What do you mean?
Obviously, priorities change.
After the wedding, even you wouldn't
want to go on this kind of boys holiday
- When is her flight?
- At 6 p.m.
Don't worry man, we'll make it.
Yeah.
Very funny!
All okay, babe?
Yeah.
Can I drive?
Can you drive?
Babe, the speed limit is 120.
You can go faster.
Yes, we may just miss that flight.
I'm not going to drive rashly.
Watch out!
Please keep your eyes on the road, please!
Then tell him not to talk to me.
Don't talk to her.
I love this song.
Rock chick in a hard rock world...
I'm a rock chick in a hard rock world...
Nothing rocks better than a rock chick girl...
I had fun.
Listen...
I'm sorry.
Me too.
Bye Bagwati.
Tell me...
what do you think about them?
- Kabir is not himself when Natasha is around.
- That's what I thought.
Correct.
I sense some tension.
Did you speak with him?
Why should I?
If a friend doesn't address
a personal problem, then who will?
Forget it man!
They'll sort their problem
and we'll get screwed in the middle.
Chee, man!
You are seriously shameless.
What?
Look... he is our friend.
When he is back,
let's talk to him.
Okay?
Okay.
God!
Now what has he done?
He's buried inside his diary again.
He's too boring.
What do you write in it?
It's private.
Rascal...
you've always been secretive.
- But there's nothing to tell.
- No, no, no!
You're obviously struggling
with an emotional problem.
What? Me?
Arjun...
I truly believe that...
if a friend doesn't address
a personal problem, then who will?
- Continue.
- Yes, absolutely.
To figure out the problem
we have to do a test.
- I'll say a word.
- Okay.
And you have to say the first thing
that comes to your mind.
Without deliberating.
- Alright?
- Okay.
- Ready, doctor.
- Fine.
Car.
Road.
Arjun.
Brother.
Diary.
Poetry.
Heart.
Love.
Mumbai.
Traffic.
Father.
- Father?
- Mother.
According to my test...
your father is the root of
your emotional problem.
And you're keeping this from the world.
And, in my opinion,
Dr. Sigmund Fraud...
it's time to shred your degree.
Please stop practicing, please!
You hurt my feelings, man.
My bwoys!
If you want a view,
look that way.
We should talk to him.
Natasha is really sweet.
It was really nice to meet her.
Yeah... even she was glad
to have met you.
Kabir...
- are you happy?
- Yes.
Why... are you asking like this?
I don't know man. Listen...
it's possible I may be wrong.
But, we are friends.
And I just...
I just have to ask you.
Are you happy with Natasha?
Dude, you just met her.
And the poor girl was a bit tense.
She thought there was something
between Laila and me.
Yeah.
But, now there's no problem.
Thanks to you, my bwoys!
Okay?
She's sweet.
Imran, you've met her.
You spent time with her.
Tell him.
Yes, she is very sweet.
Well that's good, man.
I'm happy for you.
Hey... here's an extra pillow!
Good night, bwoys.
Good night.
Guys, do you mind
if we take a detour?
Why?
There is an artist, Salman Habib.
He lives around here.
The lady at the gallery told me.
That he sells his paintings from home.
Really?
Sounds good.
Anyway, I'm a bit bored
hanging with just the two of you.
The map says we should take
the next right for Grazalema.
- Salman Habib.
- You'll find Indians in
every corner of the world.
- Really, man. We're everywhere!
Grazalema. Turn right over here.
- Dude, I said right.
- Forget it.
Don't feel like it.
Let's go to Seville.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
We can go on the way back.
It's okay.
Okay!
It's time to see
what I've planned for us.
Check it out, bwoys!
Look at that guys!
- Arjun, my pal. You rock!
- Look at that dude!
- Wow!
- You b******!
You're purposely doing this.
You know I'm scared of heights.
Don't be silly.
I want to do this.
It's my dream.
- Yeah right!
- Just imagine...
jumping from 15,000 feet
and flying towards the earth.
That's not flying, that's falling.
It will be fun.
Relax.
Remember he eventually enjoyed diving.
- Correct.
- Big deal.
With a beautiful instructor
like Laila, who wouldn't!
You never know,
you also might get lucky.
You people ready to
jump out of a plane?
- Oh yeah!
Are you ready to enter the air?
Yeah!
Head up. Eyes to the horizon.
Legs at 45 degrees.
Arch! Arch!
- Did I say relax?
- No.
I said arch.
I didn't say relax.
These are total malfunctions.
In case of a total malfunction
what you have to do is this.
Cut away your main and
deploy your reserve.
What is that?
You have a malfunction.
Cut away my main and
deploy my reserve.
What are you doing?
- It's a broken line.
- Are you sure it's a broken line?
Scissor kick... scissor kick...
Cut! Deploy!
Perfect!
What's this?
Waiver form.
Waiver form?
If something happens to us... like death,
these guys aren't responsible.
We are responsible for it.
What?
I'll see you outside.
- I'm feeling sick.
- What?
I'm going to throw up.
I'm scared too.
But that's why we are here.
Everybody get ready.
Okay!
Alright, guys. This is it!
Bye!
Dude!
I'm next.
Adios amigo!
See you downstairs!
Let go, lmran.
Just let it all go!
Push me!
Come on, lmran!
Lmran!
Who are you?
Where have you been?
I've moved the heaven and the earth
but I couldn't flnd you
But you arrive today,
so suddenly
And you give meaning to
my whole life with your love
I don't understand
I don't know
What you've said to me, Señorita
Even then, I have no idea why
I like what I heard, Señorita
Don't look away
Stay close to me
Take me in your arms
Hope you've understood Señorita
Even a few moments of love
Are never too less
Come let's lose ourselves in them
And forget we ever knew sadness
Señorita, listen to us
Señorita, d'you hear what we're saying
I will never understand
The meaning of the words
you dedicate to me
But the warmth of your gaze
Makes me feel like
the most beautiful Señorita
Our eyes looked at each other
And recounted tales of desire Señorita
That for affection and for love
There is only one language
in the world Señorita
Don't look away from me now
Come closer to me
Take me in your arms
Hope you've understood Señorita
Even a few moments of love
Are never too less
Come let's lose ourselves in them
And forget we ever knew sadness
Señorita, listen to us
Señorita, d'you hear what we're saying
With every moment that has passed
Oh Señorita
You've managed to win my heart
And that's all there is to it
Don't look away
Stay close to me
Take me in your arms
Hope you've understood Señorita
Even a few moments of love
Are never too less
Come let's lose ourselves in them
And forget we ever knew sadness
Remember before cable TV
we only had one national channel?
And every Sunday
they showed a Hindi film.
Get to the point.
The point is...
before the film there was this animation.
A white circle went round and round
and formed the channel logo.
Do you remember the tune?
Brilliant!
That tune never failed to depress me.
Depressed.
I'm feeling the same right now.
Weekend's over and school begins.
- And you wanted to cancel this trip!
- I know, man!
Can you imagine?
You know what that means?
It means...
that everything is predestined.
Everything!
This holiday was in our destiny.
You know!
You, me and asshole.
- Cheers asshole.
- Where's asshole?
Cheers!
Laila too.
I was meant to meet her.
You are in louw, my bwoy.
No, man!
You are in louw...
- You are in louw...
- Kabir, man!
Everything is written.
Listen to me.
It's all predestined.
You know what I'm saying?
This moment... us right now...
it's predestined.
Predestined.
Please stop saying, 'predestined... '!
I beg of you!
This too is predestined.
It's all written.
Alright, we get it.
Listen, we get it, zip!
Come on, man!
It's true.
It's predestined...
Guys...
Hola...
Guys, watch out!
What the hell, guys?
Yes?
- Our man is back.
- Their mobiles are switched off.
- What?
- Yup.
Even Nuria's?
Yes, I'm shocked.
When she knew we'd land up in jail,
she should've kept the phone switched on
If our bail isn't posted...
we'll be stuck here for days.
Arjun...
tell them I want to make a call.
To whom?
Salman Habib.
The artist?
Yeah.
Why will he come to post our bail?
Are you alright?
Just because we can't reach anyone,
he's losing it.
He's my father.
What?
I am his son.
Just let it go lmran.
Just let it go.
- Hello...
Hello, may I...
speak with Mr. Salman Habib, please?
- Yes?
Sir, I am lmran.
I am Rahila's son.
When did you find out?
Afew days after Abu died.
In his stuff, I found a letter
that Ammi had written to him.
The letter stated that...
Ammi was grateful that Abu had
accepted her and her unborn child.
Why didn't you tell us?
I was a bit shaken up.
What would I tell you?
Abu is not my father.
He loved you a lot.
He really loved you.
And us.
I mean, think about it.
Be it sports day or
parent-teacher meetings...
our fathers seldom came,
but Abu was always there.
Well, my father was dead.
So, if he showed up for sports day
it would've been a bit strange.
- You've got bail.
They're here.
Hi.
Imran.
Imran...
I'm Salman.
My friends, Arjun and Kabir.
- Hello.
- Thank you.
Hi... thank you.
You three look pretty hungover.
You're welcome to come over to
my place and freshen up.
Our bags and car are at the hotel.
I'll drive you there.
Come.
- Wow, this is beautiful.
It's really nice.
Are you always so polite?
It's absolute rubbish.
Anyone can do that.
This gentleman, my neighbour...
was obsessed with having his wife
immortalised in a potrait.
So, I applied my brush
and fulfilled his desire.
And with his money, paid my bills.
So, what are you guys doing in Seville?
Skydiving.
- Really?
- Yeah.
So, you jumped out of a plane
and landed in jail?
You could say that.
That apart, what do you do?
Well, I'm a financial broker.
In London.
Money man.
And you?
My family is in the construction business.
Well, never mind.
Everyone makes mistakes.
That's funny.
You're a Xerox copy of him.
And, what about you?
I write.
What?
I'm a copywriter in advertising.
Writing copy for ads is like
a buffet for the masses.
For instance, this painting is
for someone else.
Do you write anything
to feed your own soul?
I do.
Sir?
Salman.
Right. We'll be outside.
Your hands are very similar to mine.
Sit.
Do you live alone?
No.
I have a wife.
But she is away... in Paris.
Sit.
And any...
children?
Do you ever come to India?
Yes.
I was there four years ago
when my mother passed away.
- Sorry.
- I have a brother there...
but...
we don't meet.
I've often thought about you.
I mean...
that someday, somewhere we might meet.
But I never figured...
what I would say to you.
Just say the truth.
The truth... what is the truth?
Everyone has their own version.
Look... I was...
25 then.
Rahila was a few years younger.
When you're young
the future doesn't matter.
We were just kids.
One day...
Rahila told me that she's...
expecting a baby.
I wasrt ready for
the responsibility then.
And nor am I now.
So... you just abandoned her?
I guess, you could say that.
Rahila wanted a family,
she wanted to be a mother.
I had other dreams.
I wanted to be an artist.
I wanted to paint...
travel the world.
I loved her but...
she made her choice
and I made mine.
That's all.
I found out about you
only last year.
But...
you've always known about me.
Did you never want to see me?
I thought it was better this way.
You asked for the truth.
Well, this is it.
I... am sorry, lmran.
No, you're not.
Is there something
I can do for you?
Apologise only when it comes from here.
When clouds of pain loom in the sky
When a shadow of sadness flickers by
When a tear flnds it's way to the eye
When fear keeps the loneliness alive
I try and console my heart
Why is it that you cry? I ask
This is only what life imparts
These deep silences within
Have been handed out to all by time
Everyone's story has a little sorrow
Everyone's share has a little Sunshine
No need for water in your eyes
Every moment can be a new life
Why do you let them pass you by
Oh heart, why is it that you cry?
Morning...
Did you sleep or not?
No.
I think, we should get going.
Let's go.
Arjun...
I'm really sorry.
I'll see you at the car.
Yeah.
What do you mean,
'you slept in the car'?
Long story, babe.
Tell me, what happened?
Well, lmran just...
I'll tell you later, okay.
Why? Tell me now,
what happened?
I can't tell you right now.
I'll tell you when I'm back.
Why are you getting irritated?
Why are you going on about it?
Okay, forget it.
See.
It's our wedding card.
Can you see it?
Isn't it gorgeous?
I'm just so happy with it.
Oh... I've emailed a few options
for your suit.
Please select one. Okay?
Don't forget.
Okay.
You are so far away.
You love me, right?
Yeah.
Then stop fighting with me.
Everything was fine before you
went on this holiday.
Kabir, just come home.
To me, your family, your friends.
My friends are with me.
Yeah, I know.
But you know what I mean.
Happy birthday to you...
Happy birthday dear Anjali...
Oh my God!
It's beautiful!
- Nice, right?
- Yes!
Tanya?
What are you doing, baby?
I'm sorry, I'm so happy.
Kabir just proposed to Natasha.
- What??
Oh my God!
You could've waited until
your mother had cut the cake.
Kabir, this is the best birthday gift, ever!
I love you, son.
- The shy guy!
- It's a double celebration.
I'm so happy.
Now you have to call me 'mummy'.
- Get some champagne!
Come here.
Very good decision.
I'm so happy.
Babe, what just happened in there?
- What do you mean?
- I mean...
This ring...
I got it for my mom.
It's her birthday gift.
This is for your mom?
Look at it sweety...
it's a mummy ring.
What?
Why didn't you say something?
I tried.
But you were excited and screaming.
And Tanya made an announcement.
So you don't want to marry me?
It's not about you.
I haven't even thought about marriage.
What do I tell my father?
We'll say that
we gave it some more thought and...
we need more time.
That's all.
This is so embarrassing.
I'm so sorry, sweety.
You don't ever want to marry me?
It's not like that.
If it is, you better tell me right now!
I really love you, Kabir.
And I don't...
No, no... no sweety.
Don't cry.
Not now.
Kabir...
are you even serious
about this relationship or not?
You know what...
Will you marry me?
Who is it?
Room service.
Laila?
Hi!
Oh my God!
You're here... how... I mean...
Imran called and
he begged me to come.
- So I came.
- Imran?
I knew it.
He is my best friend.
I am... so glad you're here.
I'm glad you are glad.
Hello... my the two the love the birds!
Hello!
Surprised, Arjun?
Thank you.
It's good to see you.
- And you.
- Hey gorgeous.
- I love you too.
- Nice to have you back.
You got a tan!
Get dressed, soon!
- We had to leave at seven.
- Correct.
- Two minutes?
- You missed me?
I always miss you, darling.
Where are we going?
It's a surprise.
Can't tell you in front of him.
What's going on?
What do you mean?
It's San Fermin.
Running with the bulls.
- Really?
- Didrt you know?
Just follow me...
Holy shit!
Are these guys mad?
What are they doing?
Suicide.
Isn't that why you are here?
I felt this should be the
last experience of our trip.
This could be the
last experience of our life!
Stop it, Arjun.
Let's grab a bite.
Come on.
- Excuse me.
- Dude are you...
- I'm starving!
This is not an adventure sport.
I object, Judge sahab!
I agree it's not as safe as regular sports.
And is illegal in some countries.
But according to the
Spanish tradition and culture...
it is allowed.
And technically,
according to our deal...
we can choose any sport, remember?
Lmran, it's really dangerous, you know.
Yes, those bulls could kill us, alright?
We'll be dangling on their horns
like tandoori chicken on skewers!
Precisely the point.
You want to get rid of
the fear within you?
Well then, here's
our deepest fear. Death.
Let's face it.
Because beyond this fear...
lies victory!
Please spare us the tag lines!
Dude, think about it!
No training, no instructors.
Just us, my amigos!
And some bulls running after us.
If you want to live... just run!
Laila, do you know
any psychiatrist around here?
Because our amigo has
completely lost it!
I'll be at the starting line
at seven tomorrow morning.
With or without you.
I have something for you, lmran.
It's from Nuria.
It's in Spanish.
Love has no language.
So true.
I think you should
buy her something.
You're absolutely right.
Guys... next stop - shopping.
Count me out,
I'm going back to the hotel.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
That we'll only know after a test.
Test?
What do you say, Dr. Fraud?
Are you game?
Bring it on.
You have to say the first thing...
I know the drill. Ask!
Black.
Night.
Sea.
Salty.
Work.
Money.
Sex.
I like!
Friend.
You.
Marriage.
Family.
What?
Is that all?
It was enough.
Smartass...
You're using my trick on me?
Just say what you want to.
Okay.
You hesitated on 'marriage'.
So?
I'm just saying...
you hesitated... on marriage.
Look...
I don't have the time for this crap.
See you later.
- Okay.
- I'm sorry, I'm going to...
Kabir.
Go!
Kabir!
Kabir... man, just stop!
What?
Talk to us man.
What's going on?
It's nothing, really.
Kabir...
Look, I'm sorry I lost my cool.
Because I said you have
a problem with marriage?
I guess, I'm freaking out.
I don't know what's happening.
It's normal to be nervous.
It's not like you're having
an arranged marriage.
Yeah, but she isn't
the same person I met.
She's changed,
she's become possessive.
The girl I knew was a
talented, independent interior designer.
She enjoyed her work.
But now...
she's bid adieu to her passion and...
taken over my life.
Of course, I want a partner but...
I want my own life too!
The whole two bodies, one soul thing
I won't be able to handle it.
- May I ask you something?
- Yes.
Don't you think
you proposed to her too soon?
Actually, I didn't even propose.
- What?
I'd bought a ring for my mom
as a birthday gift.
Before giving it, I happened to show
it to Natasha and she thought...
it was meant for her.
- Are you crazy?
- What are you doing?
- What's wrong with him?
No wonder this vacation was
so important for you.
Meaning?
Basically, you wanted to hear from someone else
that you shouldn't get married
And besides us,
who would've told you this.
Have you totally lost it?
The invites are printed.
This isn't the time to overreact!
Kabir.
We know Natasha is a great girl.
And we know you like her.
And of course,
you don't want to hurt her.
But ask yourself...
Do you really want to marry her?
And if not, be honest.
To yourself and to her.
Of course, she'll be hurt.
But in the long run its best for both of you.
He is absolutely right, Kabir.
But I've made a commitment.
Okay, you screwed up.
No one's going to send you to prison.
It's not that simple.
Our parents are involved.
Parents?
Dude, it's your life.
You won't get it.
Just...
Just let it be, okay?
I'm sorry.
Kabir...
What a guy!
Laila?
Why're you shouting?
Why are you so far?
Better?
Best.
Ammi?
How are you?
I met Salman.
I now know why you and Abu
kept this from me.
I'm sorry, Ammi.
- I love you.
I love you too, my boy.
It took a while but
I've now learnt to live
Without the consolation of tears
There is someone who brought to mind
How I had gotten left behind
Life is like a caravan
Why are you lonely, my man
Just know that we are all here
The first rocket indicates that
the pen gates have been opened.
Second rocket indicates that
the bulls are coming towards us.
We run at the second rocket.
Second rocket.
Oh San Fermin, please protect us.
If I die...
my spirit will come back to haunt you.
Why are you thinking about death?
Think about what you'll do
if you survive.
Listen...
a new pact.
An if-l-get out-alive pact.
If I get out alive,
I'll let you read my poetry.
Why just you? I'll just...
get it published.
You write poetry?
Yes.
Okay.
If I get out alive...
Okay!
I'll go to Morocco with Laila.
Yeah!
That's what I'll do.
What's the worst that could happen?
I'll get fired.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Who cares man?
I'll be with her and I will live.
Well done, my bro!
Come on, Kabir.
Okay.
If I get out alive...
Shit guys!
The gates are open!
Kabir just say it.
It's okay, just say it.
If I get out alive,
I'll go to London...
and tell Natasha that...
Say what?
Just say it!
Come on, Kabir!
- Come on, Kabir!
- Come on!
I'm sorry but I can't marry you.
- Congratulations!
- Look out!
If you're carrying
your restlessness in your heart
You are alive
If you're carrying
the lightning of dreams in your eyes
You are alive
Like a gust of wind,
learn to live free
Learn to flow like
the waves that make a sea
Let your arms be wide open,
to every moment you meet
May every moment gift you
a new sight to greet
If you're carrying
your wonder in your eyes
You are alive
If you're carrying
your restlessness in your heart
You are alive
In the arms of the sun now life will be
With the rays in our breath
And a shine when we speak
In the arms of the sun now life will be
With the rays in our breath
And a shine when we speak
In the arms of the sun now life will be
With the rays in our breath
And a shine when we speak
Just when the heart
started moving to another beat
Out of nowhere
a new thought found its feet
That life gives you just one shot
So why not love it with all you've got
Who knows what we're waiting for
'Cause life is here and life is now
What was only a desire till yesterday
Is esactly what we've found today
Hand in hand let's always be
As we wander through our destiny
And all day and all night
Happiness rains down on
everything in sight
In the arms of the sun now life will be
With the rays in our breath
And a shine when we speak
In the arms of the sun now life will be
With the rays in our breath
And a shine when we speak
If it can knit a new dream everyday
Then you can call it a life
If it can lead you down a brand new way
If it can flirt and fly,
If it can spin and jive
Then you can call it a life